<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-25T22:03:57.118Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-24T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0b]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Planit]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Andrés Silva ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/886e5099-c235-42af-9ffa-6975dab73c80.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Merqueo]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Andrés Escobar ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/a46e305a-0953-4e1b-a6b0-5c0c5f2b0608.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[ Frubana Colombia]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Matí­as Troncar ]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/9ef89afb-b066-46b0-b497-7d1caddc221e.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>These delivery platforms are focusing on technology to optimize prices and processes to provide ever-more convenience to their users.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Delivery Platforms]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[delivery-platforms]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Planit is the first grocery retailer that does not want customers to run out of goods. We noticed that for many customers, doing grocery shopping was a hassle, especially for recurrent products in which customers were brand loyal. With our planned delivery added value, customers will be able to map out their future consumption and receive items just as they run out of them to prevent rushing for last-minute purchases. Our biggest challenge has been introducing new customers to this new way of purchasing groceries, everything through subscriptions. However, we have learned that once a customer makes a purchase, the cross-purchasing is done by itself with a current churn lower than 5%. The final consumer loves our value proposition as it saves them time and money. We are working on showing final consumers that traditional grocery shopping is not as fun as they think and that Planit is the solution for all the wasted time. We are doing a series of A/B tests with several activation techniques. From invite-only events, to massive discounts&mdash;we are trying everything.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Merqueo&rsquo;s value proposition is to democratize retail with low prices and convenience since about 75-80% of our sales go to low-income households. In terms of price, we have less operational expenses because we do not have big retail stores or warehouses. We just have dark stores, and then we deliver to customers&rsquo; doors. Being fully integrated for us has three large advantages. The first is that we control the service that we provide. Second, our inventory is real because it is ours, and no one is going to call a customer and say &ldquo;we do not have stock&rdquo; or &ldquo;we cannot find that&rdquo; because our inventory is maintained online. The third thing is that our suppliers supply directly to us, so we do not have intermediaries in the value chain. That is why we can offer lower prices: we are a pure player. In Colombia, we are in 25-26 cities. We have four warehouses or dark stores in Bogot&aacute; and six more in other Colombian cities. There is no need to open in new cities in Colombia; we just need to have more active users.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Frubana is a technology company serving small restaurants in Latam. We bring restaurants with a one-stop-shop solution on where to purchase all restaurant inputs&mdash;fruits, vegetables, proteins, grains, oils and others. For restaurants, this is an efficient way of buying goods, and they can also find better prices than in the market. They can manage all of this by a mobile application. We also serve producers, from food growers owned by small families, to sophisticated industry-integrated companies. We can provide small producers with better prices for what they produce and we work with them on the quality assessments. We also make alliances with large companies such as Grupo Nutresa, that we partner with to distribute their products., reaching a portion of the market that they wouldn't do otherwise. We deliver value in these ways to different participants and work across the value chain, from product quality control, to warehousing and logistics. The distinguishing factor of Frubana is the technology we implement to drive processes. It is one thing to build a delivery company, but we have developed our own processes and systems that are driven by technology and AI.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-24T15:03:36.049Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0a]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Fortox]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Guillermo Dulcey]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[ Regional Manager]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ G4S]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Mauricio Gutiérrez]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/cb882588-c97a-48bb-8e90-423267361489.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ Country Manager,]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Grupo Atlas]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Luí­s Fernando Garcí­a]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/f3b0608d-fb2b-4c23-a01c-c8af10641196.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[ General Manager]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[ Prosegur Colombia]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[Luí­s Fernando Carvajal]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/cc955d04-8341-482c-8715-1ea6492cef42.jpg]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[ General Director Security]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>With private security corresponding to at least 1% of Colombian GDP and growing continuously, the sector is a source of significant employment.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Security]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[security-colombia-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>What makes us stand apart from the competition is our devotion and commitment to service. First, we are a company of people serving people. Therefore, we primarily focus on many activities to ensure that those relationships with our different stakeholders are solid. For instance, we strive to have good communication and understanding our clients&rsquo; needs is valuable to us. We want to be able to see their forecasts, projections and expectations of their market, so we can contribute from our end. A second important aspect of our differentiation is the way quality concepts are embedded in our company culture. We were the first company in Latin America have the ISO 9001 Quality Certification for guarding services. Since our certification in 2000, it was of outmost importance that we designed our administration model having always in mind the quality of our services and its improvements. Since then, we have certified different aspects of our business, which has allowed as to have a reliable managing system with its respective KPIs to follow up.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>G4S is not merely the biggest security company in the world, though it works to stay at the top. It is important to have values that encompass everyone, from the CEO to the everyday employees. It is necessary to have a statement that includes corporate values such as making things right, doing business correctly, and even the sustainability of the clients and the company. G4S was acquired by an American company called Allied Universal, which means G4S is no longer a British, publicly owned company. Allied Universal made a great effort to expand and helped G4S to grow and consolidate its position in the market. Furthermore, we do not want to stop developing everyday services, such as alarm monitoring. We plan to continue offering this service and improving it to meet changing standards. We are leaders in the market thanks to our knowledge, training, and professionalism in sector. There are chances to grow, even though we are facing global competition, especially in Colombia.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Grupo Atlas has 13,600 employees, making us the largest employer in private security. We believe the security personnel to be the real hero, the real company manager, a person that performing a vital role. We have an employees&rsquo; fund and benefit fund, and offer indefinite term contracts, family welfare policies (celebrating Mother&rsquo;s Day, Children&rsquo;s Day, Father&rsquo;s Day). Of our almost 14,000 employees, at least 2,600 are women, which is an aspect I would like to highlight. Women are in fact better are security jobs than men, because they tend be more aware and notice more things that might not be immediately apparent. Women at Atlas occupy both management and operational positions. Additionally, we help our employees with housing plans through Family Welfare Funds, so that everyone who works with us can have a house. We also have a Career Plan, through which employees who enter the company as guards can work their way up to higher positions.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[<p>Prosegur has a differentiating factor and an important asset: our presence in 26 countries. Currently, the knowledge and expertise we gain globally, we apply locally in Colombia along with a deeper knowledge of regional realities. To us, regional expertise is of extreme importance. That means acknowledging our customers, our business, and our reality that, one way or another, is extremely individual: what afflicts one sector most likely is not the same thing that afflicts another. Blending that local experience with better practices and acknowledged situations that occur in other countries of the region and of the world makes us unique. We are working on the complete integration between physical security and technology. Our model allows us to not only reach our clients and satisfy their needs in everything related to physical security but also offer them a solid number of alternatives in electronic security.</p>]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-23T12:48:12.186Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-22T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5538d67986b7b0108818c458]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Baker Hughes Colombia]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Jaime Romero]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/06fcd918-6bee-41b8-8f10-f4dc5c1b7897.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[ General Director Andean Region (OFS)]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ Lupatech Colombia]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Jorge Iván Torres ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/50624925-116a-422b-ae66-090897bf4a05.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[President]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Estrella Energy]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Ricardo Sarmiento]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/86d35340-437f-4b10-bdec-e36804d235f4.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[ CEO]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>With oil and gas production and activity growing in Colombia, service providers are stepping up to provide customized technical solutions and competitive prices to help customers achieve their production goals.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Oil & Gas Service Providers]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[oil-gas-service-providers]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Baker Hughes is an energy technology company focused on the development of the energy industry. Specifically, within the oil and gas space, we have serviced all three market segments&mdash;upstream, midstream, and downstream&mdash;horizontally including these segments in the digital business. We take energy forward&mdash;making it safer, cleaner, and more efficient for people and the planet. We seek to anticipate the needs of the market. We work closely with our clients, not only to identify their needs, but also to anticipate where we can help them find solutions that allow them to carry out their projects by presenting the best cost-benefit options for all parties under full compliance and respect of international and local regulations. We are the only company in the sector that covers all market segments (full stream), and we continue to make progress in strengthening ourselves, which allows us to continue being a benchmark in the worldwide oil and gas industry. We pride ourselves in having excellent human capital, especially when it comes to driving diversity, equity, and inclusion. Our continuous commitment to investing millions of dollars in R&amp;D allows us to be at the forefront of technology worldwide.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Lupatech is focused on technological services within oil and gas. We have a presence across Latin America and stand out for combining on-the-ground expertise with a global vision of business. We have around 400 collaborators, and most of the technical and management teams have extensive international experience in different markets worldwide. Such markets include offshore deep and shallow water, land fields, high and low tier, high-pressure gas, mature fields, exploration projects. Colombia is mostly a land market, though we provide all that experience within our team at our clients&rsquo; disposal. In addition, we have presence in all oil and gas producing regions in Colombia with three operating bases strategic located in Villavicencio, Barrancabermeja, and Neiva. Part of our DNA is finding unique solutions for our clients. Large companies have cumbersome processes of R&amp;D that prevent them from having a flexible approach whereas we are a local company with highly technical international alliances and can bring technologies within our sector to Colombia to provide local solutions. We work to accommodate the technologies to the problems that our clients have in Colombia. We have been following this strategy for the last 10 years with a positive market reception.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>We have exposure in Colombia, our main focus area, as well as Argentina, and to a degree in Chile and Peru. We are a Tier-2 type of company, oilfield-wise, and have around 1,400 employees, where, again, Colombia accounts for the bulk. Our main focus in Colombia is drilling for exploration and production, thus &ldquo;development&rdquo; and well services (cementing and coiled tubing). Education has always factored into the sector. What we have done over the past six years is bring young talent from universities and nurture them rapidly to fill out different positions, both on the technical and leadership sides. We must provide our employees with best possible training, and to do so we developed our own university, which today offers over 50 courses. We also provide training to some of our clients in specific areas. It is mandatory for all of us, including myself, to go through all of the courses. They vary from highly technical to soft-skill training. The other thing is, we are pursuing career development plans for our younger generation and implementing them quickly as this new generation is destined to becoming the future leaders of this company.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T22:40:30.700Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5538d67986b7b0108818c458]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Normet Colombia]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Laura Torres ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/df4129a7-3350-42bf-bd24-a0bb843ce98a.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[MD]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ Core Tech Colombia]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[José Carlos Restrepo]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/78532aa7-1c3e-4893-85a3-83ea047cbc21.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ General Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Kluane Colombia]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Jhon Puerta ]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/52fdf234-f480-4e00-b13d-69ba1b9a6643.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[General Manager]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Given that most mining companies Colombia are still behind in mining technologies, knowledgeable service providers act as strategic allies that can help them improve the efficiency of their operations while controlling costs.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Service providers]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[service-providers-colombia-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Our target market is underground construction in mining and tunneling. Normet is a Finnish company with more than 60 years in the business, operating on over 50 locations in around 30 countries worldwide. Considered a pioneer, Normet expertise is based on providing support to our customers improving underground and tunneling processes with knowledge, innovation, and technology translating in productivity, efficiency, and profitability for our client&rsquo;s business. We work hand in hand with our client from the beginning of the project till it ends enriching processes with this continuous feedback. Our main objective is to use our technology, innovation, experience and knowledge to enhance mining and tunneling practices. Normet celebrates 60 years in 2022, and we have been in Colombia for nine years. However, growing our market is a step-by-step process. We want to show Colombia that we can assist with excellency in mining and tunneling processes with knowledge, innovative technology, and solid support. Through our work, we are committed to delivering maximum value with a positive impact in the environment, people and customers also on generating a more sustainable future.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Core Tech has been over 25 years working as a strategic partner for the mining industry, delivering high value cost efficient solutions in Mexico, Colombia, Peru, and exporting to other countries in the region. We strive to add value to our customers, by helping them control the operation costs per meter in exploration and production drilling operations and their mining process, our field support team works hand in hand with our clients field personnel to ensure products are used in the safest way possible, controlling drilling and mining costs and ensuring them and the community that products used are environmentally responsible. We are constantly monitoring new innovations and strive to come up with some of our own innovative solutions to bring to the market the latest available technologies available in the markets we work for. We are always looking for new solutions that help the industry reduce the cost per meter and increase their productivity in the safest, most environmentally responsible way possible. Efficiency gains are obtained when a good product is paired with a highly trained operations personnel and overall good practices in operations.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>What makes us stand out is that we have smaller equipment, but that can handle higher capacity. In other words, we have machines that can drill up to 2,000 meters that can easily be transported. We don&rsquo;t need a railroad to transport the machinery as it can be broken into modules and can be transported easily. We use three small motors instead of one large one and the machine is portable enough that it can be disassembled completely. And if the customer needs the transport to be done quicker, we would use a helicopter. Our advantage there is that we can use a smaller sized one for transporting the machine. Kluane, through innovation, offers more opportunities with efficiency and versatility. At the same time, we are more environmentally friendly. Most of our customers have deposits in the mountains. Locations that are more complicated to reach with heavier machinery. That is why Kluane specializes more in metallic mining, because in Colombia and Ecuador most of those minerals are deposited in higher topographical regions. Places where it is hard to lay a railroad and where there are many obstacles.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T21:24:38.267Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5538d67986b7b0108818c458]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Minerales Córdoba]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Santiago Varela ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/4fa39ff5-50a3-4678-9c3b-7b8a7745d0b1.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[General Manager]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Minera Cobre de Colombia]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Hamyr González ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/8cd08e72-a042-4f47-98e3-7acd74afa206.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[President]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Atico Mining Corporation]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Fernando E. Ganoza ]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/67da54a3-5108-4aa0-b75f-ef18dfe12c5f.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[CEO & Director]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Given that copper is one of the metals of the future and the immense copper resources around Colombia, the country has a great opportunity to become a key global player in the copper market.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Copper]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[santiago-varela-general-manager-minerales-cordoba]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Minerales C&oacute;rdoba is a Canadian-based company, committed to the sustainable development of mining projects in the department of C&oacute;rdoba and other regions in Colombia, under the conviction of creating value for the communities and the country in general. We have strong financial and technical support from our shareholders, which guarantees the transfer of their know-how to the project. The company&rsquo;s management team has extensive experience in the acquisition, exploration, and development of world-class mining projects and a proven track record in discovering new porphyry deposits in unexplored areas. In addition, the San Mat&iacute;as Project, located south of C&oacute;rdoba, is structured to bring prosperity to the region and its communities, which is essential for its development. We seek to become a relevant participant in the development of the country by consolidating one of the three most important mining projects for the national government. The commissioning of the project will bring innumerable benefits to the region, through an ambitious open-pit operation, in which we estimate a production of around 474,000 tons of copper, 1 million ounces of gold, and almost 8 million ounces of silver, in an estimated time of 13 years.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Minera Cobre de Colombia has a long history operating successfully within its region of interest and strong support from its Canadian parent company, MCC Mining Corporation. Minera Cobre holds the most promising and extensive copper exploration portfolio in the country. We want to be the company recognized for developing the potential of copper in the country, while being environmentally and socially engaged and responsible. Through our persistent efforts and solid international financial support, we are in the position to offer Colombia the opportunity to develop a healthy and sustainable copper industry that would offset the country&rsquo;s economic overdependence on carbon exports. Minera Cobre holds the most important portfolio of copper exploration projects in Colombia and one of the most important in the world. We are exploring for large porphyry copper deposits of the same type that occur throughout the rest of the prolific Andean copper belt extending from Chile, Argentina, Peru and Ecuador and continues into Panama. The Andean copper belt is responsible for 40% of the world&rsquo;s copper production. We have discovered porphyry copper deposits with principal by-product contents in gold and molybdenum, which add significantly to the potential economic value of the targets.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Atico is a Canadian company that trades on the Toronto Stock Exchange. We are focused on copper and gold mining in Latin America. We have an operating copper mine in Colombia, El Roble, and a project in Ecuador. El Roble has been in operation for over 30 years, and we took it from a small mine to a mid-sized, underground operation with high standards. It is one of the few modern underground mines in Colombia and the only copper concentrate producer in the country. This the first time Colombia is moving, storing, and shipping it. From that perspective, the infrastructure that we have created will create a path for other copper producers that follow in our footsteps. One specialization is underground mining. In the copper world, most mines are large open-pit mines. So, from the underground perspective, we have introduced many high standards in terms of safety, the environment, and the technology employed. There are few modern underground mines in Colombia, and El Roble is a prime example. And the logistics of producing, moving, and selling the concentrate is another key aspect that is helping the country understand how best to move copper concentrates.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T13:23:20.650Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c07]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Ernst & Young]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Edgar Sánchez ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/bf3dc021-5dc0-4f07-a2a8-5d15ff02a9c0.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Country Managing Partner]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Deloitte Spanish Latin America]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Julio Berrocal ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/410362ae-568b-49a0-8042-7337c5997620.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Partner - CEO Andean Region]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Mazars Colombia]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Carlos Andrés Molano]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/4360c5b2-30e3-4df8-bbae-c929e297702a.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[ Managing Partner]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[PwC Colombia]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[Carlos Mario Lafaurie ]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/b5d740b9-207f-42c0-9fec-ef0ecf2139f2.jpg]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[President]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Providing multiple services across all sectors and with a presence in several countries, these accounting firms are able to offer clients a wealth of services that meet their evolving needs.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Accounting]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[accounting-colombia-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>We provide services to over 1,500 companies in Colombia every year in all sectors. EY has two lines of business: audit and consulting, which includes management, technology, risk, transaction, and tax consulting. The question around this is how do we provide confidence. First is through transparency. When we work as auditors, we give transparency to the markets so they can make better decisions. In terms of our consulting business, it is about providing real-life solutions to real problems using technology and being innovative and putting them in place. A key theme with consultants is that we want to go beyond diagnosing; we want to be partners and help companies improve processes. You need to go to a specialist in the end and focus on solutions that will solve the problem not only in the short term but in the medium term. We need to talk about blockchain as it is at the center of many things now. EY has a network, and someone has done a similar project elsewhere, so we provide information on how something works within a context. It is not a one solution fits all.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Our value proposition is based on our purpose. Our global purpose as an organization, which also includes Colombia, is to create impacts that transcend to all the interest groups that are involved with Deloitte. This not only includes our talent, the community, and government agencies but also our clients and suppliers. In some way, that purpose is reflected in the services we offer our clients, which aims to help them achieve their business strategic goals based on our experience, our knowledge, our innovation, and the information confidentiality and information safety of our clients, supported on a global knowledge network at the service of our Colombian clients. Deloitte wants to be a strategic partner for companies and offer the global and international knowledge the company has. We have five business lines&mdash;audit and assurance, financial advisory, risk advisory, consulting, legal and tax services &mdash;with which we want to offer a 360-degree focus on the solutions we offer. We offer services per business line, but when needed, we can integrate all our business lines to offer a complete service portfolio.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Mazars is an international firm of French origin with about 44,000 professionals around the world. We have officially been called Mazars in Colombia for about four years, and today we number around 250 people, has grown by approximately 50% annually since 2016. We are a one-stop shop offering all the services entrepreneurs need to develop their businesses. We offer what is known as auditing and statutory audit. We offer outsourcing, accounting, payroll, treasury, tax compliance, internal auditing, controls, security, risks, and so forth, including financial advisory services. Those cover all transaction services, corporate finance, legal, validations, and mergers and acquisitions. We also perform financial modeling, where we have the number one team in the world by several economic models. We audit financial models or deploy them. We also have a section for tax and legal services, a law firm of 30 people that handles corporate, labor, tax, foreign exchange, and legal advice. We also provide litigation and arbitration and have worked on transfer pricing, which is rather technical.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[<p>In July 2021, the firm launched its new strategy globally, &ldquo;New equation.&rdquo; The concept of new equation drives two main aspects. The first has to do with changes, and we need to help companies navigate a period of geopolitical instability, climate change, and regulatory updates. The second is reinforcing the mechanisms that generate trust within the community. In order to achieve this, the firm came up with a strategy aimed at people who think about the present and the future. We need people who work as a community of solvers. In order to be part of this, we need to have different professional backgrounds, different levels of experience, and different profiles, so that we can continue to develop the firm&rsquo;s main goal throughout its history: to build trust and solve problems. All our strategic concepts around the new equation come from uniting this experienced, interdisciplinary human talent team with technology to help companies face changes while retaining the trust of the people. Only then will it be possible for them to maintain sustainable results.</p>]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T12:53:19.123Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c07]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Brigard Urrutia (BU)]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Sergio Michelsen ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/2e5fc9fd-d311-4438-8a8b-f57f2da489f5.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Senior Partner]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ Lloreda & Camacho]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Ángela Salazar]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/5d380d1b-fa60-4007-8583-1fc7e2376199.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Partner]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[ Muñoz Tamayo & Asociados]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Diego Muñoz ]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/c78279a8-0819-4234-a521-eedf91b9be7d.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[Founding Partner]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[ Triana, Uribe & Michelsen]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[Juan Pablo Triana ]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/965d87d1-07eb-46ed-a26b-05be6e0b8e05.jpg]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[Lead Partner]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>These legal firms help investors doing business in Colombia navigate uncertainties and provide local expertise to give them peace of mind and ensure successful operations.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Legal]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[legal-colombia-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to the firm&rsquo;s size and trajectory, BU has contributed to the design of Colombia&rsquo;s regulatory framework. We can provide certainty about the spirit of the law and in terms of how it is interpreted in congress. Other practitioners do not have that knowledge simply because they were not involved in the design of the law. Additionally, projects of national interest often involve liaising at the international level, which makes BU&rsquo;s identity as a global firm especially relevant. The firm can draw experience from similar processes elsewhere to strengthen advisory. Being a national firm with an international spirit enhances our reputation. BU has a close connection with the business community, which this means we can provide advisory from both a legal and business sense. We can communicate better and express succinctly what companies must do in order to bring their projects to fruition. When you understand their mindset, you immediately become their ally. As well as being business-oriented, we focus strongly on professional excellency. A law firm is basically the people. We are rigorous with selection in order to ensure every client receives the best service. Finally, employee talent is our number-one priority.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Lloreda Camacho is a leading innovative law firm. We have more than 80 years of experience working side by side with our clients and building successful legal strategies customized for them. Our goal is to always be at the top of the legal market. What makes us different and stand out from other firms is, without doubt, our top-notch team. We are a group of 150 individuals, comprised of 12 partners, more than 50 lawyers, eight technical advisers, and almost 80 people in our support staff, all of whom are ready to assist our clients 24/7. It is in our DNA to know our client&rsquo;s goals, to be proactive and to give practical solutions. We are different to other law firms because our partners are always fully involved in all the matters related to our clients, and the clients really appreciate such involvement. We have clients in all the fields of the economy, for e.g., pharmaceuticals, entertainment, telecommunications, and mining and natural resources. We have been lucky enough to assist most of the key players in the market in such fields. Our life sciences practice is also strong.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>We are a law firm with an international profile; between 60 and 70% of our revenue comes from international clients. When we started 27 years ago, the country was undergoing an interesting process regarding the new constitution, economic opening, and opportunities that allowed equal conditions for all. Within that process, we identified several possibilities where we could participate without facing considerable competition. One of the sectors that we identified was incoming privatizations, and we were fortunate enough to get involved in the first one. This led us to an important number of privatizations in the energy, gas transportation, electricity, and telecommunications sectors. That marked the projection of the firm in three important lines: mergers and acquisitions, to the extent that privatizations are the most complex, sophisticated, and transversal form; they involve a complex structure process that had never existed until then in Colombia, with project financing and the structuring of guarantees; and regulatory compliance. The most important factor is that the client always feels well attended to, and we have to be able to respond swiftly and attentively. We must be able to not only serve reactively, but also proactively anticipate their needs.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[<p>The firm serves as the point of entry to Colombia for investors, helping them organize employment contracts, registering their brands, renting an office, and so on. Our department, which is the corporate side, is the gateway to Colombia for foreigners. The firm works nonstop from dawn to dusk. We are our own prosecutor and auditor, and being close knit means we are aware of what works and what does not. Second, between us, there must be equity, justice, and proportionality. This stability has been maintained for the past 27 years. The third point is that our goal is to achieve, not to grow. We can only provide what we can control. Our motto is personalization of the service. The ability to respond immediately. Customization, around quality, is maintained, as we want it to be. A client may well arrive around commercial or civil litigation, and at some point, the work touches our corporate department and intellectual property, which is extremely robust and market leading. Or we might be working on a corporate issue, and it might later involve intellectual property. We always accompany our clients every step of the way, and our clients notice that closeness and 24/7 commitment.</p>]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[<p>Our team is heavily oriented toward and trained in FDI regulations. We are used to working in English even more than Spanish and being trained in highly advanced business English is not common in Colombia. More than anything, we deliver on time and we are on time for meetings. Both things might sound insignificant, though they ultimately make a difference. Our experience of 15 years has been in FDI, where we follow developments in free trade agreements, double taxation agreements, and everything to do with currency regulations, which can be rather delicate and complex at times. Our style has always been to learn about the project and to understand what the company is about and their local objectives. We design a project that, from a legal standpoint, helps them achieve their goals. We review those projects every six months to see where things are going and make the necessary adjustments. More than just reacting to a specific need, we like to develop a legal project for the company to make sure they achieve their goals, and that makes the difference. We have clients of 15 years that joined us on their first day in Colombia and are doing great business today.</p>]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[José Abusaid]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[Abusaid Gomez]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[Founder & Partner]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/d20cf74c-c61d-461d-b1b0-fe223c353d2f.jpg]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-07T23:35:26.501Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-07T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0d]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Odeon Properties]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Julien Dufour]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/6cf4a9b0-d5dd-41df-b95b-49b4933bc2d2.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Managing Partner]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Vogue Homes]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Joaquim da Silva Lico]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/7b5b5766-8e61-4eda-9b15-d50ec6c16825.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Lantia]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Eduardo Kol Netto de Almeida]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/ce193627-7258-4b3c-b358-c4e19fe062a3.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[Bondstone]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[Antonio Pereira Dias]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/3a5a2a22-d3f0-473b-bc48-a1a80b281642.jpg]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[Chief Investment Officer & CFO]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Portugal is now seeing a new breed of more sophisticated and financially savvy developers seeking to better attract international buyers to invest in their projects.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Local Real Estate Players]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[local-real-estate-players-in-portugal-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Odeon Properties develops diverse and unique real estate projects in prime or strategic locations in and around Lisbon. Each project is led by excellent architects that focus on preserving the culture of each asset, while using high quality products. This is a winning strategy for sustainability and exposure. From a historical theater transformation into a large restaurant and luxury apartments to large city center villa-homes, Odeon Properties projects and concepts standout for themselves. The Odeon historical theater from the 1920s was also the inspiration project that led to the company&rsquo;s name. This one-of-a-kind real estate asset was carefully thought out and planned to include the refurbishment of the fa&ccedil;ade. Despite the apartment units being spacious and modern, the 900 square meter restaurant will incorporate the very essence of the historical building through the refurbishment of the original 24-m high column and pediment.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>In Melides, we are currently developing a project called Utopia that perfectly melds the concepts of integration, valorization, and sustainability; Utopia emphasizes its natural surroundings as it shapes a new natural and social ecosystem that is stable, balanced and self-sufficient. We have also formed a collaboration with the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) to establish a more sustainable construction technique. Utopia will be a reference point within the industry. For this project, we will be taking into consideration the local ecosystem, from concept to construction. We have involved a team of both national and international architects to design the 230 houses that will make up Utopia. It is a project whose strategic orientation is based on principles and factors. Concepts such as comfort, sophistication combined with innovation, energy efficiency, and differentiation of design will form the starting point of the complex.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Since the beginning, what differentiates us is that we design homes for people to live in. We focus on taking our time and investing heavily to design our properties. As we start doing the layout, from design and even all the way to construction, we always look at how we can improve properties, even after they are sold. Fortunately, we have been selling well; our biggest problem is that everything has been sold. Our base of investors is different from our competition. Many of them have big corporations behind them, while we do not. All our investors are individuals. We started with a group of three or four, and we now have around 12 diverse investors from the UK, Germany, Poland, Hong Kong, Macau, Brazil, South Africa, Turkey, and Portugal. It is an interesting and diverse group. We are here for the long term and currently have plans and goals to buy two projects in the next two years. We are looking for projects in the range of 7,000-15,000sqm in the Lisbon area.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[<p>Our major competitive advantage is our investment management capabilities and the way we approach and monitor our real estate projects. We are careful with the concept and the quality of the product, and we always keep in mind that we are a private equity real estate firm, managing investments with strict investment criteria. That is a different mindset from the typical developer. We earn the trust of our investors by delivering strong, risk adjusted returns, focusing on IRR. We build, execute and manage strong investment cases. Bondstone delivers this by merging a team of highly sophisticated investment professionals with a quantitative mindset with a team of solid and capable project managers from construction and engineering backgrounds. We speak the same language of our investors while delivering investment projects that cater to very specific investment constraints.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-07T11:22:08.149Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-06T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c08]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Costa Duarte]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Martim Costa Duarte]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/bdf20408-1b81-46e1-bfcd-85ba495f08ce.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Executive Board Member]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Verspieren]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Rogério Dias]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/20f6b53f-a56b-4f89-900c-174dd6191f0b.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Managing Director]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Tranquilidade Generali]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Pedro Carvalho]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/4389f1ea-b1c1-450d-b683-c4ff1b6d3faa.png]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[Ageas Portugal]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[Steven Braekeveldt]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/35f961df-7fed-403e-9ff7-81df84167851.jpg]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>The pandemic has only reinforced the importance of insurance and the need for the sector to develop innovative solutions that will best serve the interests of society.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Portugal Insurance Forum]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[portugal-insurance-forum-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Costa Duarte is a family-owned business, already in its fourth generation, and the core business is exclusive focused in insurance and risk management related matters, providing services as insurance consultants and brokers. Costa Duarte is an independent broker, 100% Portuguese, and it is one of the market leaders in the insurance sector. Since 1921, Costa Duarte has been acquiring expertise and capabilities in several areas of insurance-related services mainly but not limited to property and casualty risks, employee benefits, credit and bonds, motor fleet management, affinities, cyber risks, public procurement and claims management for Portuguese and multinational corporate clients. Costa Duarte has been servicing its clients around the world through strategic alliances with international partners. Our clients require and expect the highest level of service and advice, and this remains the main focus and priority of the team. We are committed to providing a service of excellence to our clients, partners, and stakeholders to help the sector continue to evolve.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Our mission is to better respond to the increasingly sophisticated needs of our national and international clients, regarding risk management and the implementation of insurance solutions. We have strengthened our global service&rsquo;s offering and have acquired an increased negotiation capacity, shaped by our foundations: the 2019 merger between Mediator and Credite-EGS, two well recognized insurance brokers; and belonging to a multinational group as solid as the Verspieren Group, created in 1880, and which includes 21 companies in France dedicated to insurance brokerage and consultancy. We are committed to the digital way of doing business and to leverage the brand on the Portuguese market: upskilling and reskilling are fundamental to better prepare our teams for the digital transformation, the changing future and the always evolving customers. In the short term, we are focused on creating a new sales team. In the medium term, we are developing a new organizational culture to prepare our organization for the future.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Generali Seguros, as part of Generali Group, is currently the second-largest player in the property and casualty insurance market in Portugal, with a market share of 18.81%, offering a wide range of policies addressed to individuals and businesses, sold mainly under the historic brand Tranquilidade. Founded over 150 years ago, and adopting a multi-channel distribution strategy, which can count on the largest network of agents in Portugal (representing approximately 70% of the company&rsquo;s total premiums), brokers, and a direct channel. Innovation and digitalization are in Tranquilidade&rsquo;s DNA. We quickly responded to the pandemic and the lockdown, &ldquo;reinventing&rdquo; our business and adapting to the challenging environment such as offering telemedicine and remote physiotherapy to our customers, having first-mover advantage in offering COVID-19 specific protection to SMEs, and fully digitalizing our communication channels (chatbot, WhatsApp, mobile app), including claims settlement, all this whilst integrating three insurance companies.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[<p>The Ageas Portugal Group&rsquo;s ecosystem is strong and has numerous service and product offerings with a presence in a wide range of distribution channels. Grupo Ageas Portugal had a market share of 16.4%, in 2021, reinforced when compared to 2020, with premium growth above the market. Innovation is a key determinant of business success and is in the DNA of the Ageas Portugal Group and its brands, as exemplified by the creation of the first private network of health providers with M&eacute;dis, or the first insurer to market car insurance by phone and internet through Seguro Directo. The insurance industry has a great deal of space for innovation, which is challenging. We have numerous projects such as, for example, the Impact School, an entrepreneurship and social innovation program that the Funda&ccedil;&atilde;o Ageas has in partnership with Impact Hub Lisbon. I would also highlight the Ageas Innovation Hackathon initiative in partnership with Nova SBE that challenges university students to find innovative solutions to real cases related to the world of insurance.</p>]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-05T21:27:15.401Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-04T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c08]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Oney Bank Portugal]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Dario Coffetti ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/7f5c4b7b-a639-467f-9cf0-1ddc72ab0f68.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ BFF Banking Group]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Nuno Francisco]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/0ff7190b-7394-4c16-9afa-d35959d526e7.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ Head of Portugal]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[ Banco Carregosa]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Francisco Oliveira Fernandes]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/1c14f0dc-abb1-4091-9df4-f1f2b4831a18.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[ CEO]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Banks provide a high level of specialization, flexible financial solutions, extensive experience, and tailor-made solutions to clients&rsquo; needs to stand out in an increasingly competitive market.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Banking]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[banking-portugal-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>The French entity Auchan created Oney more than three decades ago. The Portuguese branch was created 28 years ago, the first one created outside France. Portugal is the second-largest subsidiary within the group, both in terms of results and in terms employees, with 400 team members. Our branch has almost all banking activities. We offer all financial products, such as credit cards, personal credit, insurance and so on, and the possibility of buying and paying in instalments, which follows the Buy Now Pay Later (BNPL) trend. In Portugal, we have 1 million customers in a country that has 10 million inhabitants. One key differential factor was investing in digital channels from the beginning. And parallel to this, we were innovating with the now BNPL trend, which allows us to keep having new commerce partners and to grow in the Portuguese market. We have a different, unique vision of financial services and payment solutions: we reshape them to be more modern, responsible, and human. We consider ourselves to a partner in the transformation of commerce. With our thousands of retail partners, we give everyone the opportunity and power to improve their daily lives and consume better.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>BFF Banking Group&rsquo;s core business focuses on credit management and the acquisition of trade receivables towards public entities&mdash;a niche service where BFF sets itself apart from the market due to its level of expertise and specialization in this segment, for which there is effectively no similar competition. We started operations in Portugal in 2014 in a freedom of services regime, and in 2018 we opened a branch office in Lisbon, to develop a market-tailored approach to our services and invest in local expertise and know-how by creating a fully dedicated local team. If we look back now to our decision to invest in the country and to develop of a dedicated local team, we would definitely conclude that there was market appetite for our specialized solutions, but also that the market was missing this level of expertise as well, and a tailor-made approach to client needs that would more easily address their specific treasury necessities. At this point, we can safely say that our brand and operational strategy are aligned to pursue the goal of further business growth in Portugal, and our flexibility and efficiency in providing financial services meet companies&rsquo; needs.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Being a small financial institution, we must offer a distinct value proposition to our clients. Operating within a highly regulated environment might be challenging, but there is still room for a niche approach. Ours is based on relationships and trusted advisors, using our size and focused approach in wealth management to our advantage. We target clients that value the fact that we are close to them, we understand them, and we are willing to adjust the product or service to meet their needs. We are a boutique bank with in-depth knowledge of markets, particularly the Portuguese one. We have been investing in creating a bespoke service delivered by talented qualified professionals. We also use technology for incremental improvements to boost our efficiency. In this context, being small may be an advantage: it is easier to make changes when you are agile. With a niche approach, we understand that we are not maximizing the efficiency of the solutions that we offer. This raises issues in terms of finding the right level of response to a client&rsquo;s needs and, at the same time, efficiency. This is why innovation and rethinking the way we do things are heavily on our agenda today.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-05T21:15:11.153Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-04T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[58f615b486b7b00ce8946aa8]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[WavEC Offshore Renewables]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Ana Brito Melo ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/802790af-e926-4a15-9182-69fe180bb739.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Senior Advisor]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ S317 Consulting]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Filipe Vasconcelos]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/cdb748aa-a631-4328-aaab-5a4c6bce1f7d.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ Managing Partner]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Systemic]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[Sofia Santos]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/566fe143-8611-4124-adc0-7fa6b4240127.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[ Founder]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Portugal has abundant energy resources including wind, solar, and wave energy, and there are myriad opportunities for companies to offer their products and services in this growing arena.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Green Economy]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[green-economy-portugal-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>Our main activity is related to R&amp;D projects funded by the European Commission. Our focus continues to be offshore wind energy and wave energy, but also activities related to offshore aquaculture, which is progressing. We currently have one project called BlueForests, which aims to rebuild marine forests in Portugal. It is an innovative project that is funded by EEA grants with a number of Portuguese partners and one Norwegian partner, SINTEF. WavEC is bringing to this project its knowledge of technology, instrumentation, and environmental impact studies. We integrate the knowledge from universities by connecting the academic sector with the business sector, and we are able to deliver specialized services to diversified clients. We now have a strong focus on offshore wind because there will be significant developments in Portugal in the coming years, and we have extensive knowledge in this area to contribute to the growth of this sector. We have been working with other partners in the last years in terms of market studies, site selection, environmental impacts assessment, O&amp;M strategies, instrumentation and data analysis, and technical field work, so we have the knowledge to assist all companies that come to Portugal to develop their offshore energy business.&nbsp;</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>We are a management consulting boutique that specializes in energy, water, and sustainability. We are strong in everything related to the energy transition, namely the water and water services sectors; addressing the needs of mostly the developing world; and sustainability in terms of finance, carbon instruments, and de-carbonization. These are the three main areas that we work in. We have an integrated approach and do not only look at the energy component, but also at industry as a whole and understanding the final impact in terms of the environment in the long term and the returns of our actions and projects. We have an impact on society. We started in 2015 with a strong focus on the international market, and about 70% of our business is outside of Portugal. The Portuguese market, although interesting, is not large enough for us. We have been growing steadily in these last seven years. Emerging economies are saturated with fierce competition; there are much bigger players working in everything in terms of the energy transition, energy efficiency, renewables, water management, water infrastructure, and so on. Despite the competition, we managed to develop a presence in several emerging economies in the last seven years.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Systemic was officially launched in 2013, though I established another company before in 2004, also related to consultancy in sustainability. Systemic really picked up in 2019, growing from only two people at that time to 10 now. Many companies and financial institutions started to realize they needed proper sustainability criteria, ESG policies, and all that, and demand just continued to grow. We also have many requests from city town halls, universities, large and small companies, and more. Regulations have a technical component: being a lawyer is not enough. The regulations are also about environmental data and environmental risk assessments. I have been working on sustainability and sustainable finance for the last 20 years, and Systemic can help with everything related to new regulations and assist its clients that are looking for such specific support in this area. My goal is to have the best team available to help all our clients. We are focusing on those who really want to be part of the company so we can all grow together. Another important aspect is knowledge. Everyone who comes to work with us does at least one executive course a year, so they are able to keep up with the new information coming out.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-05T20:16:16.378Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-04T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c07]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784054]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Portuguese-Spanish Chamber of Commerce and Industry]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Miguel Seco ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/77b18351-6388-4d3f-bab6-c128c65e98ee.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[President]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Italian Chamber of Commerce for Portugal]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Santi Cianci]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/54da5832-5408-49f3-8455-cdd9445fcfde.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ President]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[Hispano-Portuguese Chamber of Commerce (CHP)]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[António Calçada de Sá]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/dec53937-e2a6-4c6d-ad40-fd6babfde888.jpg]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[ Chairman]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<intervieweelist3company><![CDATA[French Portuguese Chamber of Commerce]]></intervieweelist3company>
		<intervieweelist3name><![CDATA[Laurent Marionnet ]]></intervieweelist3name>
		<intervieweelist3photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/62a9ecd6-07ef-4539-abd7-5ee2cd070d4b.jpg]]></intervieweelist3photourl>
		<intervieweelist3position><![CDATA[General Director]]></intervieweelist3position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>To better encourage cooperation, knowledge transfer, and innovations between their countries and Portugal, these chambers of commerce are working on encouraging more cross-border activities.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Chambers]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[chambers-portugal-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery1imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery1caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery1caption>
		<richbody0imagegallery2imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery2caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery2caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
		<sections01><![CDATA[<p>In terms of overall data, Spain accounts for around 30% of Portugal&rsquo;s foreign commerce. Its primary supplier and client is Spain. Aside from this, there are around 100,000 companies that export or trade between the two countries. In the financial sectors, Spanish presence accounts up to 35% of this industry. There are also numerous large, medium, and small law firms specializing in assisting businesses, as well as investments, from both countries. The chamber has seen extremely reduced activity over the last two years because of the pandemic, with only monthly webinars and a small sectorial component; however, we want to get back to business quickly. We also want to do events that give us more publicity. We will have ministers for more focused events at the sector level. We also want to do one of the investment of European funds, one on logistics, and one focused on raw materials. It is also critical to open a chamber in Porto, as there are many Spanish companies installed in the north.</p>]]></sections01>
		<sections11><![CDATA[<p>Italians are mainly concentrated in Cascais and the southern region of Algarve. There is a new community of Italians there, mainly retirees. There is also a community of businesspeople that moved to Portugal a decade or more ago. In the last few years, the Italian community has grown remarkably, with more than 20,000 newcomers encouraged by the fiscal incentives implemented by the Portuguese government. In terms of commercial exchanges between Italy and Portugal, we are talking around EUR4 billion from Italy to Portugal and EUR2.6 billion from Portugal to Italy. Portugal is considered an appealing market for Italian investors and businesses. We are witnessing strong interest and potential in the field of medical devices. Italian technology has a solid reputation internationally, and in Portugal this segment is gaining solid share in terms of imports. There are both opportunities and potential here, and the legal framework for setting up a new business is favorable to investors.</p>]]></sections11>
		<sections21><![CDATA[<p>Today, we have a unique opportunity: for the first time in many years, both Spain and Portugal have a common agenda on the social, political, and economic fronts. I am a strong believer of the concept of the Iberian Peninsula as a whole, as both Portuguese and Spanish people can work together to create a strong and dynamic power on the economic, cultural, and social sides. Both the vision and ambition of the chamber of commerce consist of connecting the dots on the political side, between enterprises in Portugal and Spain, and for activities related to science and academics. We should look at these fields as a single market. In the European context, when debating some of the most critical and important issues, Portugal and Spain have shown that when they join forces, their negotiation power is significantly stronger, and they can easily reach their shared goals. The same concept can be applied at a global level. To make this happen, the chamber brings together all the different players.</p>]]></sections21>
		<sections31><![CDATA[<p>France is among the lead partners of Portugal along with Spain and Germany. We still have a number of ongoing projects with French companies keen to invest in Portugal. Even though French investments tripled last year, we are still in third place behind Spain and Germany. That said, we have some excellent upcoming projects, and it is great that Portugal remains a prospect for consideration in France. Knowledge transfer&mdash;especially in the field of innovation&mdash;will drive growth. French companies export services and know-how. From the pandemic, we can see a true relocation of industry: this phenomenon involves French companies as well. There are many French companies with production facilities in Asia or North Africa returning to Europe. And because of the existing incentives, often Portugal is one of the countries they choose. Portugal is positioning itself not only as an industrial hub but is also attracting a growing volume of skilled human capital.</p>]]></sections31>
		<sections41><![CDATA[]]></sections41>
		<intervieweelist4name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4name>
		<intervieweelist4company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4company>
		<intervieweelist4position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4position>
		<intervieweelist4photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist4photourl>
	</node>
</data>
