<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-25T21:49:42.813Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-24T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0b]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Sony]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Camilo Riveros ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/2178eb4a-9b07-447a-87c6-e8eafd5adbf7.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ LG Electronics]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Jared Kim ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/ac207580-159d-4831-97eb-d6e3177bd973.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Global electronics brands find in Colombia an attractive market with a large appetite for cutting-edge technologies and products.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Camilo Riveros & Jared Kim]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[camilo-riveros-jared-kim]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>What has been the focus of the company in Colombia?</strong></p>
<p>CAMILO RIVEROS Our electronic products are based on quality, service, and affordability. Those are the main focuses of our business in Colombia in particular. Currently, the products that provide the most growth in Colombia are headphones, speakers and cameras, which are closely related to the pandemic and the new era of home offices, online classes, and other online aspects of our lives. Consumer electronics market has been growing consistently in the past years not only due to the pandemic. For example, "D&iacute;a sin IVA" could represent months of sales in just one day. As a premium brand, Sony products are vastly accepted by Colombians because we represent a way to fill their world with emotion through technology.</p>
<p>JARED KIM LG is developing technology not only for specific consumers but for all who want to have access to cutting-edge technologies that make their life easier. The purchasing power of the younger generation is increasing, and they are interested in buying online. LG and its commercial partners are working together to improve e-commerce capabilities to meet their expectations in terms of user experience, availability, product information, fast delivery, and so on. In terms of availability, LG is getting better due to a global negotiation with shipping companies during last quarter 2021 and Colombian consumers are being able to have better access to our products all across the country.</p>
<p><strong>How is Sony important to the Colombian economy?</strong></p>
<p>CR Regarding employment, during the pandemic we were able to maintain our headcount and starting from 2022 we hired more people in our direct and indirect headcounts. In the near future, we will continue to invest in the retail area in Colombia for the medium and long term. Colombia is on the same level as Chile, which is a benchmark for other industries. Colombia is part of the SIA group, which are the Caribbean, Central American, and Andean countries. Colombia is the strongest country within the bloc in terms of sales, headcount, and other metrics.</p>
<p><strong>What is LG Electronics&rsquo; approach to innovation and its strategy to understand consumer needs?</strong></p>
<p>JK LG Colombia has almost 1.000 promoters in the point of sales, they have direct communication with consumers who want to buy our product. This communication helps us understand what Colombian consumers are looking for from LG. Also, we run an important investment on customer surveys, studies and digital channels listening in order to better understand consumer behaviors and needs. All the information collected is shared with headquarters and is taken into consideration in product and services development to improve user experience.</p>
<p><strong>What will be the focus of development for Sony in the mid and long term?</strong></p>
<p>CR Our main objective is to understand Colombian consumers in order to offer what they really need at the right moment. Once that, our strategy for the mid and long term is to offer the &ldquo;best in town&rdquo; affordable programs and the best quality service to our products. In Colombia we will continue to grow and increase our presence in the market: through innovation (affordable programs) and the awareness that the basis of the business is the people.</p>
<p><strong>What is LG focusing on in order to be a brand of the future and to continue innovating?</strong></p>
<p>JK LG is positioned as the number one electronics company in Colombia and wants to continue to be an innovative company, with innovative technology, products, and ways to communicate with consumers. LG will continue to provide innovation to make Colombian consumers&rsquo; life easier, which is part of the purpose of LG Brand. Our headquarters in South Korea is continuously investing for Colombia in order to understand consumers&rsquo; behavior and find their insights to deliver the best of our brand according to their needs. LG has launched cutting-edge technology products and services such as WashTower, Interview, and new OLED TV, successfully, ThinQ based on IOT and AI and &ldquo;LG a tu lado&rdquo; preference service program, which demonstrate our leadership in this market.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-25T21:44:29.524Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-24T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0b]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Falabella.com]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Jaime Ramí­rez ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/3ff07c1a-0c91-47e3-84e2-8c4e24fcbe3a.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ Mercado Libre]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Lina Monsalve ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/a50c0861-2371-4928-b0b2-cb4f48ce46aa.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Understanding the customer is key in e-commerce, and these leading retailers in Colombia have found the right ingredients for success.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Jaime Ramí­rez & Lina Monsalve]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[jaime-ramirez-ceo-falabellacom]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>What key principles are necessary to lead a successful digital transformation?</strong></p>
<p>JAIME RAM&Iacute;REZ One of the key elements of any digital transformation is change management. Change starts with people; changing the way people approach and do things, and this is never an easy thing to do. Falabella started this process a few years ago. The company had always been more of a retailer, but that started to change. The company began a process to become a more digital business. This transformation process greatly accelerated during the pandemic because it forced many companies, not just Falabella, to look at things differently. As mentioned before, one of the key elements of this transformation has been change management. How to help people through the process of changing and evolving the way they work. Falabella recently introduced a new way of working, including a structure of portfolios and agile methodologies throughout the organization. As you know, agile methodologies have been around for many years within technological companies. They help to approach IT development in a different way by having squats, sprints, dating ceremonies and the daily huddle. All of these things help tackle technological development in a different way. Falabella is working on this essential front. Again, I think what's most important is making sure that you help everybody move towards that new way of working that is part of the digital transformation.</p>
<p><strong>How does Mercado Libre intend to adapt and transform commerce in Colombia?</strong></p>
<p>LINA MONSALVE Our intention is to democratize commerce and finance. The idea is to become closer with communities, generating value in transformation. We continue to move forward with development in terms of technology. In 2020 and 2021, we opened two technological centers in Colombia in Bogot&aacute; and Medell&iacute;n, generating more than 1,000 jobs. Looking at 2022, the goal is to continue to strengthen our services centers. We have a website for customer service that serves all of Latin America. Going back to technology, beyond strengthening the local centers, the goal is also to continue developing the tools that we offer to sellers, clients, and stakeholders. In the platform, we are moving closer to reaching the real-life experience in the online world. The other thing beyond technology and services is the logistic chain. We recently made public in various media the inauguration of our new, 52,000-m distribution and storage center. Related to this, Mercado en Vivo is one of our business units within the marketplace. The idea is also to continue strengthening the strategy to bring the online experience closer to clients. We support SMEs and entrepreneurs, and some 80% of the shipments that leave our centers to be distributed are delivered in less than two days, while 50% of shipments are delivered in less than a day.</p>
<p><strong>What do you intend to accomplish over the coming years?</strong></p>
<p>JR Our goal is to become the largest online retailer in the region. Right now, Falabella is among the leading players in this space, and a leader in Chile, Peru and Colombia. Our primary strength lies in having a hybrid model, that is, one present in both the digital and physical space. Falabella is a strong retailer with years of experience in this space. We know that retail is about planning and knowing what to buy and when to buy it. This is a valuable skill to have. Another strength is Falabella&rsquo;s comprehensive ecosystem. It has a solid financial arm through Banco Falabella, which allows it to provide credits to both sellers and buyers on the platform. The company also has a strong loyalty program called CMR Puntos, which is among the leading loyalty programs in the region. This program brings a strong value proposition to the customer. Both sellers and buyers are becoming accustomed to receiving something in exchange for their loyalty. Falabella works to channel all of these strengths into becoming the region&rsquo;s leading retailer for both the physical and the digital domains.</p>
<p>LM Over the last year, the company grew 26%. Maintaining our leadership position is linked to three areas. Technology is one of the pillars of Mercado Libre, and we focus on continuing to innovate and be one step ahead of our competitors. The other is to strengthen everything in the ecosystem of entrepreneurs, which is important not only to our social impact, but is also a win-win relationship, because we are strengthening our value proposal and product range. The third is logistics, which is undoubtedly an important factor. These three areas have an effect on improving our service, on reaching a positive cycle where we generate better experiences, as well as on our sellers and contractors that want to continue buying from us to sell our products.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-25T21:28:36.705Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-24T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0b]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Accenture]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Marí­a Fernanda Suárez]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/d0607377-2f39-428c-aa1f-b68697241d2f.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[ General Manager]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Tata Consultancy Services (TCS)]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Alfredo González ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/31a1ea31-2519-49d4-88dc-96e9d49362fa.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>These companies use their know-how and expertise to help clients transform their businesses and accelerate their digital transformations.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Marí­a Fernanda Suárez & Alfredo González]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[alfredo-gonzalez-country-manager-tata-consultancy-services-tcs]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>How do you help your clients deliver value?</strong></p>
<p>MARIA FERNANDA SU&Aacute;REZ The added value we give our clients is supporting them in the acceleration of their transformations, compressing them over time. The challenges our clients face is that of timely digitalization. Accenture is the best partner to achieve this. We offer change management and have prepared human talent and can help our clients to quickly adapt to these changes, considering given our global pedigree in these areas. We can accelerate change in several ways: from advisory services to managing those departments undergoing transformation, and operating part of the company for the client.</p>
<p>ALFREDO GONZ&Aacute;LEZ TCS is part of a large corporation, Tata Group, and is dedicated to technology. Digital transformation is in our DNA. One of our key points is education and practical use. If we transform a bank, we do not just give them a nice app or website; it is important to change the way it operates. We understand that transformation is a holistic process. Our main clients have a business vision, but we are looking for the technology vision connected to the business vision. This combined can allow for a business to see mid-to-long-term plans.</p>
<p><strong>What are the main needs of your clients?</strong></p>
<p>MFS We have four action lines for our clients. The first is the consulting strategy based on data analytics. The second line is technology. Here, we support our clients in the implementation of solutions such as SAP. We advise and we support them through the entire process of migrating information to the cloud. Another increasingly important aspect nowadays is cybersecurity. Here, we help them by setting the cybersecurity strategy, supporting its implementation, and, if needed, overseeing the cybersecurity operation. The fourth line is intelligent operations; a line that has seen the greatest growth. We operate specialized services for our clients, such as personalized marketing strategies, finance and accounting, purchase chains, and human talent services.</p>
<p>AG Every company is currently looking for efficiency and the only way to do so is by transformation or by generating an analytic information value that improves process and can provide a better impact on the final client. This is our potential. We are a leading technology company for the businesses of our clients. When we talk to a client, we look at how they operate, because each one operates differently. The culture of each client is distinct. Our company&rsquo;s first intention is to understand this part of our client. This encapsulates our vision. We have technology in our DNA, and we apply it with a deep understanding of the businesses. It is difficult to talk about technology without understanding a business because there is a whole wealth of technologies that can be used.</p>
<p><strong>How does the company contribute to Colombia&rsquo;s development?</strong></p>
<p>MFS We believe in long-term relationships with our clients. By having a value offer featuring end-to-end solutions, we provide comprehensive support for our client in their commercial processes. Today, we are aiming at notable growth in this market. When you analyze our footprint in Brazil, Argentina, Chile or Mexico, the other Latin American countries where we operate, relative to each country&rsquo;s economy, it is much larger than in Colombia. And so here Accenture has a major growth opportunity, which we want to capitalize on in the years to come, by providing all the global services Accenture has to our Colombian clients.</p>
<p><strong>How does the company&rsquo;s global experience benefit clients?</strong></p>
<p>AG We have nearly 3,000 employees in Colombia but not all of them are located here. If we look further, we have the entire American or Asian market at our disposal. I have over 590,000 associates to whom I can reach out for experience or outside information. TCS can be considered a bridge between the Colombian industry and international business practices. Every day, clients ask us about the best systems. For example, if a client wants to know about the best payment system, we can recommend from our system a solid payment method technology in Germany.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-24T14:58:47.345Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0a]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Evonik]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Fabián Bravo ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/9dd7511f-3835-4a95-9402-45b7c348b33c.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[General Manager Colombia]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Cremer Oleo Latin America ]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Roberto Echevarrí­a]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/3625782a-8acd-403c-a230-8cc7c733cb5d.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ Managing Director]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>More than just producing in Colombia, these multinational companies are investing in human talent, helping the country improve its value chain and export to all over the world.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Fabián Bravo & Roberto Echevarrí­a]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[fabian-bravo-general-manager-colombia-evonik]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>Can you provide an introduction to the company?</strong></p>
<p>FABI&Aacute;N BRAVO Evonik is one of the biggest chemical industries in the world. We produce specialty chemicals, and, in the case of Latin America, we focus on the industrial area. We have 12 business lines and therefore supply extremely different industries like animal nutrition, paints and coatings, pharma and personal care, to name a few. We truly cover most industries. We have made some strategic decisions in terms of Colombia. We have established a long-term plan to manage countries in Central America, the Caribbean, and the Andean region through the Colombian platform. Previously, we were working via distributors and different sales channels. Later, in July 2021, we started our own operations. The group is focusing on the growth of this region. We have ambitious plans to get closer to local producers. Basically, we want to grow together with our customers. We are commercial partners, and we have a strong position in most of these industries. We also have specialized products. In most cases, we are developing the specific uses of our products together with our partners.</p>
<p><strong>What are the company&rsquo;s projections for Colombia and what units are you betting on?</strong></p>
<p>ROBERTO ECHEVARR&Iacute;A We are looking into the biofuels sector. We are a worldwide player in bioethanol and biodiesel, so renewable energy is of notable interest. In bioethanol, we are planning to be pioneers in exporting this raw material from Colombia to the rest of the world, predominantly Europe. With the biodiesel industry, we are working together and assisting companies to commercialize not the biodiesel itself, since it stays in Colombia for the local market, but the derivatives and byproducts like glycerin. We started exporting this immediately and commercializing it worldwide, too. We are looking into the sector of green chemistry, or more specifically, the palm oil sector in Colombia. The country is likely the fourth largest producer of palm oil in the world. Malaysia and Indonesia, the biggest producers of palm oil in the world, have gone all the way downstream with palm oil ending in green chemical specialties for example, which are much more value-added products. Colombia stops midway, so there is noteworthy potential to continue going downstream in the palm oil sector and producing the green chemicals. Industries are working to move away from petrochemicals and crude oil into biochemicals, organics, or green chemistry. We see huge potential there for Colombia, too, in terms of industrial development.</p>
<p><strong>What campaigns is Evonik leading to increase the sustainability and resource efficiency of the industry in Colombia?</strong></p>
<p>FB Evonik is heavily committed to sustainability, and the whole organization has to be aligned in terms of having a chance to develop projects, whereby most of our activities will result in many improvements for humankind. Our region is diverse; the biodiversity here is much greater than in other regions, and this is a key factor for the future. We have identified companies that also have similar philosophies. We share a common philosophical fit with all of them. The future must be truly sustainable. We develop more sustainable products and solutions in every field that we are involved. Sustainability is part of our DNA and you can see it in our innovative products and in our state-of-the-art plants, in terms of technology and safety.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>What impact does Cremer have on Colombia in terms of capital investment and employment generation?</strong></p>
<p>RE Cremer will create employment and attract foreign investment. We will also add industrial value, making Colombia a more value-added destination in terms of industrial processing and the downstream chain, which involve the raw materials that we cover worldwide. Also, we will assist Colombia&rsquo;s export drive, since we are active in trading and industrial activities. Cremer Group has historically been a producer of compound feed for animals, especially in Germany where we operate 14 plants, being the largest private manufacturer in the country. That means we feeding animals, the main protein source for humans. Yet, the trend around the world is for more people going vegetarian or vegan, and consuming protein from vegetables. Therefore, one investment focus of our group is vegetable protein facilities where we manufacture the pre-ingredient that is being used in the final production of vegan meat or burgers, namely vegetable proteins. We have been investing and participating in companies in Canada, the US, Europe, and Asia. In Colombia, we will also be evaluating the opportunities in this area.</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-24T14:19:15.747Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0a]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Nestlé ]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Antonio Núñez ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/88cf5ebe-542f-48d6-ace7-a8b78a5307a0.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO Colombia]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Grupo Bimbo Colombia]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Francisco Fuentes ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/7eb158bb-3c07-41a1-95d9-6fa88c58f926.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[General Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Global food companies are not only focusing on growing their businesses in Colombia, but also on innovating with new products and through promoting healthier eating habits.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Antonio Núñez & Francisco Fuentes]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[antonio-nunez-ceo-colombia-nestle]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>What is your company's impact on the country?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>ANTONIO N&uacute;&ntilde;ez Nestl&eacute; is a brand with a remarkably important penetration in Colombia. We started local operations 78 years ago, in 1944, and have remained consistent to the essence of the Nestl&eacute; brand. Nestl&eacute; worldwide is a leading company in nutrition, health, wellness, food, and our entire history in Colombia is related precisely with that mission. This is to deliver to Colombian consumers products of the highest nutritional level and quality, and without forgetting the sensory, and organoleptic quality, while being preferred for our flavor and nutritional proposal. The best way to demonstrate the attachment the Colombian consumer has with Nestl&eacute; is to refer to our brands such as Milo, Maggi, and Nescafe, which are uppermost in the mind of Colombian consumers. For me, one of the fundamental elements we are proud of is our mission of delivering nutrition, health, and well-being, and of doing so with a vision of shared value.</p>
<p>FRANCISCO FUENTES We have a clear culture and mission: delicious and nutritious foods in every person&rsquo;s hands. In Colombia, and as Bimbo Group in general, one key factor is innovation. We are constantly looking to update our portfolio, creating new proposals, and launching new products in order to ensure the wellbeing of our consumers and their satisfaction. We have an extremely high goal, so our foods need to be delicious and nutritious. In the last 25 years in Colombia, we have also become a model for innovation. From here, we have developed important brands that have eventually gone global, such as Vital and Artesano. We are an innovation hub regarding product creation, which is extremely important. We have other products as well, such as 100% Natural Bimbo Bread and 100% Whole Bimbo Bread. We also have a B2C line of frozen products, Bimbo Bread for Home, which was launched during the pandemic. We recently launched another brand, Pa&rsquo; Mi Gente (For my people), which focuses on local flavors and products to appeal to the Colombian palate, which we are proud of. At a global level, we have 100 brands with over 13,000 products and 203 production plants in 33 countries, of which seven are in Colombia.</p>
<p><strong>What is your commitment to social responsibility?</strong></p>
<p>AN For the first time, Nestl&eacute; published its Creation of Shared Value and Social Responsibility Report that shows the impact that Nestl&eacute; Colombia has in areas of shared value creation. We have three major commitments: to people, society, and the planet. We have a role creating shared value with our people and work to accelerate inclusion, diversity, and gender balance. Nestl&eacute; is also proud of its commitment to leadership in human rights. We currently have a spectacular project that we call Community and Respect for Life that we have been developing for three years in the communities of Bugalagrande, Andalucia, and Tulua. Our main factory is located in Bugalagrande in Valle del Cauca. What we are looking for is cooperation with the municipalities, the government of Valle del Cauca, the Ministry of Justice, and a wide range of stakeholders where the UN has also been present for some time, as well as the Ideas for Peace Foundation. We are looking to generate a safer community, and contributed to the construction of an Observatory for the analysis of violence. We want to have a positive impact on the livelihood of communities.</p>
<p>FF We seek to bring nutritious and delicious foods to everyone. Our mission &ldquo;Feeding a better world&rdquo; can be segmented into three main pillars: initiatives for you, initiatives for life, and initiatives for the environment. In the first pillar, we focus on the consumer. We have seven sales and research centers in different countries, Colombia is an important development hub to innovate and update our portfolio, moving forward with the health and wellness trends that our consumers look for. At this center, we are constantly looking to develop brands and healthy categories that can be the basis for a balanced diet. We are also aware of the need to improve on existing lines in our portfolio as well and adapting them to our consumers&rsquo; needs as well as promoting healthy lifestyles. The second pillar, &ldquo;For Life,&rdquo; is focused on having a positive impact on communities. In Colombia, we have a program called Good Neighbor with the communities around our research centers and our plants whereby we work together with them to renovate parks, public schools, and libraries. Through the last pillar, &ldquo;For Environment,&rdquo; we make a commitment to respect and take care of the environment, knowing we have the responsibility of helping build a better world for future generations.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-23T13:24:56.889Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-22T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5538d67986b7b0108818c458]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[FEEL Consulting]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Nestor Neira ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/80986a9a-75a8-4458-89e3-341a2370173b.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[General Manager]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[OGE Legal Services]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Hemberth Suárez]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/ffbc864b-6297-4887-bd65-01c0bfc0605f.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[ Managing Partner]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>These experts not only focus on one particular area, but also work closely with their clients to manage their interests and ensure their success.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Nestor Neira & Hemberth Suárez]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[hemberth-suarez-managing-partner-oge-legal-services]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>What services do you provide the industry?</strong></p>
<p>NESTOR NEIRA We focus on drilling and drilling operations; specializing in drilling fluids and waste management. We also do visual conceptual projects for various operators, assisting them with planning, insights, and advisory. Data is crucial within consulting in strengthening decision-making capacity and supporting business intelligence. Data has become key, and companies are focused on real information to make decisions. Fell Consulting works closely with drilling companies. The people working here have been involved with operations on both sides, namely as operator and service provider. This allows for effective dialog with managers and drilling engineers, or the people we work for regarding the best choice regarding the technical consideration.&nbsp;</p>
<p>HEMBERTH SU&Aacute;REZ OGE Legal Services was founded in 2014 and is positioned among the main consultancies related to electric power and natural gas. This segment is home to large firms. As a developing law firm, we stand out in terms of assisting with private and commercial initiatives and realizing the vision of the investor in Colombia. In addition, we have participated from project acquisition to purchasing within companies and have also collaborated in energy sector commercialization. Our clients are private investors who want to invest in Colombia in renewable energies, energy storage, power generation, and, above all, in businesses associated with natural gas, both domestic and imported.</p>
<p><strong>How does Feel Consulting contribute to broader national development and engineering know-how?</strong></p>
<p>NN The work that Feel Consulting has done in terms of land surveying and operation monitoring is useful to newcomers. Instead of starting from scratch, they have a set of data they can lean on for key insights. This helps them avoid pitfalls and allows them to conduct more detailed planning. Essentially, we allow companies to tap into the experience we have amassed. Our database is useful for managers, operators, and field engineers. From the data we calculate Key Performance Indicators such as cost per foot, and barrels per foot. With that information, anybody with an analytical capability is able to determine the optimum strategy for a forthcoming operation, and set the best plans for water catch and disposal, and for budget planning, and so forth. Tech-oriented companies contribute to the competitiveness of industry through the technology spillover with partners, and also by raising standards of human capital and industry protocols.</p>
<p><strong>How do you evaluate the support given by government to industry?</strong></p>
<p>HS The support has been generally positive. Today, investors can find a clear legal and regulatory framework in Colombia. When they seek financial leverage, they find a need at an international level, and the aim is to show them that there is a regulation for this investment fund. This year, two laws that promote energy transition were issued: Laws 20/99 and 21/85. Moreover, these laws have become the basis for the investor to obtain resources and develop projects here. There are fiscal policies to facilitate the arrival of these new energies. In terms of taxation, there are four benefits: VAT exclusion, tariff exemption, accelerated depreciation, and income tax deduction. The opportunity to make use of these benefits was extended until 2025, both for energy efficiency and renewable energy.</p>
<p><strong>How does being a Colombian company set FEEL apart from foreign consultants?</strong></p>
<p>NN Each region in Colombia has different geological attributes. Experience and information are key to stability, and problem-free project management. Each part of Colombia has different conditions, formations, different and sedimentary conditions. And so when operators form alliances with on-the-ground consultants they achieve efficiencies that they would otherwise miss out on.</p>
<p><strong>What are the firm&rsquo;s plans to expand its services to become an engineering and economic advisor?</strong></p>
<p>HS Within our services, we do not just want to limit ourselves to the legal and regulatory scene, but also extend ourselves to other transversal services, such as environmental licensing issues and negotiations to acquire project-related assets. We do not limit ourselves to legal services, but are also integral to the management of our clients&rsquo; interests. Essentially, we must remain identified as the firm that provides consultancies in the energy sector and in the short term identify ourselves as lawyers specialized in energy resources in Colombia and Latin America.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T20:19:47.619Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c08]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Daviplata]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Margarita Henao ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/f18af455-b877-4039-8820-bb3fa007bbd6.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ Nequi]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Andrés Vásquez ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/69000ec2-8661-4678-a2c1-d99efb7ba5da.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Business Director]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Established with the premise of increasing financial inclusion in the country, digital banks have played a crucial role in providing more Colombians with access to financial services.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Margarita Henao & Andrés Vásquez]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[andres-vasquez-business-director-nequi]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>What impact has the company had in Colombia?</strong></p>
<p>MARGARITA HENAO Today, it has more than 14 million customers and a history of more than a decade. DaviPlata has played an important role in the financial inclusion of Colombia; at this point 42% of the adult population of Colombia has DaviPlata, moving their money or making payments and many more functionalities, all through a cell phone and without the need to open a bank account. We allow all our clients to access different payment methods without requiring experience or additional paperwork. Our customers can open a prepaid Virtual Card in a matter of seconds to shop online anywhere in the world, with the support of the Mastercard franchise; the best thing is that the card is completely free. Likewise, we developed the ecosystem of physical payments, we have reached more than 1.2 million stores and businesses in the country, allowing them to receive payments through QR codes and connecting them with the millions of users who have DaviPlata. Clients can access different products and services such as a broad portfolio of microinsurance as well as nanocredits. DaviPlata bets on the construction of ecosystems, seeking to connect with strategic allies such as the Rappi superApp with RappiPay and we connect to the first smart city where DaviPlata has achieved a strategic alliance with the Medell&iacute;n Metro so metro users can also enjoy city services in a single application, thanks to the implementation of the Civic SuperApp, facilitating the mobility of citizens and their monetary transactions.</p>
<p>ANDR&Eacute;S V&Aacute;SQUEZ After registering increased growth during the pandemic, reaching 10 million users, we kept seeing a constant number of new monthly additions even after its effects had faded. In fact, Nequi is becoming the standard for transactions for all people, including the informal market of the street vendors in remote areas. Growth has had an impact by changing the way people interacted with banking. We see a higher impact in informal businesses, through financial inclusion in the informal areas. If you go to any beach or island in Colombia, you see the street and beach vendors receiving payments through Nequi. QR code payment has seen exponential growth over the past year, having become the most used payment method. We have seen a change in terms of how people handle their money, their savings. Most transactions made are those of people that work in the informal economy, but this means we have reached them through financial inclusivity. This allows us to create more assertive credit models. When we spoke in 2021, we had not yet launched our new product, but now through it we have been able to reach many more people with credit and microcredit offers and possibilities, which enable them to boost their informal businesses or consumer loans. The community and user cluster we have gained has crystallized our end objective, aimed at providing inclusivity not only through savings and transaction, but also through loans.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>How do you see the future in terms of international expansion?</strong></p>
<p>MH DaviPlata is already found at a regional level, as is the case in El Salvador, but we always seek to be in more countries. In Colombia, we have an important position, and we are working to make the platform scalable to enter with force in other countries. For example, Israel is an example of innovation, where everything it creates is aimed at expanding abroad, and it also has the largest number of patents in global terms. It is important to learn from cases like Israel creating scalable products, and technology will allow us to cross international borders</p>
<p><strong>How are you making the most of your customer base to capitalizes on loan opportunities?</strong></p>
<p>AV We started with a small loan called the Lifesaver credit line, which corresponds to loans of between COP100,000 and COP500,000 to be paid within a month, designed to be used in case of emergencies. We had been working for around two years with that product. In October 2021, we started with a credit line of between COP500,000 and COP5 million, a product that enables users to defer payments to up to 24 months. Just in 2021 more than 114,000 people were able to access a loan. With this new product, we have the possibility of reaching 400,000 people in 2022 with loans. The most important data Nequi has after reaching 10 million users and increasing its activity dramatically, is the potential it has to reach people that we unable to access a loan in the past and granting them credit lines.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T18:56:34.039Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[58f615b486b7b00ce8946aa8]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Enercon]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Farid Mohamadi ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/c425a753-f2fb-4fbb-82b3-06778c0b0e47.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Country Manager]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[ABO Wind Renovables Colombia]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Christian Llull ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/1762d225-dcdd-48b8-b76c-9d2676bc0564.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[General Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Many actors in Colombia, including the government, are working on moving unconventional renewable energy forward, and many are hopeful the regulation will evolve to accelerate the development of the industry.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Farid Mohamadi & Christian Llull]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[farid-mohamadi-country-manager-enercon]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>How can a Colombian developer benefit from partnering with Enercon?</strong></p>
<p>FARID MOHAMADI Enercon could bring value in terms of technical know-how and support based on its experience in end-to-end processes when it comes to realizing wind energy projects. This starts from the planning up to the operation, including the financing and the monitoring during construction. This is crucial, especially in markets where there are not many installations yet. It is important to have companies that are experienced, can bring proven technology to the country, and share their expertise not only in terms of structuring the project, but also innovation for better efficiency, making the project competitive enough to win auctions, and so on. Enercon wants to go beyond being a vendor and become a consultant to developers, even though its focus is to manufacture and supply turbines. We have seen a need from developers, even from the large utilities in Colombia, for advice to share experiences and knowledge.</p>
<p><strong>What is ABO Wind&rsquo;s strategy in the country?</strong></p>
<p>CHRISTIAN LLULL ABO Wind was established in Germany and has been working with renewable energies for 25 years. We entered the Colombian market three years ago to contribute with our track record and experience in an emerging market. In 2017, the market was fairly new, and we intended to become a major player in the renewable energy sector in Colombia. Currently, we are focusing on the photovoltaic market. It makes sense to diversify Colombia&rsquo;s energy matrix currently based on hydropower to anticipate climate change and ensure a reliable electricity supply. Colombia has plenty of natural resources, both solar irradiation as well as wind, and it makes sense to make use of them. We have a long-term approach to the market, and we are currently developing a pipeline of projects with a total capacity of 90MW in various sizes and locations. Our expertise and activities cover the whole value chain of the renewable projects.</p>
<p><strong>What does Enercon focus on to deliver value to clients?</strong></p>
<p>FM Enercon focuses on being a reliable company on project execution. It is not enough to execute flawless projects without issues; you also have to be competitive by bringing to the market new products that are effective at the best price. For us, it is important that clients have a product that lasts over time. We also go beyond, because we believe we have a responsibility to society, and therefore we carefully choose our products to ensure they are sustainable. We look at our carbon footprints, and we also care for the entire lifecycle of the project. We have been in Colombia for four years now, and in that time, we have been spending resources and time to perfectly understand the market in terms of the technical and environmental aspects of the infrastructure. There are many challenges, and in order to overcome them, you have to work much more closely with your partner, be they a provider or customer, if you want to realize a project. We are open to partnering with all companies within the chain, though there may be smaller developers or IPPs that might find more value in partnering with us. Having said that, we have agreements with utilities as well.</p>
<p><strong>How is ABO Wind assisting Colombia in becoming a pioneer in green energy on a regional level?</strong></p>
<p>CL We have been through the development, financing, construction and operation of projects in various markets, and that is the experience ABO Wind wants to bring to the country. Colombia is on target to become a leader in the region. It is working on diversifying the matrix. That should be the main motivation and driver: moving from a conventional renewable base to the unconventional. It is a synergy, not a competition. The technology is available, and Colombia has to figure out the best balance between all the available technologies. In our experience, the government has identified the main barriers and is working on them. It will take more time to outline a proper regulatory framework to make sure projects are completed. Wind power is more or less concentrated in La Guajira because the region has the highest wind speeds; however, it is a fairly challenging area for different reasons. You have to apply the right technology in the right place. There are areas with high irrigation that are better suited for PV technology. Wind energy requires structures that are hard to transport to certain parts of Colombia, so that type of production will likely stay in a few areas of the country.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-22T18:38:03.563Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-21T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[58f615b486b7b00ce8946aa8]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ Allcot]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Alexis Leroy ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/70fced83-3f16-43cf-b55e-363a725bbca4.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Aval Ambiental]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Diana Marcela Zapata ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/d79c05b0-3762-48e0-99d5-f935c550d925.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[General Manager]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>These consultants help companies understand the benefits of investing in sustainability to not only improve their operations, but also boost their relations with communities and their own customers.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Alexis Leroy & Diana Marcela Zapata]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[alexis-leroy-ceo-allcot]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>What makes the company a strategic partner in the sustainability field for companies?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>ALEXIS LEROY Allcot has been active in the carbon industry since 2009, which makes us veterans in the sustainability space. We have survived even in difficult years. We are not just a consulting company but a project developer and an agent of change. We not only help corporations reach their net-zero goals, but also work with governments to help define legislation, determine which markets are suitable to drive investment while promoting public-private sector cooperative approach. We also develop tools to implement Article 6 pilot projects. Allcot has been involved in all the COPs since Lima and with the governments in our areas of influence. Our involvement is such that I recently had the honor of being appointed co-chair of the International Emission Trading Association (IETA) working group for Latin America and the Caribbean.</p>
<p>DIANA MARCELA ZAPATA We have three main strategic business units: strategic environmental consulting, environmental impact studies, and tax benefits. Aval Ambiental is the best ally for companies, mainly those with major environmental challenges. Our work begins at the planning stages, as it is extremely important for companies to think about the environmental aspects in the early stages of a project, such that it becomes part of their business. We work with them during that process, starting with the planning, looking over their environmental policies, and adapting them to each project, in order to follow those aspects in every stage of the project; we advise companies on how to take into account the environmental legislation, international aspects, and Colombia&rsquo;s policies to ensure they are incorporated into their processes. That is how we ensure companies have long-term viability, not only for environmental reasons, such as acquiring a license, but also to have proper land incorporation and zone adaptation for their own profit and that of the communities.</p>
<p><strong>Why is Allcot the best candidate to help companies address their sustainability objectives?</strong></p>
<p>AL We came to Colombia in 2011, and our commitment to the country is historic. My first project was with a sugar mill in the Cali area, which was impactful because it was more than just about sugar production; there was a social ecosystem around the plants. We learned to create high-quality projects that are transparent and can ensure there will be added value for the customer that wants to offset their carbon footprints. We are currently suggesting building solutions around the value of our client. Second is our understanding of the Paris Agreement&rsquo;s financial new rule. We also monitor, verify, and report on projects from not only a greenhouse gas point of view, but also the Sustainable Development Goals in line with the 2030 Agenda. We have developed a strong bond with the country. The largest source of greenhouse gas emissions in Colombia is deforestation, and we are working on solutions that helps the communities reverse the damages. The first fruits of this model will be delivered to the community in 1Q2022 and will allow funding of productive projects for the communities involved in the projects. The third reason is that there is an incredible amount of wealth in Colombia, but the financial system is still backward, and there is room for significant improvement. We are now talking to financial institutions to let them understand that if they do not measure climate and environmental exposure from their activities, they face great risks where today, there are unique opportunities. They are finally being receptive.</p>
<p><strong>What characteristics make Aval Ambiental an expert consulting firm?</strong></p>
<p>DMZ Mainly, the knowledge; Aval Ambiental has a team of senior professionals who are experts in environmental and social matters. Many of them have held government positions that provided them with a national perspective and a sensibility of the community&rsquo;s needs.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-07T23:49:52.526Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-07T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0d]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[JLL Portugal]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Pedro Lancastre]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/d07f0e69-8997-4e5e-83f3-d813503a273c.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Engel & Völkers Spain, Portugal, and Andorra]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Juan-Galo Macií ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/35e66175-a237-4665-83f3-723799cbbcd6.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>With such a diverse group of investors in the local real estate sector, these companies help interested parties navigate the different opportunities offered in the country.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Pedro Lancastre and Juan-Galo Macií ]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[pedro-lancastre-jll-portugal-juan-galo-macia-engel-volkers-spain-portugal-andorra-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>Can you elaborate on the company&rsquo;s development in the last few years? </strong></p>
<p><strong>PEDRO LANCASTRE </strong>We had a great 2021; in terms of revenue, it was our best year ever. Despite the pandemic and the uncertainty, we are going through, our gross revenue was 5% above 2019. We are continuing to grow, and it has been 25 years of great successes. Today, we have 363 people working in 360 degrees in the real estate industry, from commercial real estate to residential. We started by acquiring a small company that was 100% dedicated to retail, and we grew naturally, going from retail to office to the industrial sector. We are a one-stop shop within the industry. We cover all areas of real estate, including designing interiors from retail and offices to malls, hotels and cinemas. Over the years, we have successfully expanded our operations to the hospitality and hotel industry as well. We have a dedicated team for hotels, not only in Portugal but also around the world, and we have participated in transactions to help operators find spaces or redefine, reshape, or reconstruct their hotels.</p>
<p><strong>JUAN-GALO MACI&Agrave;</strong> For over 40 years now, Engel &amp; V&ouml;lkers has specialized in the brokerage of premium residential property, commercial real estate, yachts, and aircraft. As a leading global service company, we currently operate in over 900 locations in more than 30 countries spanning five continents. Currently we have around 16,000 people operating under the Engel &amp; V&ouml;lkers brand worldwide, and one of our expansion goals is to reach 20,000 in the next few years. Our proven business model, which consists of the well-established pillars of the market center concept and the franchise business, provides the optimal leverage to further expand our business. 2021 was a historic year, as the company exceeded EUR1,000 million in group fee income. We were able to improve and overcome barriers. With regard to Portugal, we had the highest turnover in history, with more than EUR168 million in brokerage volume of premium properties. Engel &amp; V&ouml;lkers firmly believes in the potential of the Portuguese market and has been investing significantly in the training of consultants, technological development, and the growth of the franchise network in the premium segment, now having national coverage.</p>
<p><strong>How do you shape your competitive advantages?</strong></p>
<p><strong>PL</strong> We know what developers are looking for, and we help them buy the projects and define the product. We know what market to approach. We know where demand comes from and what the market is seeking. This is a great competitive advantage. We are part of a multinational company that is present in more than 80 countries. We can predict trends and anticipate what the world is bringing to a small country such as Portugal. We are a commercial real estate company, though we are also present in the residential space, and today there are no investors looking at commercial spaces that does not also want to invest in residential.</p>
<p><strong>J-GM</strong> Engel &amp; V&ouml;lkers has been in the market for more than 40 years and has built a strong brand and global network which is one of the main competitive advantages we have. This allows us to take advantage of the synergies within the company to be able to provide the best service to our most demanding customers and maintain our high quality standards that position us as a brand of recognized prestige. Now with the arrival of the Permira fund, and its ambitious growth objectives, we are going to take an even greater technological leap in order to continue to always be one step ahead.</p>
<p><strong>What specific segment drives the growth of the company? </strong></p>
<p><strong>PL</strong> In general, all segments are growing equally. All sectors in the occupancy, investment, residential grew significantly in the last five years. In our case, in 2021 residential grew more. Residential has been constantly growing for the past four to five years, and in 2022 we still see great potential to continue to grow further here. We opened shops in 2021 in several areas, including Cascais, Algarve, and Porto. Our geographical expansion is aligned with the business volume of the company.</p>
<p><strong>What consolidation and expansion plans does the company have? </strong></p>
<p><strong>J-GM</strong> Engel &amp; V&ouml;lkers is strongly positioned around the globe to continue its course of expansion in 2022: The Group&rsquo;s proven business model, which consists of the well-established pillars of the Market Center concept and the franchise business, will be expanded further. The growing number of experts working around the world under the Engel &amp; V&ouml;lkers brand is reflective of the attractiveness of the company. In 2021, more than 90 new shops opened worldwide.</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-07T11:39:43.161Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-06T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0a]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Lusospace]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Ivo Vieira]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/c98de031-e026-494f-a456-f535d004cdf4.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Deimos Engenharia S.A.]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Nuno Avila]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/919e4074-3b9b-42e5-b47c-fa0d6187a2a5.png]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>The aerospace sector in Portugal has become extremely competitive, with companies racing to develop new innovative technologies and projects that will require not only creativity and talent but also patience.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Ivo Vieira and Nuno Avila]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[ivo-vieira-lusospace-nuno-avila-deimos-engenharia-sa-portugal-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>Can you elaborate more on the company? </strong></p>
<p><strong>IVO VIEIRA</strong> LusoSpace has been working in the space sector since 2002 and celebrates its 20th anniversary in 2022. We have been working mainly in hardware and developing products and systems for the space sector. The main products are for navigation, some are for optical communication, and we have also been developing augmented reality technology to improve the productivity of our systems. At present, we are working to deploy a satellite constellation. We operate in a highly niche segment: one of our products, for example, is the magnetometer, which no other company in Portugal sells. The optical communications terminal that we developed is set to launch in 2023 and will enable communication between Leo satellites and ground stations. Then, there are the augmented reality systems that we have been developing to improve human productivity. This has great significance for the industry itself in that we can assemble and test a satellite much faster and more reliably. The third project we are particularly proud of is the laser for Laser Interfermoter Space Antenna (LISA): LISA will be the largest manmade structure of its kind ever made&mdash;a giant laser observatory in space to probe the dark side of the universe.</p>
<p><strong>NUNO AVILA</strong> Today, with over 500 professionals in Spain, Portugal, the UK, Romania, and Italy, Deimos is one the most prominent space companies in Europe, covering all aspects from space engineering, satellite production (Deimos 1, Deimos2, Neptuno) and operation, but also a business critical information systems provider for transportation, energy production and automation. What had started as a purely engineering company doing studies in engineering for third parties 20 years ago has quickly evolved into a company that can cover the entire value chain. The company achieved a turnover of about EUR50 million in 2021. In Portugal, Deimos Engenharia&rsquo;s core business is space. We have been one of the most successful suppliers of the European Space Agency (ESA) since Portugal joined ESA in 2000. Actually, Deimos is part of the history of the Space sector in Portugal. Back in 2000, there was barely any company working in space&mdash;it was a totally new sector. In 20 years, we proudly grew in Portugal a strong industrial capacity up to the level of space system integration, developed unique technologies, nurtured a huge network of science and technology partners and co-founded Portuguese aerospace and defense associations (AED and former ProEspa&ccedil;o).</p>
<p><strong>What is the long-term vision of the company? </strong></p>
<p><strong>IV</strong> We will continue to establish partnerships with local and international institutions. We also partner with universities for specific tasks for projects, as well as for PhDs or other academic work. As an example, we have developed some augmented reality hardware that will replace your smartphones in the future, and we have been working with universities that have state-of-the-art microtechnology that can be of benefit in hardware development. We have three main ambitions: to be a satellite integrator, a leader in optical and quantum communications, to spin off the augmented reality technology to other sectors beyond space. 2022 looks promising, as we are bidding with other companies for our part of Portugal&rsquo;s Recovery Plan. If we are successful in this, we will be able to develop and deploy a constellation of satellites.</p>
<p><strong>What are the main challenges characterizing the industry you are working in? </strong></p>
<p><strong>NA</strong> This is really a niche market where having an extremely skilled and stable team is a key asset. And that makes attracting and retaining top human capital the main challenge of Deimos. The market now is booming, people are needed, and Deimos is on the front line to welcome the best professional in space, but also in ICT and software. Our team in Lisbon is now 75 people. Overall, what we are seeing globally is a lack of people educated in STEM subjects in order to keep up with the requirements and pace of technology businesses worldwide. There&rsquo;s a vibrant tech environment in Portugal right now, which is backed by a strong institutional vision and governmental push in making Portugal a reference in technology services, space being one of them.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-07T11:34:24.439Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-06T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c0a]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Primedrinks]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[João Morão]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/aea865cb-29e8-4380-b879-c55109b1f730.png]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Director]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Viborel]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[João Braga]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/98eba2c8-352d-4202-81de-33f72582fc0d.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[General Director]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Wine and beverage distributors are focused on expanding their coverage and gaining market share, intensifying their digitalization efforts, and meeting customers&rsquo; needs in the market.&nbsp;</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[João Morão and João Braga]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[joao-morao-primedrinks-joao-braga-viborel-portugal-2022]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>How has the company evolved since its establishment? </strong></p>
<p><strong>JO&Atilde;O MOR&Atilde;O</strong> PrimeDrinks is the number one wines and spirits distributor in Portugal selling around EUR60 million. It is a cohesive, family-owned company with three shareholders (Espor&atilde;o, Aveleda, and William Grant &amp; Sons). It also represents 10 third-party brand owners in wine&mdash; Ermelinda Freitas, Herdade dos Grous, Carm, Fiuza, Nicolau de Almeida, and Luis Pato&mdash;and spirits (Edrington, Stoli Group, Amber Beverage Group, and Lucas Bols). It has a strong portfolio of leading brands such as Monte Velho, Casal Garcia, Espor&atilde;o, Aveleda, Hendrick&rsquo;s, Grant&rsquo;s, The Balvenie, and Glenfiddich. Currently, sustainability has become a big differentiator for companies across all industries, and bio and natural wines are gaining traction among younger and informed consumers, while categories continue to blur such as ros&eacute;, sangria, wine with flavors, and so on. Alcohol education is fundamental: drink less but better.</p>
<p><strong>JO&Atilde;O BRAGA</strong> Viborel is a successful company and has always earned profits since year one, even during the pandemic. COVID-19 interrupted 10 years of growth for the company, but we are currently almost at our 2019 levels. We have partners that have been with us since the beginning, or almost the beginning. Those represent 80% of our business. The loyalty of our clients is part of our success also. Our core business is focused on still and sparkling wines. Our suppliers, the wineries, all have their export departments, so our knowledge and expertise remains local markets and distribution. We have never sought to go abroad, because we would need teams that would need to have that expertise and create a new department for that purpose. We are doing well, one of the best in the local markets. What achievements are you particularly proud of? JM We are bringing innovation to Portugal by launching Monte Velho Ros&eacute; in 2021 and Monte Velho Bio in 2022. We are doing brand development and expansion into new wine regions: Espor&atilde;o launching Bico Amarelo from the Vinhos Verdes region in 2021 and Aveleda launching Mandriola (red &amp; white wines) from the Lisbon region in 2022. In whisky, we are focused in bringing knowledge and education to the trade and consumer by developing a 360-approach based on the whisky tasting profiles. As leaders, we create trends. The entire company is driven by innovation through in-house processes development and education. JB We were the ones to introduce Red Bull, Monster Energy, Cutty Sark, and Capri Sun in Portugal. Those companies are multinationals, and when we work with these companies we also acquire their know-how. They usually have money to invest and develop their brands and markets, and we learn with them. We also open new points of sale that allow the development and introduction of our main brands. However, the greatest achievement is becoming the distributor of brands there are leaders in their categories and creating the conditions to keep them leaders for next years.</p>
<p><strong>How did the pandemic affect the company&rsquo;s operations? </strong></p>
<p><strong>JM</strong> The pandemic brought uncertainty and doubt in terms of on-trade constraints, raising payments, and cash flow issues. It was critical to manage the financial capacities, address stress tests to maintain the company&rsquo;s structure, and secure cash flow to address business issues. We also developed a digital channel and were the first distributor to implement a digital dedicated business unit. This was followed by a similar approach to the luxury and prestige business area with a fine wine and spirits division to address this big opportunity, particularly for the on-trade reopening.</p>
<p><strong>What are the key advantages that make you a leading player in the local market?</strong></p>
<p><strong>JB </strong>The most important advantage is being an independent distributor. We treat everyone and supplier, big or small, the same way. They all have the same opportunities. Viborel is the only distributor with a mixed style of succeeding in the market. We can fill the market more quickly than others, because we have our sales force, and we can quickly respond to the needs of the market and transfer to the other Portuguese markets, the experience that we have in Lisbon. This is the big difference we have from all the other big distributors of beverages in Portugal. We are an independent, flexible, and agile company.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-05T20:46:20.695Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-04T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c07]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[ DAREFY]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Carlos Sezíµes Managing ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/315e6123-04b3-4e8e-8121-43438baeef80.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[Partner]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Odgers Berndtson]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Luí­s Sí­tima Managing ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/b984c2b4-61c9-4f0c-8e23-ff6272dbda13.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[Partner]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>Given the importance of talent in all organizations, initiatives to increase engagement and develop leadership qualities are becoming an important aspect of HR.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[HR]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[hr]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>How is the company positioned to make change happen in the local business community?</strong></p>
<p>CARLOS SEZ&Otilde;ES We are trying to address leadership and culture in a holistic approach and manner. We try to develop projects that can make the company more effective and a great place to work. That is why we address corporate goals and also assess people, employees, and their expectations. We address issues such as engagement and employment branding. We do both the human side of projects and the corporate side. We try to position ourselves across a wide range of sectors with companies. The company was born in Portugal, it is a Portuguese-based idea, but our mindset is global. Our first client was in Portugal. Our second client was outside Portugal, so we try to address these areas worldwide. We are looking to the Portuguese-speaking countries in Africa to expand our business. The main sponsors for these projects are typically executive level management. They have a broader view of the company and they feel that something must be transformed. The top level management are the first enablers of change. The second enablers are HR managers, because they have the view of the people, the issues and expectations of the driving forces within the company. It is a matter of trying to define a specific scope of transformation and step by step, trying to address that.</p>
<p>LU&Iacute;S S&Iacute;TIMA We are a multinational company specialized in leadership and talent. For over 50 years, Odgers Berndtson has been helping some of the world&rsquo;s largest and best organizations to recruit, advise, and develop their senior talent. We are in 33 countries and we have been in Portugal since 1993. We aim to be the trusted advisors on leadership and talent for our clients. We think of leadership from A to Z, including recruiting top leaders, namely CEOs, C-Level positions, boards, and directors. However, our activity is not limited to executive search; we also advise leaders on their assessment and development, how to build board and top team effectiveness, developing the best leadership and talent strategy for the company, and improving organizational effectiveness. We believe that progress and evolution are all about people. People make the difference, in all aspects of the business and the society. We focus on recruiting, advising and developing great people across the organization. We do it on a case by case basis, putting the right people with the right competencies in the right places at the right time. Our clients should be, and are, the most important companies in Portugal&mdash;mainly top-level companies but also medium-sized companies. We want to be their trusted advisor on integrated solutions and leadership and talent.</p>
<p><strong>What are your key ambitions and targets set in your agenda for the year to come?</strong></p>
<p>CS The quality of our targets is more important than the quantity. We want to impact as much as possible, and impact as many people as possible. The main issue in terms of providing change in organizations relates to impact. We have a B-side called social innovation which we are also focused on. We are providing mentoring and coaching for NGOs, associations, start-ups, community projects. That is also in our DNA to transform, positively, the world, not just the corporate world but also the entire ecosystem in providing support to three small social innovation businesses that are focused on education and fighting social exclusion and poverty. We want to try to improve literacy among children and to teach soft skills at schools.</p>
<p>LS First, we want to continue to growth. We have tripled the value of the company in the last four years. The objective is not to continue at this rate, though we want to continue to grow by double digits. The second point is to grow further on the leadership and organizational consultancy side, where we built strong track record and partnerships with some of the biggest companies in Portugal in last years. Third, we also have other areas of growth, both in executive search and consultancy, by investing more on technologies and AI. Finally, to continue to attract, retain and develop the best leadership and talent advisors in the market, because our business, as all business, is all about people.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2022-08-05T20:31:56.349Z]]></inserttime>
		<publishdate><![CDATA[2022-08-04T23:00:00.000Z]]></publishdate>
		<articlesectorid><![CDATA[5536d10386b7b004b4574c07]]></articlesectorid>
		<articletypeid><![CDATA[552ef2b03616181268784052]]></articletypeid>
		<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		<countryid><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Portugal]]></countryid>
		<geocountryidlist0><![CDATA[]]></geocountryidlist0>
		<intervieweelist0company><![CDATA[Edenred Portugal]]></intervieweelist0company>
		<intervieweelist0description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist0description>
		<intervieweelist0name><![CDATA[Filipa Martins ]]></intervieweelist0name>
		<intervieweelist0photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/36bb2dd4-6f84-4f80-a32a-b4019401451d.jpg]]></intervieweelist0photourl>
		<intervieweelist0position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist0position>
		<intervieweelist1company><![CDATA[Coverflex Portugal]]></intervieweelist1company>
		<intervieweelist1description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist1description>
		<intervieweelist1name><![CDATA[Miguel Santo Amaro ]]></intervieweelist1name>
		<intervieweelist1photourl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/interviewee/1b2f9d57-4b7e-40ce-9d8f-6e8e575a3f8c.jpg]]></intervieweelist1photourl>
		<intervieweelist1position><![CDATA[CEO]]></intervieweelist1position>
		<intervieweelist2company><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2company>
		<intervieweelist2description><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2description>
		<intervieweelist2name><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2name>
		<intervieweelist2photourl><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2photourl>
		<intervieweelist2position><![CDATA[]]></intervieweelist2position>
		<previewsummary><![CDATA[<p>With the increased focus on employee welfare post pandemic, these companies are showing that there are new ways to design attractive compensation packages.</p>]]></previewsummary>
		<status><![CDATA[publish]]></status>
		<subject><![CDATA[]]></subject>
		<tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
		<title><![CDATA[Filipa Martins & Miguel Santo Amaro]]></title>
		<url><![CDATA[filipa-martins-ceo-edenred-portugal]]></url>
		<richbody0content><![CDATA[<p><strong>Can you elaborate on the company&rsquo;s offering?</strong></p>
<p>FILIPA MARTINS Edenred is present in 46 countries. We have about 50 million users around the world, 2 million merchants in the system, and about 900,000 corporate clients. Talking about the Portuguese operations, we have about 500,000 users, 41,000 merchants in our ecosystem, and about 17,000 corporate clients. We are a joint venture with a local bank, and it has been a sustainable operation in terms of growth over the years. There are three main social benefits in Portugal: the meal voucher; benefits in education and infancy; and benefits related to health, seniors, and others. All these have a specific legal framework. These are the projects that we can develop in Portugal in a closed-loop way, because our solutions are social vouchers, not payment means. This also means that companies like us manage the ecosystem, and we attribute these benefits to companies that then forward it to their own employees in the market. Employees can then use their social vouchers in a network of partner merchants.</p>
<p>MIGUEL SANTO AMARO Companies today have to be more flexible and find better, more engaging solutions to attract and retain employees. We help companies design compensation packages so they are more fiscally interesting. It is about becoming the bank of employees featuring the user experience. There are many neo-banks trying to do this, but they generally focus only on the salary. They might not provide access, tools, or information about how an employee can do their taxes or what their total compensation is including the pay slip, a lunch card, health insurance, discounts, and so on. We help employees visualize all that so they can have a full 360-degree view of their finances. We want to democratize access to a great compensation solution. Our actual solution is a dashboard for a company as well as a mobile app and a VISA card for employees. It is an app and a smart card together that replaces many other things. The user experience is much better.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>How do you shape your competitive advantages in a small but highly competitive market?</strong></p>
<p>FM We have five values that guide us through this. The first is passion for customers, and our customers are merchants, users, and clients (MUC). We work to fine-tune our relationships with each one of them, so that they can recommend us in the market. The second value that we foster is respect for the entire ecosystem; therefore, we are extremely transparent in all our communications. The third value, imagination, fosters innovation and inspires our employees to develop new ideas to get ahead of the competition. We started with paper before switching to cards, and now we have cardless solutions. The fourth point is simplicity, basically explaining something that is complex in a simple way to better position ourselves. Finally, we are driven by our entrepreneurial spirit, being that the most important thing is to develop and adapt solutions locally.</p>
<p>MSA Our major focus is the SME market because it is an untapped market. We started in Portugal in January 2021 and have 2,000 clients; we are growing around 30% month to month. In terms of compensation, we conducted EUR30 million worth of transactions in 2021. We process around EUR300 per person every month. We must educate companies about the concept of flexibility: over 80% of our companies did not have a solution before Coverflex. We are onboarding around 200 clients per month, which is only possible if we do it digitally. We are building a compensation package that is in a complete new category, and the challenge is educating the market on how it is an easy tool that can be set up in a few hours. This can be done online or with our support.</p>
<p><strong>What are your main targets in 2022?</strong></p>
<p>FM We have a clear view of what we want to offer the market in 2022, and we expect to accomplish it this year. We will reinforce and enlarge the scope to broaden our offer of social benefits to be a multi-flex benefit platform. We will also accelerate the digitalization of the customer journey. Finally, in the CSR area, our current initiatives are just the beginning for what will come in the next year.</p>
<p>MSA We want to have a global company. We will be comfortable in Portugal, but expanding beyond Portugal is our number-one priority. We are Europeans so we want to focus on Europe for the moment, where there are different currencies, cultures, and laws in terms of compensation and salaries. That will remain our focus. That means raising enough capital to be a top brand that also enables us to hire the team to do that.&nbsp;</p>]]></richbody0content>
		<richbody0imagegallery0imageurl><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0imageurl>
		<richbody0imagegallery0caption><![CDATA[]]></richbody0imagegallery0caption>
		<richbody1content><![CDATA[]]></richbody1content>
	</node>
</data>
