<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2017-01-02T12:19:25.554Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Arab IPO Summit 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The current market trends aim at moving away from dependencies on the oil and energy sectors and IPOs are the most optimum method to encourage foreign and regional investments. It is imperious that financial institutions, private firms, stock exchanges and financial institutions come together and review, discuss and tap the region's investors through IPOs. The Arab IPO Summit aims at a collective collaboration of the top companies, stock exchanges, investment banks and capital markets in sharing their invaluable knowledge and expressing proficient opinions about the present business scenario and predicting the future of the financial markets.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://arabiposummit.com/?utm_source=Website&utm_campaign=TBY&utm_medium=banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f01a6dc7-f813-4de0-8b99-c292a78da7b2.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170314]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170315]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-21T13:46:38.982Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Powering Africa: Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > US]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Washington DC ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Powering Africa: Summit is a platform to showcase power, trade and infrastructure investment opportunities across the African continent, engaging decision makers from the American and African public and private sectors to explore how project bankability can be increased. Under the new US administration, how can the relationship between the US and Africa be strengthened to pave the way for future investments? This year's Summit will showcase project opportunities across the African continent, presented by some of the sector's most respected decision-makers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.energynet.co.uk/event/powering-africa-summit-2017]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/9b2dcd7b-82d6-423f-8471-a37af78ad03a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170308]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170310]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-20T14:23:11.294Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Nigeria Power Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abuja ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Nigeria Power Forum, taking place on 27 February 2017 in Abuja, Nigeria is the premier gathering for high-level stakeholders in Nigeria's power sector. The Forum annually provides a platform for the entire industry value chain to assess the barriers that remain in creating access to electricity across the nation.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.nigeria-power.com/?utm_campaign=media-partner&utm_source=the-business-year&utm_medium=banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/956e5f0d-c32d-4ace-83a3-f0d97e359361.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170227]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170302]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-15T13:21:08.308Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Nigeria Oil & Gas Conference & Exhibition (NOG)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abuja ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Featuring exclusive speakers, sponsors and supporters, as well as an overview of  Africa's largest oil, gas and power exhibition; the latest brochure demonstrates the unrivalled opportunities to hear the latest industry updates and form new business partnerships.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.cwcnog.com/?utm_campaign=media-partner&utm_source=the-business-year&utm_medium=banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7bbfd2eb-b1eb-4f85-aa69-6dc3ce995aea.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170227]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170302]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-14T14:12:41.212Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Romanian Tourism Fair]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Romania]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bucharest ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The spring edition of The Romanian Tourism Fair will take place between the 16th and 19th of February 2017, in 6 halls, from C1 to C6 within Romexpo Exhibition Centre.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.targuldeturism.ro/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0ba2e22d-bde8-4dca-a119-62bd3da080b9.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170216]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170219]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-14T09:45:41.154Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[19th Annual Africa Energy Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/eea28898-d19f-4c94-90da-84abff4b93da.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Denmark]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Copenhagen ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Africa Energy Forum (AEF) is the global investment meeting for Africa's power, energy, infrastructure and industrial sectors. Nineteen years in the running, AEF brings together senior-level representatives from governments, utilities, regulators, power developers, financial institutions, technology providers, consultants, law firms and large energy consumers to form partnerships, identify opportunities and collectively move the industry forward. AEF has a loyal following of credible players working in the power space, and a track record of delivering a valuable networking experience.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://africa-energy-forum.com/?utm_campaign=Media]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/369dabbb-d860-463d-ab1c-3a6605632ae8.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170606]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170608]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-12T13:52:59.669Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Russian Investment Summit 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Back in 2014 Russia experienced major politico-economic turbulence which has led to a deep recession. Some say that the impact cannot be compared to the 2008 crisis, whereas others see more positive outcomes; the investment market, which always bring high yields, has never been so cheap. Due to a rigorous policy set by the Russian Central Bank the economy is expected to show recovery in 2017. At the same time, the realisation that the country cannot purely rely on natural resources has brought an economic diversification plan on to the agenda.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://newspartaevents.net/event/russia2017/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d769640e-7ef1-48fa-a333-c7359f8ff7af.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170323]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170323]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-12T13:51:26.033Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Central and South Eastern Europe Investment Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the last few years CEE – SEE has seen significant growth and investment across the region. This has led to countries such as Romania potentially moving to emerging market status and according to analysts Poland, Czech Republic and Hungary experienced double GDP growth in the Q3 of 2016 in comparison to other EU countries. Greece is on the rebound after a tough few years and the chances for more debt relief are looking promising going into 2017- 2018. Asian investors are keeping a close eye on the region and have reaffirmed their commitment by setting up CSEE-focused funds, such as China-CEE fund in Poland and Romania.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://newspartaevents.net/event/csee/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8547bcc0-b5ba-4395-9d4e-6642950e506f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170329]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170329]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-08T14:22:36.020Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Middle East Smart Landscape Summit 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The fifth edition of the Middle East Smart Landscape Summit will take place on 15-16 May 2017 at Sofitel Dubai The Palm Resort &amp; Spa. As the only landscape focused conference in Dubai, the event emphasizes on the region's commitment to the sustainable growth of green spaces and will outline innovative approaches to green transformation. As the region's leading landscaping event, the summit aims to promote investment in green infrastructure and present the diverse opportunities and obstacles faced in increasing green landscapes in the city. The 2016 edition of the summit was successfully held under the patronage of Dubai Municipality. With over 400 delegates in attendance, the summit provided an exclusive platform for senior landscape architects, contractors, landscape engineering consultants, government officials and developers from the GCC region to discuss smart, innovative and sustainable landscaping technology and best practices in the industry.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://linktrack.info/.25w0y]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5f68f023-6c36-4752-b39a-0a8abd3f1e4f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170514]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170515]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-08T14:21:19.645Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Middle East Smart Lighting & Design Summit 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Having successfully organized the summit in Abu Dhabi for the past five years, the event has now moved to Dubai. The Middle East Smart Lighting and Design Summit is the leading lighting design event in the region focusing on public lighting, urban lighting, street lighting and smart controls &amp; automation. The event will be held on 26-27 April 2017 in Dubai. Specially designed for lighting technology and design professionals, the summit will witness over 300 lighting consultants, designers, architects, developers, engineers and government officials coming together to gain information on remotely controlled intelligent lighting solutions, new techniques and innovative approaches to lighting design from renowned experts based regionally and across the globe.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://linktrack.info/.25w0x]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/81c6a9c6-7110-431b-b592-7fe6f046900f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170425]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170426]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-08T14:19:31.380Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Arab Future Cities Summit Qatar 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Qatar]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Doha ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With the World Cup 2022 fast approaching and in a bid to facilitate its National Vision Strategy 2030, the Qatar Government has undertaken a number of initiatives across sectors that involve implementation of technology along with seamless execution of major infrastructure projects. Industry reports indicate that the government is expected to spend $40bn on railways, $15.5bn on the new airport, $20bn investment in roads, $7.4bn on the new port and $4bn on stadiums. Against this backdrop, the 2017 Arab Future Cities Summit's aim is to highlight the building blocks required towards achieving a sustainable and connected city. Under the theme Advanced Technology Transforming Qatar's Future, the Arab Future Cities Summit Qatar to be held on 10th and 11th April 2017 at The Ritz Carlton, Doha will touch upon the key aspects of connected transport, smart stadiums, cyber security, airport technology, security, government technology and smart economic zones, amongst many others. The fifth edition of the summit held under the patronage of Ministry of Transport &amp; Communications and Ministry of Municipality and Environment Qatar was a stupendous success, witnessing over 450 senior industry professionals in attendance.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://linktrack.info/.25w0w]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3ed0f36b-7c0e-4a67-beec-e0b4b0320378.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170409]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170410]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-08T14:17:54.040Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Smart Data Summit 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/0eb370bc-7776-45dd-975f-5e42b4c2575a.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past three years, the Smart Data Summit has emerged as the leading big data and analytics event in the Middle East region. In its fourth year, the summit will explore the benefits and evaluate the business potential of using big data and analytics in day-to-day business. The 4th Annual Smart Data Summit will be held on 3rd and 4th April 2017 at Sofitel Dubai The Palm Resort &amp; Spa. The 2016 edition of the summit saw experts from globally renowned organizations coming together to emphasize on the potential of big data and analytics and its impact across different industry verticals.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://linktrack.info/.25w0v]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c0c9bf13-6161-4090-bfe9-a4c9d763c431.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170402]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170403]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-08T14:12:56.460Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Aluminium Middle East]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>ALUMINIUM MIDDLE EAST is the biggest gathering for aluminium professionals and the leading exhibition for aluminium products, technologies and investments in the Middle East. Launched in 2009, the event brings together international industry front-runners including producers, manufacturers and processors of raw materials and end products made with aluminium components, as well as suppliers of technologies and accessories for aluminium production, processing and refinement. <br>In its 5th edition, ALUMINIUM MIDDLE EAST gathers 180+ exhibitors from 30+ countries and over 3,500 industry professionals are expected from more than 70 countries. The event will highlight the Middle East's future role as the world's powerhouse in aluminium production and facilitate discussions on uplifting the downstream sectors to support this phenomenal growth in upstream industries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.aluminium-middleeast.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c010c51d-1ae6-4ba9-99e9-2d622b2b528d.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170514]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170516]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T15:13:35.596Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Middle East Refining Technology Conference (MERTC)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Bahrain]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The World Refining Association (WRA) are excited to announce the launch of MERTC (Middle East Refining Technology Conference) taking place on the 23-24 January 2017 in Manama, Bahrain. The inaugural MERTC will be the premier meeting place for downstream technology and innovation. MERTC will utilize WRA's 20 years of experience in a new flagship event for the region. WRA's strategic content , stakeholder support, and innovative formats will will combine advisory board scored papers and technical content to become the number one refining and petrochemical technology event for the Middle East.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://mertc.wraconferences.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/cae3096f-e78c-4d8d-a3ca-5312f2997681.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170123]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170124]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T11:45:11.317Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GETENERGY VTEC MENA 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Italy]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Milan ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Getenergy will be hosting our 4th Getenergy VTEC MENA meeting for host Governments and the oil and gas industry to focus on collaborating to develop sustainable localised operations across the Middle East &amp; North Africa taking place on 26th – 27th January 2017 in Milan. The event is co-hosted with Eni, and will be held alongside the 11th North Africa Oil &amp; Gas Summit and the North African Downstream Summit. The meeting will engage strategic discussions on shaping future skills development initiatives and how Governments and oil and gas companies can best support each other in their aims to deliver commercially successful projects for both citizens and shareholders alike. The event supports companies in the optimisation of training strategies, informs the strategic direction of local's talent development and assists local education systems in better aligning with the industry's needs.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://mena.getenergyevent.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0245b8dd-7346-4d08-a1e4-3be818dad81d.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170126]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170127]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T11:43:25.067Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[European Gas Conference 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Austria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Vienna ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In recent years the gas market has undergone tremendous shifts with the emergence of new supply sources, the comeback of coal in the power sector, the decline of domestic production and the severe fall in oil and gas prices. However, one fact remains certain: gas is and will remain a central pillar of the European energy mix and promoting mutually beneficially relationships with Europe's major supplier key. With 432 participants, 12 sponsors and 30 hours of networking in 2016, the 2017 Summit will set new levels of attendance and engagement through stimulating panel discussions, insightful presentations and invaluable networking opportunities for the European gas community.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.europeangas-conference.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f8b90c2d-e957-4357-9ae7-0e7c1f69f42e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170123]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170125]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T11:40:35.852Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[North Africa Downstream Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Italy]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Milan ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The North Africa Downstream Summit has been specifically designed to provide operators from the refining and petrochemical industry a platform to share insight, expertise and best practices. Co-located with the 11th annual North Africa Oil &amp; Gas Summit, the summit is the ideal platform for vendors to present the solutions and technologies to succeed in times of extremely tight operating margins.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://nads.wraconferences.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/14fd8723-836f-4b2b-9ca8-413b00c26220.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170126]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161227]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T11:39:17.056Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[North Africa Oil & Gas Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Italy]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Milan ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>For the past 11 years, the North Africa Oil &amp; Gas Summit has been the meeting place for North African NOCs and their partners. Co-located with the 4th North Africa Downstream Summit, the events represent the ideal platform to explore upstream and downstream opportunities for investment, understand the benefits of latest technologies and plan financial strategies to support oil and gas projects across the region.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://nas.theenergyexchange.co.uk/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2496d8ac-1ab5-47a3-870c-0a0c0f93939d.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170126]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170127]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T10:51:23.441Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Insurance Innovations 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With a history of 6 successful annual events, the Middle East and Africa Insurance Summit, presents its 7th edition as - Insurance Innovation 2017, with a to inculcate innovation and regulated, digital transformation so as to be updated with the dynamic and ever-growing insurance sector. Rotating around the central theme of "Gateway to explore New Opportunities", this conference aims to engage in in-depth discussion on progressive topics such as Insurance Aggregators, Telematics, InsurTech Options, Digital transformation, product innovation and much more.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://fleming.events/en/events/finance/insurance-innovations?utm_source=The%20Business%20Year&utm_medium=Listing]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/9c40ba81-264d-45c4-982f-382c90deccb7.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170313]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170314]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-06T10:50:04.432Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Kingdom Education Innovation 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Riyadh ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This two day summit will provide a platform to discover, develop, learn and explore technology to improve learning, school operations and raise standards. Rotating around the central theme of “Collaborate – Innovate - Educate”, this conference aims to provide a platform for Ministries, government bodies, private professionals, industry experts and solution providers to discuss and brainstorm on the reforms and innovations in the education sector in the region.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://fleming.events/en/events/hr/kingdom-education-innovation?utm_source=The%20Business%20Year&utm_medium=Listing]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/16c2ef1d-8eb1-4d2e-891e-dc013a515697.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170306]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170307]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-05T14:33:42.029Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Almaty Invest 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Kazakhstan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Almaty ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hosted by the Administration of Almaty city, this event will focus on investment opportunities Almaty provides, especially with regards to large-scale infrastructural projects, retail sector, tourism, food processing and light industry. The forum will feature series of discussions, interactive presentations and workshops (including topics such as state support measures for investors and businesses), as well as tours to special free economic zone, industrial spaces, and touristic destinations.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.almatyinvest.com/en]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/b15a2737-942b-43c5-af75-fdf5a7cd82d5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161207]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161209]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-02T12:55:05.553Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Ras Al Khaimah Finance & Investment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Ras Al Khaimah ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Ras Al Khaimah Finance and Investment Forum (RAKFIF) is a high-level two day international business investment and finance forum bringing experts from government and leading industries across various sectors of Ras Al Khaimah together with international and regional investors and financiers to explore business opportunities in the Rising Emirate.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.rakfif.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/6051eed7-b408-48bf-9e67-c3fbdb4b47b7.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161213]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161214]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-02T12:49:16.990Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Electric, Power & Renewable Energy 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>EPRE is Malaysia's flagship show for power generation and transmission and will focus on all the current methods of energy generation placing much emphasis on the increasing importance of renewable energy as the landscape of energy mix changes in line with the Government's commitment to increasing the percentage contribution from non fossil fuel sources. No other trade show in this sector can give you that unique international content coupled with the strong local government support that will enable you to maximise on the business opportunities currently available in this fast moving energy market.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.epremalaysia.com/home/index.php]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/25ceea3a-c32c-46c4-93d1-ac96dac80d44.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170315]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170317]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-12-02T12:44:14.871Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Saudi Water and Environment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/80c985ff-8c81-4d41-bf7b-2a44dde4a8e3.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Riyadh ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Officially endorsed by the Ministry of Environment, Water &amp; Agriculture, SWEF 2017 is THE meeting place for the KSA's water and environmental services. International investors will have the opportunity to meet senior officials from the Ministry of Environment Water &amp; Agriculture (MEWA), the National Water Company (NWC), Saline Water Conversion Corporation (SWCC), Electricity Co-generation Regulatory Authority (ECRA), and the General Authority of Meteorology and Environment (GAMEP). It also provides an ideal opportunity to meet and establish relationships with key utility companies, major industrial consumers and leading local stakeholders.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://saudiwaterenvironment.com/?utm_campaign=media-partner&utm_source=the-business-year&utm_medium=banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/6fdae612-ec2b-4a3e-bad6-47796a504e9d.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170212]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170214]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-30T14:06:08.794Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[West African International Petroleum Exhibition and Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lagos ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The West African International Petroleum Exhibition and Conference (WAIPEC) is the only oil and gas event held in partnership with Nigeria's petroleum industry. Working directly with PETAN, the organizers will draw on their global resources to ensure that the event delivers to the needs of all stakeholders in Nigeria and through the region.</p><p>WAIPEC 2017 will be the largest petroleum event of its kind in West Africa, as the city of Lagos welcomes thousands of key regional stakeholders - plus leading international E&amp;P firms and partners - to develop and drive new business across the sector.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.waipec.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/388e807d-7102-4aa2-8be1-ffac69a86123.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170221]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170223]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-30T09:44:18.142Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[2nd Kuwait International HSE Conference & Exhibition (KIHSE)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Kuwait]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuwait City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Kuwait International HSE Conference &amp]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.kihse.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d3d58b70-a1bc-481f-9c1a-c77b31008e88.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170215]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170216]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-29T12:15:48.655Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Hydropower Caspian & Central Asia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/b9077d83-5e2c-4f1e-a6f1-d1a8c1f14aa8.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Georgia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tbilisi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This international congress is a professional platform for high-level participants to discuss key topics to guide the course for hydropower construction and operation in the Caspian and Central Asia region. High-profile speakers will discuss the changing role of hydropower in the energy mix and the benefits of interconnections beyond national borders. Participants will review initiatives and commitments and discuss action priorities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.hydropowercongress.com/en/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0132c1d7-a49f-408b-9408-eb4c7f50daec.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170215]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170217]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-28T15:12:41.210Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Airport Show 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Airport Show provides an ideal B2B platform for companies to showcase airport and aviation-related products and services.  In 2016, the event gathered 7,166 aviation professionals who networked, sourced their product requirements at the show. The 17th edition of the Airport Show will be held from 15-17 May 2017 at the Dubai International Convention and Exhibition Centre (DICEC). The world's leading B2B event for airport procurement, supplies, solutions and technology enjoys solid support from both the government and private sectors and is an industry favourite.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://registration.n200.com/survey/15xj8injd6sxa?actioncode=NTWO000173FGV]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ba52b4fa-4b60-43a6-96d7-ce6913750ba1.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170514]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170516]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-28T08:10:15.963Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Big Show Oman 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The BIG Show (Builders International Gathering) is an annual international exhibition that caters to the building and construction industry in Oman, the Middle East and global markets.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.thebigshow-oman.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ab4c237f-6aa7-4504-a6f9-ec0df01afffa.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170313]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170316]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-24T12:11:11.448Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Iran Oil & Gas]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Azerbaijan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Baku ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It is exciting to see that Iran is currently opening up after two decades of sanctions, which are now being gradually lifted. This presents a huge opportunity for major oil companies, investors and our most prominent international clients looking for the next, and probably one of the last, big emerging market play. Timely to this important market development, we are proud to bring you a high-profile large-scale 2 day event in Baku for the international oil and gas community.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.iranenergyconference.com/index.php/en/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ef7b357a-c70c-4374-b787-d49eec924c3e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170314]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170315]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-18T14:46:07.291Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Saudi Transtec 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dammam ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its debut in 2010 SAUDI TRANSTEC receives official support from the Ministry of Transportation and the logistics and supply chain community throughout the region. The exhibition has been recognised as the top exhibition in the sectors of Transport, Freight Delivery, Warehousing and Logistics. After a successful trade show in 2015, SAUDI TRANSTEC is already geared up for the 2016 edition. By attracting a very targeted audience for the participating companies, SAUDI TRANSTEC has once again proved that this is a strong trading platform where increasing your distribution network, strengthening business relationship and sharing industry developments.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[www.sauditranstec.com]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ccf31606-05ee-4d9d-9934-805156658d88.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161205]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-17T14:11:50.515Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Healthcare Insurance Forum 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The healthcare insurance sector is highly competitive and many organisations are running losses as they underwrite too much risk to maintain operations. Viable operations may be achieved through differentiation and creating a niche within the sector as well as taking advantage of the technological advancements to gain new business.</p><p>This workshop will focus on best practice to help your organization get ahead of the competition. Practical information will be shared on:</p><ul><li>Mitigating your risk and ensuring sustainable returns</li><li>Harnessing technology for customer attraction and retention</li><li>Customizing benefits in your offering while ensuring profitability</li></ul>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.healthcareinsuranceforumme.com/Forms/BrochureDownload/?utm_source=The%20business%20Year&utm_medium=banner-mediapartner&utm_content=healthcareinsuranceforumme+AZ3200+CFHC+mediapartnerbaner+17Nov2016&utm_campaign=The%20Business%20Year]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0478ac19-dffd-459c-93c3-a578f0813948.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170130]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170202]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-17T14:03:38.355Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Sustainable Energy & Technology Asia 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The premier Asian annual energy and technology event, Sustainable Energy &amp; Technology Asia (SETA) is ongoing to develop an international platform for the value chain of energy to meet and discuss the latest issues the policy planning and technology advancement to support the global low carbon advocacy.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.seta.asia/registration/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d19fa5b8-67ef-467e-8970-a210bfc8f92e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170308]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170310]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-17T07:38:51.735Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Advanced Manufacturing]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>For the first time in Mexico, key buyers processing, packaging, automation, advanced design &amp; manufacture assembled for the first time.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://manufacturingmx.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7cb4dad2-4a87-4bff-ad58-ed21f8d851bd.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161115]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161117]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-15T13:34:40.790Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[ZIMEC 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/f9778fe3-58b6-4217-b867-4902211d2259.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Zambia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lusaka ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>For 6 years, ZIMEC has played a pivotal role in shaping a sustainable growth path for the development of Zambia's mining and energy sectors.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://ametrade.org/zimeczambia/?utm_source=The%20Business%20Year&utm_campaign=Zimec%202017&utm_medium=Banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/04ec16e3-acb8-407e-a8b5-52147cb43363.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170621]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170622]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-15T13:33:39.299Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mozam Build]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/339b3b94-33dd-45c4-ac1c-784225c2691d.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Mozambique]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Maputo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>MOZAMBUILD is the leading and most well established, construction, building and interiors trade event in Mozambique.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mozambuild.com/?utm_source=The%20Business%20Year&utm_campaign=Mozambuild%202017&utm_medium=Banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d1c896b0-eeea-4a4d-b2ef-6d37ae379dae.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170315]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170317]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-15T13:32:46.909Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mining on Top: Africa Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/b76e3989-25ad-4583-af98-a31d99738636.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Germany]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Frankfurt ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 4th Mining on Top- Africa London Summit (MOTA) will be held in Frankfurt, Germany on the 6-7 July 2017 . The two- day conference is expected to attract over 200 participants from over 20 countries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://ametrade.org/miningontopafrica/?utm_source=The%20Business%20Year&utm_campaign=Mota%202017&utm_medium=Banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e63c0a7a-f992-48b1-8d7c-fefbd62fb13b.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170705]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170706]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-15T13:30:51.358Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Turkey 2016: Business on the Bosphorus]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite recent political unrest Turkey's economy is still growing at a relatively steady pace. Increased government spending and a 6% rise in private investments show that Turkey still remains an attractive market for investors new and old. Turkey 2016: Business on the Bosphorus will look at where the opportunities for investment and growth lie. The event will also look at understanding the impact of the government's push for privatisation and the state of Turkey's financial sector going into 2017.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.newspartaevents.net/event/turkey-2016/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d94eaa23-96b8-4f71-88f3-8056e80c00ca.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161207]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-14T10:31:57.890Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[23rd International Energy & Environment Fair & Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/4c50e871-24da-42ba-bac2-8950493ba43e.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The most sustainable international energy fair organized every year on a regular basis in Turkey since 1994. It is Turkey's biggest energy fair with its 285 exhibitors. It is also the most environmentalist event for it is Turkey's first carbon neutral fair and conference. It is the only international platform where conference, B2B meetings and fair activities are carried out concurrently.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.icci.com.tr/en]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/053bce82-a9d8-4a58-b519-194bdd507d95.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170502]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170504]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-14T08:17:28.318Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Regional Energy Co-operation Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/c657ad9b-b814-468a-9212-a9e746bd43ec.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Ivory Coast]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abidjan ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Regional Energy Co-operation Summit takes place each year in a different city of the region and the Republic of Côte d'Ivoire is the host country from 25-27 January 2017. The Summit comes as an evolution of the successful Powering Africa: Ghana meeting which took place in 2015. Energy, infrastructure and finance will form the cornerstones of the discussions. Cross-border cooperation in West Africa is crucial to develop mechanisms that facilitate trade and power exchange among States. Sessions will address cross-border co-operation and regional integration, unlocking West Africa's investments in energy and infrastructure to support industrialisation. This meeting so for has the full support of the Ministry of Power of the Republic of Ghana, GRIDCo, Electricity Company of Ghana (ECG), and the Public Utilities Regulatory Commission (PURC) as well as the West African Power Pool (WAPP) and ECOWAS Regional Electricity Regulatory Authority (ERERA).</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.energynet.co.uk/event/regional-energy-cooperation-summit-2017]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/bcb31c3c-ca21-4c17-9dc6-53b54f640a1e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170125]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170127]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-10T15:04:36.016Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Offshore Mexico Congress 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Gulf of Mexico is an exploring hot spot for international offshore players. Mexico acts as an emerging market in the region, attracting more attention. OMC will focus on the latest policy and strategy in the country, ongoing projects and upcoming deepwater bidding in Round One, learning technology and project management from the excellent projects around Gulf of Mexico.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.szwgroup.com/offshore-mexico-congress-2016/?hmsr=TBY&hmpl=W&hmcu=OMC2016&hmkw=&hmci=]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/bf6a9be7-0381-440e-b561-4c57e80bf844.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161117]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161118]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-10T14:53:46.319Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[3rd Annual Post Trade Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Austria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Vienna ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://glceurope.com/3rd-annual-post-trade-forum/?utm_source=thebusinessyear&utm_medium=media_partner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7b8dbf5e-f8ea-4310-af52-01fdd5e18aaf.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170223]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170224]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-10T14:51:12.617Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[3rd Annual Credit Risk Management Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Germany]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Berlin ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://glceurope.com/3rd-annual-credit-risk-management-forum-details/?utm_source=thebusinessyear&utm_medium=media_partner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/b99da7f7-d639-4668-a984-854cacb592ae.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170302]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170303]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-10T14:47:27.257Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[4th Annual Back Office Operations Forum (BOOF)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Austria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Vienna ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://glceurope.com/4th-annual-back-office-operations-forum-details/?utm_source=thebusinessyear&utm_medium=media_partner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a1c1a00a-cf1f-4633-9441-2464ce174306.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161124]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161125]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-09T08:58:37.090Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[InvestPro UAE Dubai 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/1c19c05f-d1e0-4117-80ec-92bda76f0daf.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Bosco Conference invites you to join the b2c conference InvestPro UAE Dubai 2016, which will take place on December 06 - 07th, Grosvenor House, Dubai. Conference InvestPro UAE Dubai 2016 is devoted to international investment, finance, wealth management and asset protection, building global business structures. Essential questions will be highlighted by the leading professionals and consultants from the Middle East, Asia and Europe.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.bosco-conference.com/en/events/upcoming/investpro-uae-dubai-2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/9a725db7-820a-4ef5-9fb6-718c39afb4d3.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161206]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-04T11:54:11.889Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Kurdistan-Iraq Oil & Gas]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>For the 6th consecutive year, the premier and largest strategic event in the history of the Kurdistan Region returns to London.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.cwckiog.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/583fb5ab-8bcd-4689-a234-3cecdc157490.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161205]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-04T11:52:50.015Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mozambique Gas Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Mozambique]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Maputo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Mozambique Gas Summit &amp; Exhibition, organised in partnership with ENH, and with the full support from INP and CMH, is the most established gas event in the country. Now in its third edition, the event welcomes high level international gas leaders to meet with the Government and national companies to discuss latest developments, projects and partnerships available in the region.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mozambique-gas-summit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/787a2204-cfdb-40fa-9366-1c7147fcad08.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161130]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161202]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-01T14:18:37.559Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Real Estate Development and Investment Meet (REDIM) 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Real Estate Development and Investment Meet (REDIM) 2017 which takes place on the 27th – 28th of February in Dubai, UAE will see the coming together of active and pre-qualified Investors and Developers who all have key interests in tapping into the Middle East &amp; African Real Estate sector. The objective of REDIM 2017 is to showcase numerous Real Estate Development &amp; Investment opportunities all across Middle East &amp; Africa through 'Real Life' Case study presentations running back-to-back and to ultimately ignite deal making strategies during the course of the 2-Day event</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://aebicongroup.com/event/2016-real-estate-development-and-investment-meet-dubai/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c742a3cd-5c73-427f-b799-a0d18465698e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170227]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170228]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-01T14:07:30.025Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mining Investment Asia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Singapore]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining Investment Asia is a strategic mining conference and exhibition for the leaders of the mining, quarrying and construction materials industries, bringing together 1100 attendees from 35 countries. Ministers, mining companies, investors and service providers travel from all over Asia, North America, Europe, Middle East and Africa for four days of partnering, networking and business matching. Join us at an invaluable platform to seek new partnerships, new business and new opportunities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mininginvestmentasia.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1f7b55eb-9ec9-4f10-9f42-a61cf424cc8f.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170327]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170330]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-01T14:04:22.718Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mining Investment Botswana]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Botswana]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Gaborone ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining Investment Botswana is a strategic mining conference and exhibition for the leaders of the mining, quarrying and construction materials industries, bringing together 400 attendees from 15 countries. Ministers, mining companies, investors and service providers travel from all over Africa, Europe, Asia, North America and Middle East for three days of partnering, networking and business matching. Join us at an invaluable platform to seek new partnerships, new business and new opportunities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mininginvestmentbotswana.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c1f3544a-d6c4-4271-9571-75692b954290.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170213]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170215]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-01T14:02:14.162Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mining Investment Europe]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Germany]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Frankfurt, Germany]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining Investment Europe is a strategic mining conference and exhibition for the leaders of the mining, quarrying and construction materials industries, bringing together 250 attendees from 20 countries. Mining companies, investors, governments and service providers travel from all over Europe, Middle East, Asia and North America for three days of partnering, networking and business matching. Join us at an invaluable platform to seek new partnerships, new business and new opportunities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mininginvestmenteurope.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f304784a-5a0e-4152-835c-96738053c3b9.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170301]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170303]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-11-01T10:43:35.951Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Egypt Trade & Export Finance Conference 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo, Egypt]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Building on its established presence in the Mena region, GTR is excited to be returning to Cairo following a 3-year hiatus in the country for the Egypt Trade &amp; Export Finance Conference 2016. Featuring influential speakers from across the trade finance community, including local and international banks, financiers, leading corporates, lawyers, insurers and more, this will provide a key platform for anyone looking to develop trade relationships in Egypt.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gtreview.com/events/mena/egypt-trade-export-finance-conference-2016/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d9dfe740-45fa-4204-9010-845ef38a45b6.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161115]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161115]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-31T13:42:27.613Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Oman Minerals & Mining Exhibition & Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Oman Minerals &amp; Mining Exhibition &amp; Conference is an international trade event that aims to be a business platform for the rapidly growing metal and non-metal industry in Oman by showcasing the latest services and technology used in mining operations, leveraging the increasing demand for minerals, discussing and addressing topics and issues relevant to the expansion of the industry, and attracting investment. It aims to support government initiatives to develop the sector in Oman and the Middle East as a whole.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.omanminingexpo.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a97a5126-679b-4ee5-a4f7-19791bd3c889.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170116]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170117]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-27T13:07:09.335Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Petrochemistry-2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai, UAE]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>International Conference on Oil, Gas and Petrochemistry is going to be held during April 03-05, 2017 at Dubai, UAE. Petrochemistry-2017 is a gathering of researchers,leading scientists,engineers and technology developers in to exchange information on their latest research and innovation. This scientific conference facilitate sharing and collaboration between world class researchers. Petrochemistry-2017 has sessions covering key political, economic, and environmental issues affecting the petrochemical industry. The sessions emphasize global competitiveness in the petrochemical business and are presented by recognized experts in the area of petrochemistry. Petrochemistry-2017 conference includes Plenary lectures, Keynote lectures and short courses by eminent personalities from around the world in addition to contributed papers both oral and poster presentations.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://petrochemistry.madridge.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/147605fc-77a5-4ba6-828b-6ec82d1e953b.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170402]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170404]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-26T10:55:07.332Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GCC HVAC Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With the construction business on in full swing across GCC, the need for an efficient HVAC system that can bring down the energy consumption is the need of the hour. With events such as Dubai Expo 2020 and the FIFA World Cup in Qatar, the demand for HVAC technologies is on the rise and trends indicate that it will continue rising. </p><p>The GCC HVAC Summit 2016 for the first time brings the who's who of the industry under together for discussions, deliberations on technological advances and landmark events that are helping shape this industry for the better.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.thehvacsummit.com]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0691b6f5-39fd-4856-9bcd-fdd561535987.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161102]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161103]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-25T14:41:32.260Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Jeddah Urban Development Event – Powered by Cityscape]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/c4ac120a-43f2-44db-88b7-e44f9e6f57de.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jeddah, Saudi Arabia]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Connect with leading real estate professionals, keep up to date with the latest trends in Saudi real estate, and develop business opportunities with over 70 exhibiting companies during a 3 day exhibition you cannot afford to miss and network with over 8,000 of your industry peers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.jeddahurbandevelopment.com/forms/visitor-pre-registration-form?utm_medium=Display&utm_source=Freemedia&utm_campaign=CSJD2016-the-business-year-web-banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/226b9d67-0aab-41d2-99da-b0a2e1640150.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161102]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161104]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-25T12:16:37.618Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Petroleum Conference Iran 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>PETROLEUM CONFERENCE – IRAN is the voice of Iran's petroleum industry's private sector, which for the first time has united all the major oil &amp; gas industry associations in Iran including: ICCIM (Iran Chamber of Commerce, Industries and Mines), APEC (The Association of petroleum industry engineering and construction companies), S.I.P.I.E.M (Society of Iranian Petroleum Industry Equipment Manufacturers), SATSA (Iran Industrial Equipment Manufacturers Association), OPEX (Iranian oil, gas and petrochemical products exporters' union), ICCA (International Consultants and Contractors Association of Iran), ECCA – OPI (Engineering and Construction Companies Association) and APIC (Association Petrochemical Industry Corporation). The associations have come together to host the international Petroleum Conference – Iran 2017, with Iran's Head of Parliament H.E. Dr. Ali Larijani, Minister of Petroleum H.E Mr. Bijan Zanganeh, and Iran's President Deputy in Science &amp; Technology Dr. Sorena Sattari who have been invited to speak about the updates on current commercial projects and insights into the investment opportunities presented by Iran's petroleum sector.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.petroconfex.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/915afd71-d342-4b19-b08c-8d0250113a3e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170130]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170201]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-24T13:56:13.904Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[EU-Arab World Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Greece]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Athens ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Union and Arab world have throughout the years been sharing a destiny of geographical proximity, economic and political cooperation on many fronts. The two major worlds have a long history of cross-fertilization and human and cultural exchanges that had shaped their heritage and shared history and values. However, a legacy of conflicts and misunderstandings has in many instances affected both worlds' ability to leverage this natural complementarity in order to establish strategic partnerships and create a global Euro-Arab zone of stability and prosperity.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.iktissadevents.com/events/EAS/1?utm_source=EAS2016_TBY&utm_medium=EAS2016_TBY&utm_campaign=EAS2016_TBY&utm_term=EAS2016_TBY&utm_content=EAS2016_TBY]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4545e265-1e90-4504-907f-d50ac7c1b280.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161103]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161104]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-20T12:48:32.212Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[2nd World Congress and Expo on Oil, Gas and Petrochemistry]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>2nd World Congress and Expo on Oil, Gas and Petrochemistry invites all the participants across the globe to Abu Dhabi, UAE from November 28-30, 2016. Petrochemistry-2016 addresses issues involved in asset condition evaluation for exploration, drilling, production systems, pipelines, terminals, refining, chemical manufacturing and storage facilities and health hazards. Each day focuses on presentations relevant to upstream, midstream, downstream operation and integrity management and provides an opportunity to learn about new and existing industry codes and standards, to hear about emerging trends from experts. The conference will bring together all the experts and professionals of the industry, academia, consultancies, and scientists and will offer them a great platform where they can share their experiences and ideas with others and discuss about the latest advancement of the energy sector.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://scientificfuturegroup.com/petrochemistry-2016/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/18f877b9-09b6-48ca-a505-db11ac93d594.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161128]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161130]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-20T12:46:07.011Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[3rd Annual African Insurance Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > South Africa]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Johannesburg ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Annual African Insurance Forum will bring together the most progressive insurance leaders in the region to drive unparalleled strategic advancement. Join this elite group as they look for new ways to engage with an evolving customer, open new routes to market, or reshape old ones to reach new customers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://ins.fextons.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e5711762-6bdc-4686-b5c1-99817b8bdb2f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170309]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170310]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-20T07:18:54.595Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Nigeria Mining Week]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abuja ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>PwC Nigeria and Infrastructure Partnerships for African Development present a two-day high-level forum at an opportune time for the solid minerals sector in Nigeria. With a new government in place with a desire to exploit Nigeria's vastly underexploited natural resources in the wake of the drop in oil prices, IPAD Nigeria will initiate and fast-track a new mineral sector reform roadmap that encourages and provides innovative business ventures and supports partnership opportunities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.ipad-nigeria.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5875f16b-e763-40be-888c-0349a9fbcbcb.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161024]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161026]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-19T12:13:50.808Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi International Downstream Summit 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/99c664be-1f56-4310-aca2-dac36efdbade.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The World Refining Association would like to thank all Abu Dhabi Downstream International 2016 attendees, speakers and sponsors for contributing to another hugely successful event, and we look forward to welcoming you to the 18th Abu Dhabi International Downstream Summit in 2017.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://adid.wraconferences.com/?utm_source=external&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=thebusinessyear]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7efb6311-69a1-4b5b-873a-5367ed9286fd.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170917]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170918]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-19T12:11:31.326Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Annual GPCA Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/67f63b2b-c57d-4fef-8f0a-c409c4f47ace.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past decade, the Annual Forum - GPCA's flagship event - has not only become a key feature in the global chemical industry agenda, but also a crucial knowledge sharing and networking platform for regional and global stakeholders. In 2015, over 2,000 members of the international chemical community gathered together in Dubai to celebrate the achievements and growth of the petrochemical industry in the Arabian Gulf region and 10 years of the Annual Forum, which throughout the years have become a key feature in the global chemical industry agenda. We confidently expect an even bigger audience in 2016 and the strongest and most business critical program in its history.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gpcaforum.net/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d7a0f96f-cd9c-4606-b478-e71f8b9eae16.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161127]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161129]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-19T08:49:02.772Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Islamic Banking Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Bahrain]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bahrain]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>For 23 years, the World Islamic Banking Conference (WIBC) has solidified its reputation as the indisputable compass for the global Islamic finance and banking industry, building a robust platform that comprises of leading bankers, institutional investors, asset managers, policy makers, academics and other stakeholders from across the globe.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://wibc2016.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0ce29f09-fda2-43ed-a374-a99d0a779cfc.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161205]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-19T07:15:57.548Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Retail Congress 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Since the launch event in Barcelona in 2007, the World Retail Congress has established itself as a vital and unique meeting place for the global retail industry. Attracting retail leaders from across all sectors and geographies, it has come to represent a barometer for the latest ideas, strategies and innovations that help the industry move forward.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.worldretailcongress.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/94cf8be6-7009-4194-a326-50af6eb4cb80.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170403]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170405]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-17T11:17:15.051Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Iran Hotel & Tourism Investment Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/6fd828a3-4dc4-4346-b656-93e818b76067.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>IHTIC will attract an international audience of senior figures and decision-makers involved in all aspects of hotel and tourism investment in Iran. The conference will focus on hotel development and tourism attraction in Iran. Join us in Tehran and hear from the regions industry experts on the opportunities available in the region, find out what lessons they have learnt about doing business in the country and how they have overcome development and operational challenges. Find out how government is stimulating foreign investment into the country, what incentives and projects are available.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.iranian-conference.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/393727ba-f3b0-4c2f-9cb3-5ed7500feab7.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170207]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170208]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-13T10:22:22.570Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[5th Annual Renewable Energy Finance in Practice Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Austria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Vienna ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The <span></span>5th Annual Renewable Energy Finance in Practice Forum will happen on October 20 in Vienna.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://glceurope.com/5th-annual-renewable-energy-finance-in-practice-forum/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/89cb81c2-aaed-4abc-aa0a-3f1ef3c7bb06.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161019]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161020]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-06T10:35:13.307Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Global Islamic Economic Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/cf120891-45c1-44f4-a332-171e97e1702d.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Global Islamic Economy Summit (GIES) is the region's premier forum on the Islamic economy. It brings together world-class experts in critical industry sectors that span geographic regions and cultural boundaries to directly address the greatest challenges and opportunities in the Islamic economy.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.giesummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/879d016a-9301-44bd-b053-ec0a41bca7b7.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161010]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161011]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-05T07:07:55.033Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Renewable Energy Trade Mission Iran]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Renewable Energy Trade Mission Iran will be held on October 16-20 in Tehran, Iran.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.retrademissioniran.com/conference/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/15ddc510-68f7-47c7-bf2a-6d11ce6ecfd3.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161015]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161019]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-04T14:27:09.684Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Big 5 Dubai]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/79e2d68a-89ef-4ac1-833c-aa90c951625d.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Big 5 will be held on November 21-24 in Dubai, UAE.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://register.thebig5.ae/?utm_campaign=The%20Big%205%20Dubai_The%20Business%20year&utm_medium=web%20banner%20visprom&utm_source=Media%20Partner%20&utm_content=&utm_term=]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5ebc5c70-a1da-4c8e-9ebf-5b6ac0feadf4.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161121]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161124]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-04T10:33:51.723Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Oil & Gas Exhibition & Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Tanzania]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition & Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dar es Salaam ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Oil &amp; Gas Exhibition &amp; Conference will be held on August 16-18 in Dar es Salaam, Tanzania.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.expogr.com/tanzania/oilgas/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/eb0e1c77-d2df-4e1d-8484-f30e9bd09dd1.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170815]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170817]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-04T07:52:33.990Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[9th Edition MENA HR Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 9th Edition MENA HR Summit will be held on October 11-13 in Abu Dhabi, UAE.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://fleming.events/en/events/plan/hr/mena-hr-summit]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/02f86847-2740-4778-96ec-3e3af8cd8344.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161010]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161012]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-04T07:07:04.519Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[18th Global Women in Leadership (WIL) Economic Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 18th Global Women In Leadership (WIL) Economic Forum is bringing together up to 500 global male and female business leaders, policy makers, as well as young female professionals and entrepreneurs. They're gathering to dissect the challenge of diversity, share experiences and produce actionable strategies to strive for women's economic empowerment.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.naseba.com/what-we-do-/leadership-forum/global-wil-economic-forum/?utm_source=partner&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=TheBusinessYear]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f589e95b-d632-4ee5-9a21-4746a1c08317.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161023]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161024]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-03T11:42:34.017Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Project Lebanon]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Lebanon]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Beirut ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Project Lebanon 2017, the 22nd International Trade Exhibition for Construction Materials and Equipment for Lebanon and the Middle East, is the premier event of its kind in the region, bringing together industry leaders from around the world. In its 2016 edition, 456 exhibitors from over 20 countries showcased their latest products and services to 21,678 visitors.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.projectlebanon.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/420803ff-f73f-4cb7-8448-1e48ba746b7b.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170515]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170518]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-10-03T09:02:38.756Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Middle East Banking Forum 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The UAE Banks Federation and The Banker present the fourth Middle East Banking Forum: Transforming the Customer Experience, a half-day event focused on new approaches to banking in a period of immense change. Through presentations, panel sessions and on-stage interviews, senior executives from regional and international banks will be joined by thought leaders and experts to share their experience and perspective of how banks can implement innovative banking strategies. Topics to be discussed include the phenomenon of de-risking, improving the customer experience, mobile banking, cyber security, business resilience, fraud prevention and the impact of financial technology.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://live.ft.com/MEBANKS?reference=thebusinessyear&utm_source=emh&utm_medium=thebusinessyear&utm_campaign=2016pmiddleeastbankingforumme]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e96e3400-53dd-4391-886a-2615dc5edb38.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161114]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161114]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-30T12:08:46.681Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mining Investment Middle East & Central Asia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining Investment Middle East &amp; Central Asia is a strategic mining conference and exhibition for the leaders of the mining, quarrying and construction materials industries, bringing together 250 attendees from 25 countries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mininginvestmentmiddleeast.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/64276343-bdaa-4de5-a641-27f800815f81.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161010]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161012]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-27T12:38:22.854Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Healthcare Investment MENA]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Healthcare Investment MENA serves as the only gathering of the most influential decision makers from investors, healthcare providers, pharmaceuticals and other industry stakeholders; to successfully harness the biggest opportunities in investing and expanding in the dynamic MENA healthcare market.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://healthcareinvestmentmena.com/Forms/BrochureDownload/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/6b19cb6a-9dbd-4da0-b83a-e7176973a7d6.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161023]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161026]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-27T12:05:29.701Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[EGYPS - Egypt Petroleum Show 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>EGYPS 2017 brings together Egyptian and North African government representatives, key project owners, NOCs and IOCs, international service providers, EPC contractors, consultants and financiers to address the evolving opportunities in the Egyptian and North African energy arena.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.egyps.com/about-the-exhibition/book-a-stand/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7111b64a-76fb-4972-8594-b55c48b0eaab.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170214]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170216]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-27T12:02:26.142Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Muslim Leadership Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Since the formation of the Islamic Calendar, the movement of the Muslim people in the form of Hijra, has been a pertinent part of the faith. As the Prophet (SAW) fled persecution from Makkah to Medina, Muslims today face similar issues of Islamophobia, radicalisation, terrorism and war. These issues have meant that every day, many Muslims hope to leave behind the state of injustice and oppression, to move from the fear of their land to hope and reliance upon Allah (SWT). This movement has meant a loss of the collective vision for a united Ummah. In understanding this the World Muslim Leadership Forum (WMLF) observes the need to consolidate leadership amongst the Muslim community in order to affect change within all aspects of life. Nevertheless, the conference also ascertains that Islamic values hold a unique perspective on the governance of the global community, and argues that in understanding Islam's spheres of influence within economics, sustainable development, global values and international institutions, Islamic perspectives can offer innovative solutions to current global crises.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.asli.com.my/?p=upcoming-events/world-muslim-leadership-forum#.V-pfaT596Cl]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/986355cf-9862-4153-9d31-cafdaf260fbb.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161005]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161005]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-26T10:08:25.929Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[RENPOWER IRAN 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>uroconvention Global is delighted to be the organizer of the forthcoming RENPOWER IRAN 2016 - Infrastructure, Power &amp; Renewable Energy Investment Conference in collaboration with Open Iran Group. The event is scheduled for 23-24 October at the Espinas Palace Hotel in Tehran.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.conventionventures.com/events.php?action=details&event_id=123]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/70647ab9-abc0-48e3-a4dc-356e2a5316e6.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161106]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161107]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-26T08:34:20.873Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 10th Oil Trading & Logistics Expo]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/e9697585-4050-46fe-b70d-d281297b71e1.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lagos ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The OTL Africa Downstream Conference will hold from 23 - 26 October 2016 at the Oriental Hotel in Lagos. OTL Africa Downstream Conference 2016 will offer over 2000 delegates, speakers, exhibitors and special guests opportunities for high-level networking, business match-making and learning.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.otlafrica.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2c654baf-977b-4627-bf03-48e4b7a53eef.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161022]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161025]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-26T08:13:15.575Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Outlook Oman]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/a6d040ba-35b0-4c75-b73c-dfc1d51403b5.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With so much going on with the economic reforms in Oman, it has become hard to identify the opportunities created in the $209bn market due to inaccurate information and time. Overcome these challenges at Outlook Oman Forum, being held on October 24, 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://outlookoman.meed.com/learn_more_mp%20?utm_medium=banner&utm_source=BusinessYear&utm_campaign=MediaPartner&utm_term=MDC075_BY_WBBNR&utm_content=LandingPage]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5bc79e8e-7913-4124-ae10-c98949eac21a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161023]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161023]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-23T06:55:13.459Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 1st Iranian Consumer Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 1st Iranian Consumer Summit 2016 will provide a unique opportunity to examine the consumer market in Iran and learn valuable lessons from those already operating and investing there. We will discuss the best ways and models to enter the market, learn how to optimize international financial transactions, evaluate legal and business risks as well as to assess consumer culture. Along with that, the summit will provide practical know-how on more detailed issues surrounding operations, distribution, HR, legal and marketing. The audience will also hear about the process of local Iranian companies' selection for partnering, conducting due diligence and KYC procedures for ensuring long-term reliable and trustful relationships. The summit will provide a networking platform for foreign investors and corporates, both those who only now are looking to enter Iran but also those who already are operating there; as well as local Iranian manufacturing companies, distributers, legal and advisory firms.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.newspartaevents.com/event/iranian-consumer-summit-2016/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/b84e4d0a-b93b-43e1-a5d6-66019e3b2e43.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161123]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161123]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-21T10:35:21.299Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Infra Oman]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Infra Oman - dubbed as one of the largest building and construction expo in the Middle East has been continuously defining the industry's development for the last 5 years. It is considered as the annual meeting place for industry leaders, suppliers and buyers in the Sultanate of Oman. Infra Oman has proved to be an ideal starting point not only for the local companies, but also for foreign entities that are more determined to be part of Oman's growing market.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.infraoman.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e69a541a-76e6-4e1f-ac87-74bef8959f94.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161009]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161011]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-20T08:55:17.418Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Economist Energy Summit 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Join us at the Energy Summit 2016 where the industry's foremost business leaders, policy-makers, international investors, regulators, innovators and academics will gather for a series of hard hitting debates that will determine the future of energy.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/energy-summit-2016?cid1=eve/part/socialmedia/none/thebusinessyear/201609/socialmedia/General-publicity/EM1485/Energy-Summit/none/EMEA/none]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8b915505-125e-4df5-820b-0485c9fccdc5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161110]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161110]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-19T14:42:24.910Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Power Nigeria Exhibition and Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition & Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lagos ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The meeting place of the Power Industry in Nigeria. Here, you will meet with exhibitors from across the globe and witness a broad spectrum of products and technologies over the three days of the exhibition. The conference will bring to light Disco, Government and Finance perspectives, as well as an indepth workshop on the Gas to Power Value Chain.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.power-nigeria.com/en/Forms/Pre-registrationForm/?Prioritycode=THEBUSINESSYEAR&utm_source=THEBUSINESSYEAR&utm_medium=REFERRAL&utm_campaign=Visprom4]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c4606aab-cc78-4f2a-b028-632bdb2f6df2.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160926]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160928]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-16T13:37:24.227Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Islamic Finance News Pakistan Forum 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Pakistan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lahore ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Islamic banking industry in Pakistan has progressed considerably since its introduction to the South Asian nation, with its share reaching almost 12% of the overall banking industry in terms of its asset size. The branch network of Islamic banking is continuously expanding throughout the country at a rapid pace, and the strong demand for Shariah compliant banking products is reflective of the State Bank of Pakistan(SBP)'s goal of having a 20% market share by 2020.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=Pakistan2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2d2fc779-2a94-41b7-90f2-953bf1b4d946.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160925]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160925]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-16T13:27:53.704Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Practical Nigerian Content]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abuja ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 6th Practical Nigerian Content Forum (PNC), taking place from 22-24 November 2016 will be held for the first time in Abuja, Nigeria. This decision has been made following discussions held with the NCDMB, our partners, the Nigerian oil and gas industry and other Government agencies. PNC 2016 will answer key questions and topics raised by key players in Nigeria. The Forum will also include a Showcase Arena and a Site Visit displaying Nigerian Content in action.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.cwcpnc.com/?utm_campaign=media-partner&utm_source=the-business-year&utm_medium=banner. ]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5c74d900-4a82-40e4-9dc9-086825636115.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161122]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161124]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-16T13:25:14.038Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[ Iran Upstream Congress 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Iran's oil and gas sector ranks fifth largest in the world. The easing of sanctions pursuant to the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA) has facilitated Iran's returning to (most) world markets. It's a great opportunity to enter Iran oil gas industry today.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[www.iranupstream.org]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3b238cc7-fc81-4d93-83ad-b4e8bf36387c.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161016]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161017]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-16T13:21:32.341Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[THE WORLD FUTURE ENERGY SUMMIT EXHIBITION 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The World Future Energy Summit (WFES) is the world's most influential event dedicated to advancing renewable energy, energy efficiency and clean technology.  Held each year at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre, World Future Energy Summit (WFES) is hosted by Masdar. In 2016 the World Future Energy Summit (WFES) exhibition and conference brought together 600 companies from 32 countries and more than 30,000 attendees from 150 countries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.worldfutureenergysummit.com/?utm_source=google&utm_medium=homepagebanner&utm_content=visprom&utm_campaign=the%20business%20year]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/df98ffec-f0e5-4336-927f-899e2fdda5d2.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170116]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170119]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-09T11:24:01.442Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Latin American Financial Risk Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Panama]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Panama City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Latin American Financial Risk Summit will be held on September 22-23.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.risksummit2016.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1378b63b-3f24-4e3f-b4bc-75e65e6dc7b0.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160921]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160922]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-01T10:55:07.747Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[9th Infrastructure & Sub-Sovereign Finance in Mexico Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Monterrey ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>LatinFinance will return to Mexico in September for the 9th edition of its Infrastructure and Sub-Sovereign Finance in Mexico Summit – the only event which brings together both Mexican state and municipal government officials with investors, financiers, project sponsors, concessionaries and operators.<br></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.latinfinanceevents.com/events/9th-infrastructure-sub-sovereign-finance-in-mexico-summit/event-summary-a5533488c622438b846b96066a1d1e96.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/cdb01738-23b8-475d-a6c8-a483860de031.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160921]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160922]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-09-01T10:53:35.983Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[10th Andean Finance & Investment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Peru]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lima ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>LatinFinance's Andean Finance &amp; Investment Forum will return to Peru in September for its tenth edition. The region's largest financial markets forum, it will convene: CEOs, CFOs and treasurers from leading Andean corporates; international and local investors and financiers; and top government officials from across the region. Over the course of two days of panel debates, the event will explore the region's changing economic and financial  landscape to identify new opportunities for investment, in financial markets and in strategic sectors, and to cast light on the risks facing this dynamic marketplace.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.latinfinanceevents.com/events/10th-andean-finance-investment-forum/event-summary-9e9833cabd7846fe841c21f004aa6ac8.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4baf9fab-f606-4166-9d12-218006788af3.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160912]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160913]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T13:01:11.166Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[SPE Intelligent Energy 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Aberdeen ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>SPE intelligent Energy is a conference &amp]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.intelligentenergyevent.com/en/register/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/bb4c6dde-037a-4864-bd9e-c762d44389dc.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160905]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160907]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T12:58:56.370Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Kish Invex 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kish ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Kish Invex 2016 is on October 31-November 3.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://kishinvex.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/19df85e6-2571-46c8-a351-5eb2dea4f2a7.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161031]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161103]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T12:54:40.376Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Colombia Startup 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bogota ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Colombia Startup 2016 is on October 7.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.colombia-startup.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/56530805-f28b-4d6b-9fef-8ffdef3837af.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161006]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161006]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T11:31:43.931Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GTR Africa Trade & Infrastructure Finance Conference 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>London will once again play host to the GTR Africa Trade &amp; Infrastructure Finance Conference on October 5-6 2016, bringing together high-level participants from across the trade finance community for topical discussion and unrivalled coverage of the African trade, export, commodity and infrastructure finance markets.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gtreview.com/events/africa/gtr-africa-trade-infrastructure-finance-conference-2016/?utm_source=TBY&utm_medium=Banner%20Link&utm_campaign=GTR%20Africa%20Trade%20%26%20Infrastructure%20Finance%20Conference%202016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f0b56476-0da4-4ddd-b42b-170df81aac86.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161004]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161005]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T11:25:45.648Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Intergas]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > France]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Nice ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Intergas will be held in Nice, France, on November 28-29.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://gassummit.org/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ea8a6533-70da-40c6-a51b-c795f3b2c757.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161128]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161129]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T10:31:35.696Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Engage]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Engage has been developed to bring you the very best global knowledge and tools to either get you off to a flying start or to accelerate your existing activities. With structured training workshops, take-home support material, case studies, inspirational speakers that challenge the status quo and four streams of content taking you over the entire marketing funnel and the strategic thinking behind it, this is one day you don't want to miss.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.engageinbound.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/baceaa35-a88d-44a3-9512-0976fece3fcb.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160918]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160918]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-31T10:29:50.519Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 25th Annual Middle East Petroleum & Gas Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>MPGC 2017 returns to where it was originally launched in 1993, DUBAI, UAE and with ENOC as its hosts. After 25 years, MPGC remains the region's longest running annual oil &amp; gas conference, a trusted brand and a hallmark of excellence in thought leadership. MPGC 2017 will bring together 350 participants from more than 100 global companies of over 50 countries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mpgc.cc/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/6d31e52d-e347-45c8-89d9-10485dd03c74.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170429]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170501]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-25T13:05:16.855Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[West and Central Africa Mining Chapter 2017]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Ivory Coast]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abidjan ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This exclusive event running from 20- 22 March 2017 in Abidjan,Ivory Coast, is the most important mining investment event in the region where key decision makers partake in a very high calibre and relevant engagement around the future of west and central Africa mining industry,while investors are exploring opportunities in mining projects.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://miningresources.co.za/index.php/west-and-central-mining-chapter]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/dd547a90-96bf-4beb-aedc-44b6ad304c36.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170320]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170322]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-25T13:02:51.011Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Southern Africa Mining Chapter 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Mozambique]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Maputo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This exclusive event is the most important mining investment event in the region where key decision makers partake in a very high calibre and relevant engagement around the future of Southern Africa's mining industry, while investors are exploring opportunities in mining projects.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://miningresources.co.za/index.php/47-event]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/53343e3d-c84f-4b89-af7c-cde1e456861f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161024]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161025]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-25T13:00:36.488Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Miners and Investors Exchange Copperbelt Africa 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Zambia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[ Lusaka ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The most senior and influential community of mining executives in Africa. We connect mining executives, and in turn their companies, to each other and to their partners in the finance and investment worlds.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://miningresources.co.za/index.php/124-event]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d2155927-d13d-4c4a-af63-9577326d475e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161116]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161116]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-24T13:31:43.157Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Sustainable Investment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > US]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[New York ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sustainable Investment Forum will be held in New York on September 20.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.sustainableinvestmentforum.org/#register]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/774f7f41-24a4-4a42-a370-0d7c9433699c.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160919]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160919]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-24T13:29:03.502Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Sustainable Innovation Forum 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Morocco]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Marrakech ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Be a part of the largest business-focused event taking place during the annual Conference of Parties (COP22) - the Sustainable Innovation Forum 2016 - taking place on 14-15 November at the Four Seasons Marrakech, Morocco.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.cop22.org/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1c7671f0-2de0-417c-9c90-cfeb12df372f.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161114]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161115]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-24T08:54:39.426Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Complimentary AXENS Technology Seminar]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Euro Petroleum Consultants (EPC) is pleased to welcome oil refining &amp; petrochemicals operators to AXENS complimentary seminar, focused on Delivering Profitable Technologies to Fuel Sustainable Growth – a unique opportunity to hear company experts present and discuss best practices and key aspects of AXENS' most relevant technologies and advanced catalysts to meet current market challenges in Asia.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://europetro.com/en/asia_2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/77b21f62-84bf-4fff-acce-358c337e4ee1.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161009]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161009]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-23T08:41:47.612Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Egypt Oil & Gas Business Meetings 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Egypt Oil &amp; Gas Business Meetings on 14th - 15th  November 2016 in Cairo, featuring a faculty of high-level speakers and exhibitors presenting on key technical and business issues, and welcoming even more future investors who are interested in the country. The event will be a platform for pre-arranged meetings where delegates will network and exchange knowledge.<br></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.egyptsummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/30fa7088-7513-4d6b-a570-c5c7e633666a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161114]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161115]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-19T14:21:36.214Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The CWC World LNG & Gas Series: Asia Pacific Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Singapore]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Spearheaded by an industry-led Steering Committee and featuring the CWC Trading Exchange and the CWC Asia Pacific LNG Innovation Award, CWC is excited to announce its 8th Annual World LNG &amp; Gas Series: Asia Pacific Summit.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://asiapacific.cwclng.com/?utm_campaign=media-partner&utm_source=the-business-year&utm_medium=banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/bdb66025-5d2a-4f00-8968-bbf04d450317.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160919]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160922]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-18T14:25:33.121Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[North Africa Banking Technology 2016 Exhibition]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This two day large-scale conference will shed light on the rapidly advancing North Africa and MENA banking landscape – bringing together the largest banks and the most innovative solutions and technologies shaping the market today.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.northafricabanking.com/#!join/g0ts6]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f36ea215-1d2c-4bb8-9c04-f67e4e9854ba.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161108]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161109]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-18T13:19:40.177Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[​​​Property Progress Report Thailand 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Property Progress Report Thailand 2016 is taking place on October 13 in Bangkok, Thailand.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.asiapropertyawards.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/de43e7da-1631-4f7c-a124-e6c6830d4dc5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160921]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160921]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-18T13:17:24.647Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Property Progress Report Singapore 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/86cdbcc8-f978-45f5-8555-42468897a254.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Singapore]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Property Progress Report Singapore 2016 is taking place on October 13 in Singapore.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.asiapropertyawards.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/28c9eff0-b2c6-41dc-9930-924a3bd747b0.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161123]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161124]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-18T13:15:18.883Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Property Progress Report Indonesia 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/74b472de-672a-44e9-8d74-f97ede2ce403.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Indonesia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jakarta ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Property Progress Report Indonesia 2016 is taking place on October 13 in Jakarta, Indonesia.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.asiapropertyawards.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/58bdb22b-410b-40ba-9537-2871ddb3fe45.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161012]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161012]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-16T15:33:12.935Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Comex]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>27th edition of COMEX will take place from 28th March - 1st April 2017 at newly built Oman Convention and Exhibition Center. It is Oman's premier ICT event which takes place annually. Oman's ICT industry is growing at a steady pace and a lot of cooperation is going on in public and private sector.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.comex.om/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/6a7c6802-8863-4a76-8df3-b8cd0db6b154.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170327]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170331]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-12T14:33:11.424Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[International Islamic Banking Summit Africa]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Djibouti]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Djibouti]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The International Islamic Banking Summit Africa will take place in Djibouti on November 2-3.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.ethicolive.com/events/islamicbankingdjibouti/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d22a8167-520b-4383-87a1-442dbf5a52ab.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161102]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161103]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-12T14:02:38.208Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Africa Renewable Energy Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Morocco]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Marrakech ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In partnership with Global Nexus and the Institute of Research in Solar Energy and New Energies (IRESEN), EnergyNet is pleased to host the Africa Renewable Energy Forum (AREF). The Africa Renewable Energy Forum has been awarded with the official endorsement of COP22 and will be 'the' renewable energy side meeting for AllAfrica to support on-going implementation of the Paris Agreement. This will be the first of an annual cycle of conferences focused specifically on renewable energy for African development to benchmark and maintain the outcomes of the Conference of Parties (COP) for AllAfrica.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.energynet.co.uk/event/africa-renewable-energy-forum?utm_campaign=Media]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8d5c2a0a-ecde-42b9-9065-55562db852f5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161102]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161104]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-12T14:00:55.548Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Powering Africa: Nigeria]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/3c5abb60-c3fc-41f5-96c4-73fa408876c2.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Nigeria]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abuja ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The annual Powering Africa: Nigeria meeting will take place in Abuja on the 12 - 14 October at the Hilton Transcorp. The Forum will be a premium private sector-led and finance focused summit on investment strategies, bringing together Nigeria's electricity supply industry, local finance institutions, IPP and NIPP investors, power developers and international financiers to release capital in Nigeria's transforming power sector.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.energynet.co.uk/event/powering-africa-nigeria-2016?utm_campaign=Media]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1c1dad2c-5772-491c-b354-88560a8b8a5d.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161011]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161013]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-10T08:24:39.129Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GCC Environment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jeddah ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The GCC Environmental and Sustainable Development Forum, GEF, was originally launched in 2010. Since the first edition, GEF has grown in popularity and prestige over the years to assert its position as Saudi Arabia's flagship environmental event.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gccenvironmentforum.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2546faa1-16db-48f0-800f-96e67b38d2c8.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170403]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170405]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-04T10:47:42.880Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Intersolar Middle East Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/99a29ed2-089e-466f-9803-ab8344b8b51a.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Intersolar Middle East takes place 19 - 21 September 2016 at the Dubai World Trade Centre, United Arab Emirates. It is in conjunction with GulfSol, the key event in the Middle East dedicated to the solar industry. The event's exhibition and conference both focus on the areas of photovoltaics, PV production technologies, energy storage systems and solar thermal technologies. Since being founded, Intersolar has become the most important platform for the global solar industry.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.intersolar.ae/en/tickets/registration.html?utm_campaign=MediaPartner&utm_medium=web&utm_source=TheBusinessYear&utm_content=Visprom&utm_term=Website]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5349119b-10d0-4696-968e-cff39abcecf6.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160918]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160920]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-04T08:58:50.797Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[2nd Tanzania Infrastructure & New Energy Investment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Tanzania]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dar es Salaam ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to announce the hosting of the 2nd Tanzania Infrastructure &amp; New Energy Investment Forum which will take place in Dar Es Salaam on the 21st of September 2016. This event will bring together senior participants from across the business, investment and finance community for topical discussions and unrivalled coverage of the Tanzanian infrastructure and renewable energy markets.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.conventionventures.com/events.php?action=details&event_id=118]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/469967b6-c3d7-4d2d-8a5f-2c06fa87b2f3.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160920]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160920]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-03T07:59:08.479Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Cityscape Kuwait 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Kuwait]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuwait City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cityscape Kuwait is the premier international real estate investment event in the State of Kuwait and is a key meeting place for real estate developers, home buyers, private and institutional investors, architects, consultants and other real estate service providers to find investment opportunities, network and do business. Whether you are a large scale real estate developer, broker, a real estate service provider or a private investor, Cityscape Kuwait is your opportunity to access the Kuwaiti and regional real estate and investment community all under one roof.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/2aZsCon]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/42dc292c-5439-4137-85c9-7ac40f6a9e40.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161016]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161019]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-02T14:21:09.227Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Data Center Summit 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Costa Rica]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[San Jose ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Data Center Summit is the first conference in the region on infrastructure and data center standards, which brings together leading experts from organizations such as the Uptime Institute, The Green Grid, ICREA International Data Center Consultants</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.datacentersummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c3a72508-c776-44a7-b4eb-b826fc23402c.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160829]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160829]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-01T14:32:33.082Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[MENA New Age Banking Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/223bdf6e-5ad0-49a7-977b-df04c4289aee.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Qatar]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Doha ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Trying to match the expectations of their 21st century customers, banks worldwide are embracing and adopting the culture of innovation, technology with the banks in the MENA region recently woken up to this fact.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://newagebanking.com/mena/?utm_source=web&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=tby]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0871d606-8a45-44f0-89d1-11ab217fced4.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161003]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161004]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-08-01T11:20:37.645Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The International Economic Forum of the Americas]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Canada]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Toronto ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Toronto Global Forum is an international conference fostering dialogue on national and global issues. It is held under the auspices of the International Economic Forum of the Americas (IEFA). The IEFA organizes annual summits bringing together heads of states, central bank governors, ministers and global economic decision makers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://forum-americas.org/toronto/2016/speakers]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d76c6ed1-d1d1-41bf-a33a-06d63089aff1.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160911]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160913]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-28T13:04:41.936Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mexico Trade & Export Finance Conference 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>GTR is delighted to return to Mexico City on October 20 for the Mexico Trade &amp]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gtreview.com/events/americas/mexico-trade-export-finance-conference-2016/?utm_source=TBY&utm_medium=Banner%20Link&utm_campaign=Mexico%20Trade%20%26%20Export%20Finance%20Conference%202016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0f30a3a9-6e7c-4edd-8e2d-dd09fad96b88.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161019]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161019]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-28T11:03:41.713Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Retail Congress Asia Pacific]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Against a back-drop of change in mature economies, rapid retail evolution in developing markets and dynamic opportunities in the fast-growing emerging markets, the 2016 Congress will bring together over 350 senior members of the retail community throughout the region and across the globe.  Join us for exclusive insights into growth market opportunities in Asia Pacific, how to become more customer centric, staying ahead of the ever-evolving retail market and more.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.retailcongressasia.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d26c0afa-8ba8-4724-97f2-392b6b7d4fd8.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161011]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161012]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-26T10:17:24.704Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[THAI-UK 2016 – Celebrating 70 Years of Thai-UK Partnership]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Thailand and the United Kingdom have shared a history of close friendship and partnership for more than 400 years beginning with the early trading routes of the late 1500's. Today, examples of Thai-UK partnership stretch across all facets of business, education, culture and philanthropy. As a major partner and investor, the UK continues to play a significant role in the Thai economy and 'Thai-UK 2016' is a celebration of this partnership and a landmark for future co-operation.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://thai-uk2016.com/thai_uk/2016/en/index.asp]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d7109494-b9a1-4716-a9e1-73c5a0aaf96b.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160906]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160909]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-25T14:09:13.903Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[National Treasure]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/3e65e8e2-73d5-411d-827a-c7ea84e7c4ab.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>National Treasure is the region's most anticipated gathering of leaders shaping the future of UAE, hosted under the patronage of Dubai Chamber of Commerce &amp; Industry and in partnership with Tejar Dubai. Our mission is to help organisations and individuals improve their quality of life by leveraging on merits of credibility to drive high performance. The goal of National Treasure Initiative is to shift the focus from idea generation to idea execution through road tested insights and actionable talks from the region's most pragmatic leaders and visionaries. The program explores new possibilities by allowing us to transcend our ordinary experiences and limitations that would propel a person from apathy to possibility, and transform the way we perceive our own capabilities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://nationaltreasure.ae/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7730ea78-46f6-4d31-ac71-5399677fccbc.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160926]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160927]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-25T11:50:06.192Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Petroleum Conference Iran 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Petroleum Conference – Iran 2016 is the voice of Iran's petroleum industry private sector, which for the first time has united all the major oil &amp; gas industry associations in Iran.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.petroconfex.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5b0e2ef7-87aa-4131-8a81-15a9a3047294.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160930]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161002]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-25T09:05:46.394Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Certx]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Riyadh ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia gearing towards a knowledge based future society, and the aim to empower its people, it is slowly transforming itself into a knowledge-led economy. The aim of this exhibition and conference is to bring together international certification bodies under one roof, to showcase their services to business education and training institutes and organisations who are looking to enhance the skills and knowledge of their workforce.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://leeaint.com/uk/Events-CERTX-18---20-April-2107]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1368368e-54d5-4a71-a667-da173255ef23.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170417]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170419]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-25T09:00:36.151Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Big 5 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Big 5 is an annual meeting place for the international building &amp; construction community in Dubai. Presently running in its 37th year, the international exhibition and conference brings together buyers and sellers together from all over the world to conduct business, forge relationships and exchange knowledge. Scheduled for 21 – 24 November, the event will take place at Dubai World Trade Centre, Dubai.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/2aKEgot]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/aafeb163-8f0d-4ad7-8e44-5dcaaf5d31db.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161121]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161124]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-25T08:57:51.402Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Big 5 Construct East Africa]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Kenya]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Nairobi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Part of the largest portfolio of international construction events of the Middle East and Africa, dmg events is bringing its expertise to the emerging market in East Africa.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/2dP1xrQ]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/da6a035b-9d5c-4949-9f1e-7a2c9883efe5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161102]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161104]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-22T11:28:33.259Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Big 5 Construct Indonesia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/ffae81b7-0b49-4d00-9916-6023cc8c1972.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Indonesia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jakarta ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>After delivering a successful launch event in 2015, The Big 5 Construct Indonesia is committed to building upon its success. Furthermore, we are pleased to announce for 2016, the collocation of The Big 5 Construct Indonesia and Konstruksi Indonesia, in conjunction with Indonesia Infrastructure Week, the country's leading event for the infrastructure industry, collectively forming Indonesia's largest construction event. The event will reflect the growth and demand within the industry as the government's expenditure on construction projects continues to increase rapidly, estimated to reach $550 Billion by 2019. Taking place from 9 – 11 November 2016, the event will be held at Jakarta Convention Centre, Jakarta Indonesia.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebig5constructindonesia.com/?utm_campaign=The%20Big%205%20Indonesia_The%20Business%20year&utm_medium=web%20banner&utm_source=Media%20Partner%20&utm_content=&utm_term=]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3c13e6fa-1f45-46bd-97e7-ef3f4bc1146d.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161109]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161111]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-21T10:00:03.200Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[2nd Mines & Mining Industries Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Iran welcomes the world's leading finance, engineering and mining businesses to explore the country's untapped $700bn mining industry at the 2nd Mines &amp; Mining Industries Summit on December 10-11, 2016 in Tehran-Iran.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.iicic.com/imis2016/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/830bf03b-d982-4dad-9385-63e4ee9c584d.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161210]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161211]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-19T08:28:05.647Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[PANGKOR DIALOGUE 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Ipoh, Perak ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Pangkor Dialogue 2016 will explore challenges and what it takes to build a resilient society, as well as the connections with an inclusive and sustainable future.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.pangkordialogue.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ce7ae1a1-b6ff-418d-aea8-30cf3991c9c5.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160904]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160906]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-14T14:24:16.335Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Plant maintenance & Reliability Optimization Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Plant Maintenance and Reliability Optimization Forum (PMRO) will serve as a platform for the organizations from multiple industries such as Oil &amp; Gas, Petrochemicals, Plastics &amp; Polymers, Chemicals, Utilities and others to achieve these goals. PMRO goes beyond just presenting case studies, it presents technologies, strategies and structural changes that can be implemented for visible improvement.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[www.pmroforum.com]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ce2bfc08-a3c5-420f-b135-e183927982b1.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161003]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161004]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-14T14:15:28.183Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Arab Future Cities Summit Dubai 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/fae85603-446a-4499-ae44-e73a7eb917ff.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 3rd Annual Arab Future Cities Summit 2016 will be held on 8th and 9th November at the iconic Palazzo Versace, Dubai. Ranked as one of the most innovative cities in the world and set to become the 'smartest' city, the Dubai Government has identified six key components - transport, communications, infrastructure, electricity, economic services and urban planning that are integral to smart city development.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://linktrack.info/.1xa7s]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4d62e5ac-25b3-4323-9a61-66a6ab1e7495.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161108]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161109]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-14T06:50:50.483Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mexico Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><strong></strong>This September, join editors of The Economist and more than 200 leading business executives and thinkers to navigate the disruptive forces impacting Mexico's business climate for the year ahead.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.economist.com/events-conferences/americas/mexico?fsrc=events|TBY15#ec-event-overview]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ae54e1c8-88f1-4ff5-84ef-33144156ea7f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160907]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160907]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-14T06:23:35.455Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Power & Electricity World Africa]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > South Africa]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition & Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Johannesburg ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Beginning in 1997, Power &amp; Electricity World Africa started as a small conference. It is now both a conference and an exhibtion and takes up 4 massive halls in Johannesburg, Sandton Convention Centre. Now in it's 20th year, it has grown to become Africa's most successful and well attended power and electricity conference and exhibition.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.terrapinn.com/exhibition/power-electricity-world-africa/?utm_source=The%20Business%20Year%20&utm_medium=OP&utm_content=Banner&utm_campaign=The%20Business%20Year-%20OP%20]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/964bff2f-baa9-4f07-9f81-35812161397f.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170327]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170328]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-12T10:44:27.380Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Cityscape Global 2016 ]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/9e5c564e-8ffd-4cee-b58d-1cc07ab85927.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Returning to the Dubai World Trade Centre from 6-8 September, Cityscape Global is expected to span across 41,000sqm of exhibition space, featuring new exhibitors showcasing hundreds of project launches.  Cityscape Global is recognised as the annual barometer for the real estate industry in emerging markets and is one of the largest and most influential real estate events held globally. The event supports real estate growth worldwide to an international audience, highlighting iconic architecture, significant developments and unparalleled investment opportunities. For more than fifteen years, Cityscape Global has been the bridge between emerging and mature real estate markets bringing together investors and professionals from Asia, Middle East, Africa, Russia and the Indian subcontinent with those from Europe and the US. With over 43,000 participants expected, Cityscape is the annual opportunity to build and maintain your presence across emerging real estate markets.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/29eVhrR]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/308366e2-772e-4399-830b-b82f58f3040e.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160905]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160907]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-11T13:52:05.911Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Africa Renewable Energy Leaders’ Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Kenya]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Nairobi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>ARELS is a networking community for the East Africa Renewable Energy professionals. It provides a unique platform for policy makers, governmental organisations, investors and technology leaders to advance the renewable energy market in East Africa.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.africarenewablesummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/421e229a-76fd-489b-8c92-f044453db95b.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161102]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161103]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-11T08:47:05.086Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Sustainability Congress]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>World Sustainability is a Not-For-Profit Organization advocating for Sustainable Leadership. World Sustainability attempts to bring Organizations, NGO's, Public Interests Groups and Governmental Bodies, to accelerate and educate on sustainable business practices and solutions for a better tomorrow.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.worldsustainabilitycongress.org/#home]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e4788376-22df-4408-ad5f-01a1ebd88ebd.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161004]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161005]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-05T12:51:40.576Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Big 5 Kuwait]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/f1da80d1-0eee-49bb-93d9-1892ee7b8e17.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Kuwait]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuwait City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Building on the success of  our previous editions, the event provides an excellent and essential opportunity for professionals from across the construction industry to: source and compare the latest products and technologies; network and develop their learning; and introduces some exciting new features to The Big 5 Kuwait.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/2ad2Co5]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ad22488b-be2a-486b-b99b-a2a67e7f03f3.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160924]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160926]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-07-01T11:11:27.052Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[23rd World Energy Congress]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The World Energy Congress, being World Energy Council's global flagship event is the premier international, multi-energy forum for participants to better understand energy issues and solutions from a global perspective. This time Istanbul is hosting the leaders who will build the future of energy from today. The 23rd World Energy Congress will enable dialogue among Energy Ministers and leaders from business, finance and academia around the world who will seek options for delivering sustainable energy systems on national, regional and global levels. The congress and exhibition will bring together more than 10.000 top world leaders in the field of energy.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.wec2016istanbul.org.tr/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/266cb5dd-7ec3-413a-86ae-9fe5156c548c.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161008]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161012]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-29T14:51:15.906Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GSF 2016: Gulf Safety Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Qatar]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Doha ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Euro Petroleum Consultants [EPC] is delighted to announce the Gulf Safety Forum that will take place under the patronage of H.E. Sheikh Abdullah bin Nasser bin Khalifa Al Thani, Prime Minister and Minister of Interior of the State of Qatar. Jointly organised by EPC and the Gulf Organization for Industrial Consulting [GOIC], the Gulf Safety Forum will bring together key industry players from across the Middle East to discuss strategies for continuous improvement of safety procedures as well as share successful case studies and roadmaps towards achieving the goal of zero accidents. International safety experts and providers of safety tools and technologies will also present the latest methodologies which can assist companies to achieve these goals.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://europetro.com/en/gsf2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3fff6df4-cf68-418c-89a3-740d0243144c.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161029]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161031]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-29T14:49:55.920Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[ASIA-TECH: Asia Downstream Technology Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Euro Petroleum Consultants [EPC] is proud to announce that Thailand's largest and Asia's leading integrated petrochemical &amp]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://europetro.com/en/asia_2016 ]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5d603970-dda2-4c6e-9fa1-5c189920aaf3.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161010]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161011]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-29T14:46:02.519Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[OpEx MENA 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In today's challenging economic environment it is more important than ever for companies to focus on improving their operations to increase margins. In refinery and petrochemical complexes in particular there are many opportunities to improve efficiency of operations. OpEx MENA will bring together major operators in the region with the leading suppliers of technology, systems providers and consultants to exchange ideas and experiences on the important topic of operational excellence. As usual the event format is structured to encourage networking and open discussion. It is this spirit of knowledge sharing that will drive the industry to even greater levels of operational excellence improvements, allowing companies to innovate in the areas of 'people', 'process', 'assets' and 'technology'.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.europetro.com/en/opex_mena16]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ffc2981b-2cd6-4eb1-87a6-857c899e2461.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161206]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-29T13:55:43.203Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[6th PPPs in Emerging Markets]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The conference series gives access to emerging markets from across Africa, Americas, Asia Pacific, Europe &amp; the Middle East for a programme of capacity building and networking with Infrastructure &amp; Project Finance leaders across government agencies, investors, project sponsors, EPC's and consultants. The programmes are interactive and based around panel discussions with Case Studies sharing expertise from global thought leaders. The content is developed specifically to cover key issues in developing countries for attracting investment in critical infrastructure, developing best practice and understanding risks and rewards for major essential projects. Combined with a business matchmaking programme the PPP 6.0 edition allows all parties to arrange meetings during the event allowing you to plan your visit and connections in advance and maximise your networking capabilities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.kwppp.com/register-pay.html]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2f37dd8b-212a-4e7f-bf72-613d24d0b9d4.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160710]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160712]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-22T13:10:11.204Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[4th Iran Europe Oil & Gas Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Germany]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Berlin ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 4th Iran Europe Oil &amp; Gas Summit, brings together European technology and expertise with the vast potential and opportunity of the reinvigorated Iranian oil &amp; gas sector. IRN will build on the experience of the three previous events and bring together a faculty of high-level speakers who will present on key technical and business issues and welcome investors who are interested in the country's hydrocarbon industry.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.iransummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2aebe02e-d01c-497d-9b77-3c7f90a89130.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161101]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161103]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-22T13:09:00.634Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Global ESG Investment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Global ESG Investment Forum brings together a multi-stakeholder approach to examine the challenges and issues that investors and the other stakeholders are facing in the current global economic arena and within the ESG sphere.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.esginvestmentforum.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2c2e6dd7-b98b-4a34-8bf2-76936a71d28a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161025]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161026]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-22T08:20:40.633Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Asian Downstream Week]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/3d680a46-e2bb-4d40-97ac-21a3d8c58b0b.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Singapore]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>At this year's Asian Downstream Week, connect with40 Exhibitors, 600 Attendees and 80 Speakers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.downstream-asia.com/?utm_source=TheBusinessYear&utm_medium=Banner&utm_campaign=Delsprom]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4965622c-5ea6-40ad-a5f5-2e3dc7fe53d5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161025]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161026]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-21T07:38:34.782Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[6th LatAm Power Generation Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Chile]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Santiago ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Besides analyzing shifting energy policies and regulations across the region, theBNamericas 6th LatAm Power Generation Summit will focus on the ample business opportunities in the sector, such as the new political reality in Argentina, where subsidies and rate controls are being lifted; the changes that continue to come about as a result of Mexico's landmark energy reform; and Chile's electric power thirst and its growing bet on renewables.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://events.bnamericas.com/bnamericas_events/6latampowersummit/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7fad1668-07a3-4986-86a6-72c7e18a42de.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160809]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160810]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-14T10:29:32.942Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Expo Café Latam Costa Rica 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Costa Rica]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Costa Rica]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>During July 9th and 10th, 2016, Costa Rica will host at the Centro de Eventos Pedregal, the Expo Café LATAM – Costa Rica, with the main goal to arrange spaces that will allow all the participants in the chain of processing coffee to meet face to face, in an international event that strives to integrate the different national and international traders related to this great product through exchange of knowledge, information and establishing networking.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.expo.cafe/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ae83c1cf-d2a9-4537-93ea-513ec298782a.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160708]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160709]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-09T12:53:37.373Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[23rd Anniversary Africa Oil Week]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/b30fb8a5-bbde-447a-b848-33c116f71106.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > South Africa]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cape Town ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><br></p><p>Global Pacific &amp; Partners, with ITE Group, will host the 23rd Africa Oil Week/Africa Upstream 2016 Conference over 31st October-4th November 2016, at the Cape Town International Convention Centre, South Africa.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://aow.globalpacificpartners.com/events/?fa=overview&id=966]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0defd705-f7ab-42e6-bc64-94f7ddb5c054.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161031]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161104]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-09T09:41:08.216Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Asia Pacific Smart Cities Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/82e012e7-965a-4cb0-8255-2be5f2c43499.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With a predicted 62 mega-cities by 2025, up from the current 32, Asia has no choice but to figure out the best way to use technology to help their citizens live better lives. Get the insights on the smart cities movement at the Asia Pacific Smart Cities Forum.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://goo.gl/ByItxf]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4285adb5-442d-4965-aa29-5aee4b8ec9db.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160926]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160927]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-09T09:39:36.936Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IACSP ASEAN Security Symposium & Awards]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Exclusive regional and international speakers from security institutions, intelligence services and government bodies in the field of Counter-Terrorism and Homeland Security. The first IACSP Security Awards and Gala Dinner in the ASEAN Region. Dedicated half day Workshops on the most advanced and pertinent topics in modern Counter-Terrorism such as Countering Improvised Explosive Devices (CIEDs) that has become the weapon of choice of adversaries and Behavioral Identification Methods in the aviation security to help detect potential adversaries.<span></span></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://goo.gl/8VZmhc]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a8730b17-975e-400e-a83b-f20a65296424.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160905]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160906]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-09T09:37:42.646Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Renewable Energy Project Financing Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Get insights into how the new green technology financing scheme (2015 -2017) can grow the industry. Understand about the latest and most innovative financing models in RE projects. Develop the latest strategies to mitigate against risk in new projects. Create successful bankable projects with insights on new financing structures and business models.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://fleming.events/en/events/partners/energy/renewable-energy-project-financing-forum]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7a35f1f6-3c52-4975-9461-6c6c398bb333.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160725]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160726]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-08T11:36:58.252Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[ASQ MEA 2nd Regional Quality Conference 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 2nd ASQ MEA Regional Quality Conference 2016 will help align quality professionals with the regional need of " Innovation and Best Practices in Quality". It will be a forum for ideas and international network of thought leaders, experts and peers who are eager to share their best practices, tested solutions and proven results. At the conference, delegates can demonstrate commitment to quality, be preview to some expert advice, benchmark the levels of quality, network and enhance their career development.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.asqmeaconference.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/02b2940a-14d9-4ae5-87e3-e1a25ac5e8b6.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161018]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161019]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-07T14:50:47.240Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Angola Infrastructure & Renewable Energy Investment Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Angola]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition & Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Luanda ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Euroconvention Global is hosting the Angola Infrastructure &amp; New Energy Investment Conference in Luanda on 12 and 13 July 2016, bringing together senior participants from across the business, investment and finance community for topical discussions and unrivalled coverage of the Angola infrastructure and renewable energy markets. The event will offer timely updates on the country potential in these sectors through presentations and Q&amp;A. Dedicated networking moments will be held throughout the two days allowing delegates the chance to meet and to initiate business development as well.<span></span></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.conventionventures.com/events.php?action=details&event_id=114]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/72e7298c-e1de-49aa-add2-9e49b9134c1e.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160711]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160712]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-07T13:38:21.914Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Brand Congress]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Congress would be a meeting place for leaders from every sector and continent. Join over 500 of the world's branding and marketing elite under one roof. Hear top executives from the World's biggest brands and most influential marketing organizations answering today's critical business challenges. Experience the power of Brand-Building and Rapid-fire Ideas On Marketing to reach out to the consumer at the World Brand Congress 2015.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.worldbrandcongress.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ea000968-52cd-40dc-9ae4-68a73671faaa.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161004]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161005]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-07T07:54:28.523Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The MEBAA Show]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>MEBAA Show is the Middle East's leading business aviation exhibition and a must-attend event for companies across the entire industry. Exhibiting at the MEBAA Show provides the ideal platform to reach key business contacts and build relationships.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mebaa.aero/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/63f6a466-7fb5-4b79-95f1-96d5b23db273.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161206]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161208]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-07T07:20:42.784Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Expo Invest]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Panama]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Panama City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>An event aimed at companies seeking business juncture. Whether these are investments in public sector or in the diversified and competitive market for the private enterprise. These parameters for current and future developments in commercial, tourism and service areas will be established here for the financial, industrial and technological business, and also set the place for people looking for bargains on private investment, retirement, second home or to study abroad.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.expoinvestpanama.com/home.html]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/80f86453-b616-4e7b-8266-fc1fdceed2e0.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160608]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160610]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-03T07:28:31.597Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[5th Annual Peru Investors Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Peru]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Lima ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Peru Investors Forum provides Peruvian pension funds, family offices, private banks, insurance companies and sovereign wealth funds with a platform to exchange views with the global asset management industry. Delegates discuss and uncover trends and opportunities in global alternatives including hedge funds, private equity and real assets, as well as newfound opportunities and portfolio construction in equities, fixed income and ETFs. Available to 12 asset managers and financial service providers through sponsorship only, the meeting provides an intimate platform to access the most active institutional investors in Peru.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.marketsgroup.org/forums/peruvian-investors-forum-2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5e9ed419-5fea-499d-b8ec-423707209c1e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160615]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160615]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-02T13:37:04.074Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 22nd World Petroleum Congress]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>THE WORLD PETROLEUM CONGRESS (WPC), also known as the "Olympics" of the petroleum industry, covers all aspects of the oil and gas industry from technological advances in upstream and downstream operations to the role of natural gas and renewables, management of the industry and its social, economic and environmental impact. Companies, governments, other industry sectors, NGOs and international institutions will join in the dialogue.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.22wpc.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4682fe59-a43f-423a-80af-21cda23a93aa.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170708]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170712]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-06-01T06:39:32.586Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[West Africa Real Estate Investor Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Africa's rapidly growing property markets are attracting increased interest from international investors, developers and occupiers. It is a particularly lucrative and profitable sector across West African countries from Nigeria to Senegal and everything in between. Chinese investors' involvement in large-scale development and infrastructure projects across Africa has been particularly eye-catching. The West Arica Real Estate Investor Forum will bring together business owners and investors with the advisory community to explore opportunities in this high-growth market. This forum provides a platform for investors, lenders and developers to hear the latest insights on the key challenges and opportunities in West African real estate.<br></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://acecorporateevents.co.uk/index.php/west-africa/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7d98f53c-62c6-4f92-a02c-8cf32a0dd42f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160922]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160922]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-30T08:55:10.972Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Airport Modernization Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Riyadh ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Kingdom's aviation sector is set to play a significant role in the government's economic diversification efforts and the Saudi government has already earmarked $10.65 billion (SAR 39.4 billion) to build and upgrade more than 20 airports to help accommodate its fast growing aviation industry. With the successful launch of the Prince Mohammed bin Abdulaziz International Airport in Madinah, the first airport in Saudi Arabia to be constructed and operated entirely by the private sector following a Build-Transfer-Operate (BTO) Agreement, the regulators have announced the plans to privatize airports as a means to support Kingdom's finances. This will allow foreign companies to invest in the Saudi Arabian airports without the need for local partners. The Saudi Arabian Airports see an annual increase of more than 10% of passengers and 5% of aircraft operations. 70% of goods bound to the Middle-East are destined for Saudi Arabia and the government is focused to increase its cargo handling capacity to circumvent the need for shipments to transship through neighbouring GCC countries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://nispana.com/ams/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e02f2d1a-1554-4fca-9aef-c1085f85aa45.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161011]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161012]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-26T08:35:48.032Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Iran Hotel Expansion & Development Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Iran Hotel Expansion &amp; Development Summit will bring together local and international hotel stakeholders; hotel chains, investors, developers, architects and construction companies as well as hospitality institutions, government officials, finance institutes, consultants and technology providers to discuss new developments and ways to realize the potential hotel projects in the Islamic Republic of Iran.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://iran.hotelandresortsummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/834f48dd-1033-40a7-b855-c04c3d195054.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161108]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161109]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-25T06:47:42.937Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Sharjah FDI Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Sharjah ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This key event, organised in partnership with the Sharjah Investment and Development Authority - (Shurooq), and under the patronage of His Highness Sheikh Dr. Sultan bin Muhammed Al Qasimi, Member of Supreme Council, Ruler of Sharjah, provides an unrivalled opportunity to examine the outlook for investment in the U.A.E. and in Sharjah, and the opportunities available to your business. The programme will feature a combination of keynote addresses and lively panel debates from international business leaders and high level policy makers, all keen to share their knowledge and experience.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://live.ft.com/Events/2016/Sharjah-FDI-Forum?reference=businessyear&utm_source=par&utm_medium=businessyear&utm_campaign=2016psharjahfdiforumuae]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7dbfe6f3-1864-4330-8df3-c1710f31126f.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160927]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160928]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-20T14:05:59.900Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Astana Economic Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Kazakhstan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Astana ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Astana Economic Forum is an annual event held in Astana, the capital of the Republic of Kazakhstan, which brings together representatives from the world's economic community, current and former heads of states, Nobel Prize laureates, outstanding figures from the scientific world, and businessmen.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://forum-astana.org/en]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7520d778-ac63-48ec-8a0a-b4f3544ce024.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160524]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160525]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-20T08:55:46.461Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Project Lebanon 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Lebanon]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Beirut ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Project Lebanon 2016, The 21st international trade exhibition for construction material &amp; equipment for Lebanon &amp; the Middle East is the premier event of its kind in the region bringing together industry leaders from around the world. In the 2015 edition, 487 exhibiting companies from over 20 countries showcased their latest products &amp; services to more than 20,000 visitors.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.projectlebanon.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0a4c13c1-f05a-449f-a37d-7e74a24b3749.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160530]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160602]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-20T08:21:16.282Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[WAMPEX 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Ghana]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Accra ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>After 22 years WAMPEX has become a major forum for the international mining and power industries, which attracts visitors and exhibitors to Ghana from across the world. Meet suppliers and discover the new technologies that can help you revolutionise the way you do business. This year WAMPEX looks at latest developments and challenges in power, energy and mining, new technology, cost efficient production, renewable energy, latest products and solutions, and provides a unmatched opportunity to network and share insight and experiences with other key industry personnel. Remember to secure your seat at - WAMPOC 2016 - the 12th West African Mining &amp; Power Conference which runs within Wampex across the full three days of the event and features senior industry speakers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://register.wampexghana.com/events/event_main.asp?id=13&e=WAMPEX2016&utm_campaign=VisReg&utm_medium=SocMed&utm_source=MPTBY&utm_content=&utm_term=]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/766a0fd9-9c87-4152-9bd5-e4796636630c.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160531]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160602]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-18T14:34:54.537Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GITEX Technology Week]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/359ae840-f00e-4790-bf1d-959acec836a6.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead of the latest innovations from across the world of technology with all the most important lessons you need to learn in one easy to access place.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gitex.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/fb4064e5-6724-4347-ab33-07e9b1acd51f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161015]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161019]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-18T07:27:30.099Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Heavy Oil Congress 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Canada]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Calgary ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its launch in 2006, World Heavy Oil Congress has grown into the globe's largest gathering of heavy oil professionals. The comprehensive conference program features technical and business sessions from industry experts and examines the challenges and opportunities facing the heavy oil sector. Numerous elite networking events allow for the fostering of valuable relationships within the community. Join us at the most opportune platform to explore the latest advancements making heavy oil reserves profitable in the global marketplace.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://worldheavyoilcongress.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/415c80d5-068b-4355-ad21-1357cfd26a56.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160905]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160908]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-17T14:24:26.142Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Retail Banking & FinTech Africa Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > South Africa]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Johannesburg ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>With a history of 7 successful annuals, 8th Retail Banking &amp; FinTech Africa Forum aims to provide a platform for the leading banking experts to discuss and analyze the future of retail banking and FinTech in Africa. Through regional case-studies, interactive panel discussions and presentations on trending topics, the event will focus on strategies for the region's retail banking industry. Experts participating at the event will include senior representatives from leading banking and financial organizations in the region. Call us on +971 4609 1570 or email at mohor.mukherjee@fleming.events to request conference agenda featuring complete speaker panel, minute-by-minute sessions and list of all participating companies.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://fleming.events/en/events/partners/finance/retail-banking-fintech-africa-forum]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/89d76fff-1a03-4a4c-8590-d83e9919a8de.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160927]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160928]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-17T14:23:21.362Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[North Africa Future Banking Forum 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>North Africa Future Banking Forum 2016, rotating around the central theme of “Innovation for 21st century banking”, aims to address the latest innovations, trends and challenges for this emerging market. CISOs, CTOs, COOs, CISOs, Directors, Department Heads and other decision makers will join the event to provide a holistic approach on identifying channels and opportunity to transform the region's banking sector in to a more advanced, competitive and futuristic one through experienced knowledge sharing sessions on: Call us on +971 4609 1570 or email at mohor.mukherjee@fleming.events to request conference agenda featuring complete speaker panel, minute-by-minute sessions and list of all participating companies.<span></span></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://fleming.events/en/events/partners/finance/north-africa-future-banking-forum]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1b2869df-8ac4-497a-9d32-9114dd4d0e8e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161023]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161024]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-13T11:54:11.629Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[2nd International LNG Congress]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/2b69f635-59c7-4b40-ba55-92cd20277938.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Germany]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Hamburg ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>2nd International LNG congress is the brand new platform for sharing experiences and networking. The latest trends and technologies, new visions and hot discussions, key topics and future projects are presented on the congress. World leading companies' top management and key specialists attend the event to find new partners and to discuss the current projects. Welcome to the new era of communication!</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://lngcongress.com/?utm_source=pr&utm_medium=mediapartner&utm_campaign=TBY]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8a0f5f75-7f59-4b19-b977-a047e13766a4.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161128]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161129]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-13T11:29:13.550Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 3rd Annual Egypt Power Infrastructure & New Energy Investment Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 3rd Annual Egypt Power Infrastructure &amp; New Energy Investment Forum is scheduled to take place in Cairo on May 31 and June 1, 2016. It will gather project developers, IFIs, government representatives, engineering, consulting, banking and legal entities to discuss further private investments into Egypt renewable energy sector. Participants will review the impact for the RE market of some of the government strategic shift and explore the huge potential in the sector. Business development and networking opportunities will be at center focus during this 2-day event.<span></span></p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.conventionventures.com/events.php?action=details&event_id=116]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ed14f1d9-c3d2-40dd-a554-e1cf297e2455.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160530]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160531]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-13T08:55:09.446Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[WTM London 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>World Travel Market is the leading global event for the travel industry to meet industry professionals and conduct business deals. Through its industry networks, unrivalled global reach, WTM creates personal and business opportunities, providing customers with quality contacts, content and communities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.wtmlondon.com/registration/?utm_campaign=online-media-partner-visit-2016&utm_medium=media-partner&utm_source=the-business-year&utm_audience=visitors&utm_content=banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4051ce57-d8b9-459c-9bea-630e4bca92b4.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161107]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161109]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-11T14:37:38.098Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Global Corporate Reputation, Crisis Communications & Public Acceptance Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Ghana]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Accra ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This conference will benefit all sectors and industries who engage in international business transactions, have business operations in overseas locations or who market their goods or services internationally whether in one location or many locations.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://accrasummit.com/index.html]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e964b855-9ecd-4dd9-8a23-611bd9a21e2a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160816]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160817]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-10T12:15:19.747Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Gas Africa 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > South Africa]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Sandton ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This popular and highly informative event will feature a new format program with top speakers for all across Africa. We have once again started to assemble a panel of speakers who will provide you with insight, perspective and an opportunity of being one step ahead of the industry.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://ingadaevents.co.za/current/gas-africa-16]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2a1cbaf6-16ee-4186-8e7b-70acad07ae49.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160530]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160531]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-09T10:29:00.551Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GCC Power 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Qatar]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Doha ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Managed by GCC CIGRE, The 12th GCC – CIGRE International Conference and 21st Exhibition for Electrical Equipment , GCC POWER 2016 Conference &amp; Exhibition, will be held inSheraton Hotel – Doha, State of Qatar from 8th to 10th November 2016. In addition, Tutorials will be held on 7th of November 2016. This event gives participants the opportunity to learn about the latest developments in the electricity and energy industry, as well as providing exhibitors with access to the most lucrative deals.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://cigre-gccpower.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/add08a85-b822-44ca-a535-d132865d3631.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161108]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161110]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-09T09:29:53.163Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Islamic Treasury Products]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Treasury products offer end users a range of opportunities to hedge, speculate or manage risk exposure, and Shariah compliant equivalents of conventional products are no different. The structure, use and application of Islamic treasury products are, however, governed by very important rules and conventions. With Shariah compliant treasury and hedging products becoming more widespread by financial institutions for both risk hedging and for structuring client investment solutions, these rules and conventions are crucial to the development of these products.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=IslamicTreasuryProducts]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/10075bf0-8397-406a-b3e1-c61d87b436c5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160601]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160601]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-09T09:28:19.238Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Retail Banking Summit in Lebanon]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Lebanon]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Beirut ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In its second year after the successful first run in 2015, Retail Banking Summit in Lebanon will bring together key decision makers in the retail banking industry in the country and from across the region to debate and identify the most pressing challenges to be faced by the banks in the areas of digitisation, retail payments, distribution of financial services and issues related to compliance and credit risk.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.efma.com/index.php/events/conferences/overview/EN/2/513/1-1U9EXV]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/71e1ce92-44f8-4e01-9d36-bbb36e885edc.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160725]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160725]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-06T08:55:54.377Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 7th Muslim World Biz 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>After six years of impressive success, OIC International Business Centre (OICIBC) officially started the preparation for the 7th Muslim World BIZ. The leading trade event, which consists of a number of unique conferences as well as a huge exhibition zone, is organized annually by OICIBC in collaboration with the Islamic Centre for Development of Trade (ICDT). The main objective of the Muslim World BIZ as stated by the founder, the late Dato' Dr Raja Mohamad Abdullah, is to connect businesses from around the Muslim world and enhance inter-trade activities among them as the first step towards effectively introducing the Islamic economy on global platforms.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://2016.muslimworldbiz.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/715c297b-c76a-4ee1-96cf-2f7268b13c11.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161017]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160521]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-05T10:24:35.723Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Saudi Arabia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jeddah ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Saudi Arabia is one of the most active and influential markets in the Islamic finance space today and certainly the biggest in the Gulf. With landmark steps including the opening of Tadawul to foreign investors, the potential for access to the Saudi debt market, expectations of a sovereign Sukuk issuance and booming asset classes including IPOs, real estate and project finance, more and more issuers are coming to market and the overall investment scene is growing dramatically. Our exclusive access to the movers and shakers who matter make IFN Saudi Arabia the essential event for anyone with any interest in the Saudi market.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=SaudiArabia2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f4e01bcc-0278-4da0-9405-e5ee2f472b57.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161128]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161128]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-05T10:23:37.302Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Kuwait]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Kuwait]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuwait City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Kuwait is an interesting and developing Islamic finance market and 2016 will see the third annual IFN Kuwait Forum, building on the success of previous years and with the support of both local regulators and international participants to explore and encourage Shariah compliant investment opportunities into the country.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=Kuwait2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/61fdb71d-18d1-4678-9c20-536ba465b1d0.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161023]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161023]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-05T10:22:33.533Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Oman]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Oman]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Muscat ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest Sukuk regulation issued by the Capital Market Authority is set to see Oman participate more actively in the Islamic finance space, despite being the last player to join the Islamic finance club in the GCC. Oman has made commendable progress since its 2015 debut sovereign Sukuk sale, with another offering expected in the second quarter of 2016. Now with a dedicated legal framework in existence, it is expected that corporate players will take advantage of the conducive environment in tapping the Sukuk space to meet their funding needs. Having hosted the IFN Seminar, Dialogue and Report in 2016, the event for 2017 will evolve into a forum with an expected larger number of participants,against the backdrop of further inroads that Oman has made in the industry thus far. The forum will see experts and investors from neighboring countries weigh in on current economic challenges in light of lower commodity prices and volatile market conditions, and how the development of the Islamic financial market in the country will create an efficient alternative channel to mitigate further disruptions to business and economic activities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=Oman2017]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f0d012a5-f026-4b0c-b513-f5b0d2579d64.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170307]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170307]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-05T10:21:14.561Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Project & Infrastructure Finance]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It is not just geographical markets that make an industry, and adding to the action-packed year ahead, 2016 will see the first-ever IFN Project &amp; Infrastructure Finance Forum taking place in Dubai: a new event focusing on one of the most active sectors in our industry today. Covering areas including transport, energy, renewables, power, utilities, education, health care and more, the Forum will explore issues such as capital-raising, investment avenues, public-private partnerships, the role of intermediaries and much more: and is expected to generate significant interest from the global community.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=ProjectInfrastructureFinance2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2f7b6c4b-10a4-44f9-ab4a-0f00ddda77ac.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161008]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161008]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-05T10:20:04.270Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Iran]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2016 IFN Iran will return for a one-day event in Tehran to provide industry players with an invaluable chance to explore the potential in this immense and immensely exciting market. With the recent sanction agreements and the enormous opportunities now opening up in the country, this intimate Forum and Dialogue will mark the second of many more IFN events in Iran to come.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=Iran2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/b10931bc-3729-4d70-9e1d-0c614cde5d41.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160822]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160822]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-05T10:18:57.769Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Investor]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In April 2015, IFN launched its inaugural IFN Investor Forum in Dubai to great success, allowing participants to focus on exactly the issues that are relevant to them and creating a targeted, effective and efficient platform for discussion, analysis and action on both sides of the industry coin. Going forward, to ensure that the broadest and most effective global coverage is achieved, the annual IFN Investors Forum will alternate between Dubai and Kuala Lumpur. This event will encompass everything related to Islamic investment, attracting a truly global audience and focusing on both the central issues to the area and also on the latest developments, trends and innovations across the sector. The wide-ranging program will include multiple and varied formats and sessions for maximum participation: including a brand new series of issuer case studies.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=Investor2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e7acb3cb-b686-4771-8ab1-5d35d15769fa.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160905]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160905]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-03T14:47:12.810Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Airport Show 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Airport Show provides an ideal B2B platform for companies to present airport and aviation-related products and services.  In 2015, the event gathered over 7,120 aviation professionals who networked, sourced their product requirements and created over US$20 billion worth of regional business possibilities.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.theairportshow.com/portal/home.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5add2683-c6fa-484e-997b-6677bc3fc0cc.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160508]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160510]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-03T13:44:59.788Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Travel Catering & Onboard Services Expo Middle East 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/7af0a48c-26fd-4b4a-91d3-41f8f4acfccd.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>World Travel Catering &amp; Onboard Services Expo Middle East will provide leading global suppliers, caterers and experts a dedicated platform to tap into the opportunities presented by its booming aviation catering business, thus ensuring the sector mirrors the growth and success of the region's aviation industry. The event will feature a full range of products and services relevant to the airport and airline catering industry from food and beverage, travel amenities, and accessories to catering equipment and technologies.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.wtceme.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3af8d0d7-54fd-4fc0-b68b-6270ffa6d82f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160508]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160510]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-05-03T08:36:03.644Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFMA's World Workplace]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>IFMA's World Workplace is the association's flagship event. It is the most longstanding and well-respected conference and exposition for facility management and related workplace professions. Held annually, World Workplace is an interactive conference focused on finding innovative, resourceful solutions to common facility challenges; gaining achievable strategies that will get the attention of customers, supervisors and colleagues; and sharing best practices for managing facilities</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://worldworkplaceuae.ifma.org/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a4e30fe3-64c6-40d3-8210-1cd23d2d2869.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161206]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161207]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-26T07:53:24.153Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Real Estate Business Summit 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Monterrey ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Real Estate Business Summit 2016 will take place on May 12.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://summitmty.inmobiliare.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/38ec9216-2443-4f06-9906-5b46bc90a08f.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160511]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160511]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-26T07:47:31.739Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Expo Negocios Inmobiliarios]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Expo Negocios Inmobiliarios will take place on November 9-11.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.exni.mx/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/153633f4-e6ef-443c-be93-01badac9464e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161109]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161110]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-25T12:04:22.592Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Islamic Economic Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/79e5b546-bc5f-4164-878e-3a566362a67b.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Indonesia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jakarta ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>World Islamic Economic Forum will be held in Jakarta on August 2-4.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://wief.org/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/d6f85d9d-be83-4218-8576-11bcc6596393.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160801]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160803]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-25T11:02:26.748Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Iran Trade & Export Finance Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Iran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Global Trade Review's inaugural Iran Trade &amp; Export Finance Conference will consider the implications of a return to the fold for Iran, as the world considers the possibility of a new area for growth at a time when the global economy most needs it. With a business environment ripe for investment and joint ventures, and a mood of cooperation within the upper echelons of government, Iran is keen to benefit from external expertise in key sectors such as transport, telecommunications, infrastructure, technology, real estate and financial services.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gtreview.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a6b62011-a725-4508-b9b3-2784cd2a9c05.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161107]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161107]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-25T10:13:58.905Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Human Capital Forum MENA]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 11th Human Capital Forum MENA is the region's leading HR platform dedicated to bringing together talent managers, business and thought leaders.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.humanassetsmideast.com/?utm_source=partner&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=thebusinessyear_banner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2d788ff0-6d1c-4234-a287-fde7b1a14201.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160524]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160525]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-22T12:21:02.638Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia International Oil & Gas Exhibition (SAOGE 2016)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dammam ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Should you wish to join us please contact us at exhibition@saoge.org</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.saoge.org/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/2d4cac8d-b59f-4f07-b5ca-8ff05e571d82.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161016]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161018]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-18T10:35:34.999Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Saudi Power 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Riyadh ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Saudi Power gathers all the major industry buyers under one roof who are looking for the latest products to service their multi-million dollar projects.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.saudi-power.com/en/Forms/VisitorRegistrationForm/?prioritycode=THE%20BUSINESS%20YEAR&utm_source=THE%20BUSINESS%20YEAR&utm_medium=BANNER&utm_campaign=MEDIA%20PARTNER]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8e0ca568-9626-4fae-bb27-0d07b384290f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160508]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160510]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-15T12:59:25.274Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[4th Annual Malaysia Rail 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>4th Annual Malaysia Rail to be held on 25 – 26 July 2016, will focus on some of the major ongoing and upcoming railway projects in South East Asia. The conference will ideate on next generation policy, procedural and regulatory initiatives needed to attract investments in the railway sector. Associates will delve into the state of development and trends in bench marking for the Malaysian railways in operational parameters. The conference will provide participants an update on technology up-gradation and joint ventures with equipment manufacturers.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bricsaconsulting.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/95b5f439-2ff3-427a-b9e5-626272c6c478.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160724]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160725]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-14T12:34:26.586Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[2nd Iran Mines & Mining Industries Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/86c45124-7bb9-4d47-95c3-27770a8f517a.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Iran]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tehran ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Holding IMIS2015 as a successful summit which gathered together more than 1670 delegates from 590 companies came from 21 Countries in Tehran, encouraged us in IMIDRO (Iranian Mines and Mining Industries Development and Renovation Organization) to kindly announce IMIS 2016 (Iran's Mines and Mining Industries Summit) which takes place on July 11-12, 2016 in Tehran, I.R. of Iran. Iran is blessed with abundant Mineral and energy recourses, a young, educated and experienced workforce, a relatively untouched market of 75 million, access to international water ways, low cost labor, a developed infrastructure of roads, railways, ports, power supply and telecommunication network, together with asset of investor friendly laws and regulations; all of which makes Iran a particularly attractive country for international investors.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.iicic.com/imis2016/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0f70c176-65d7-4164-b17b-204b792c16bd.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160710]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160711]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-12T12:19:14.640Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Saudi-American Healthcare Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Riyadh ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>From Arab to American scientists, Saudi Arabia and the US have been a crossroads of science and creativity in the world of healthcare innovation. Both regions share many common interests and increasingly interdependent economies.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.sahf16.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/fd45100b-92a3-4731-a54c-37e2960a8b0c.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160422]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160426]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-12T06:58:09.872Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mexico Energy Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Mexican Energy Forum will be held in response to the recent Energy Reforms in Mexico and will be covering the complete spectrum of Mexico's opportunities in the energy sector, assessing key investment areas in the upstream, midstream/infrastructure, electricity, power and downstream sector. The event will also cover important industry priorities and challenges, including local content, security, fiscal terms and more.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://energy-dialogues.com/mef/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/991e71a4-d66b-4706-a938-5e7af3e21c87.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160711]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160713]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-08T11:32:10.897Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[CEE & Turkey Refining & Petrochemicals]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Izmir ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Returning to Izmir, Turkey, the event this year will reflect on the changes and developments which took place in 2015 and look forward in a challenging environment to discuss what lies ahead for the region and how refineries and petrochemical companies, along with their suppliers, can survive and even thrive in a difficult climate. You can also participate in a site visit to the STAR refinery which will include updates on developments from the past two years and operational challenges and opportunities as the site nears completion.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://cee.wraconferences.com/partners/http://cee.wraconferences.com/brochure-mp/?utm_source=external&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=the%20business%20year%20brochure]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3d44c375-78a0-4156-aa25-da435d45ad63.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160918]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160920]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-07T12:54:21.168Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Global African Investment Summit (Kigali)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/15cfdc89-45a4-4920-bc47-7e0ba292ce97.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Rwanda]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kigali ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Under the patronage of His Excellency Paul Kagame, President of the Republic of Rwanda, the summit will play host to multiple African heads of state, government ministers and private sector business leaders. Bankable projects and business opportunities will be presented.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.tgais-kigali.com/?%20utm_source=mediapartner&utm_medium=advert&utm_campaign=thebusinessyear]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/5e89130a-2e4b-4b16-ae36-04428fc77361.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160904]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160905]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-06T07:49:32.070Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Kazakhstan Investment Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Kazakhstan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Astana ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Economist Events' inaugural Kazakhstan Investment Summit will analyse the progress made by the country on its route to delivering on economic diversification, discuss the improvements needed and explore where the investment opportunities lie.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/kazakhstan-investment-2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ec389666-ec95-4381-84be-3adb4452e69c.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160524]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160524]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-05T12:20:52.273Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[ArabNet Digital Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/e702b910-4137-4598-b96d-d6ac9415f963.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The ArabNet Digital Summit will bring together industry leaders from brands, publishers, agencies and technology platforms to discuss the latest challenges and opportunities in digital media and marketing. With the surge of platforms, the race is on to capture consumer share of mind and share of wallet. ArabNet will tackle how to leverage native and programmatic advertising, snapchat and new social media platforms, video content and much more.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://arabnet.me/conference/summit/?utm_source=TheBusinessYear&utm_medium=WebBanner&utm_content=Generic492x103px&utm_campaign=AS16]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f11b95b8-62c2-4805-a545-19519ce8982d.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160529]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160530]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-04T13:08:14.773Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Africa Energy Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/424896a6-0980-438e-b643-6ed4f7433ace.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 18th Africa Energy Forum (AEF) will be hosted at London's newest landmark, the prestigious Intercontinental O2, London 22nd– 24th June. Undoubtedly the most respected and established gathering of power players, the Africa Energy Forum is the global investment meeting for Africa's power, energy, infrastructure &amp; industrial sectors.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://africa-energy-forum.com/?utm_campaign=Mediahttp://africa-energy-forum.com/?utm_campaign=Media Partner&utm_medium=Banner&utm_source=The Business Year]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1b3c776c-48cd-4c38-bfe9-6d45a6e71890.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160621]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160623]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-04T11:28:44.529Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Agritech Expo Zambia 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Zambia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Chisamba ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Attend Agritech Expo Zambia 2016 and learn from the experts in agriculture by attending free-to-attend technical workshops.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.agritech-expo.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3bb20cc6-e9ef-4a4a-b877-2aff0a07dcaa.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160413]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160415]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-04T07:47:07.527Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[IFN Forum Asia 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Indonesia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jakarta ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>As major Asian economies begin to seriously assess the prospects of Islamic capital raising the IFN Asia Forum will continue to deliver on its promise: to provide delegates with prospects, opportunities and current trends in mature and new Islamic finance markets in Asia.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://redmoneyevents.com/main/event.asp?IFN=Asia2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8b76517c-f73b-4988-92d5-b54aa68d43e9.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160405]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160406]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-01T12:54:58.721Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[UK Shale Gas Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/c3636be1-2ba4-411f-967d-c027cc2b7cb1.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Manchester ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The UK Shale Gas Summit 2016 (formerly   E-SGOS) is a two-day planning and strategy event for the UK onshore oil and gas industry. The summit will address the role for shale gas in the new energy infrastructure and consider the latest developments, strategies and opportunities within UK unconventional exploration &amp; production. Through a combination of conference discussions, technical workshops and networking the summit will provide a platform for stakeholders to discuss key debates, maximise potential and accelerate growth with the UK shale gas industry.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.esgos.eu/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c95c9349-765c-4dab-91bd-6c916e23dbfc.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161010]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161011]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-01T12:06:41.030Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Growing Economies Energy Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/a22d7f2b-f331-4be0-b275-6294a4ecd7ea.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > UK]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[London ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Growing Economies Energy Forum will host open discussions between the Governments and pre private sector from the most exciting and anticipated new energy markets in the world – Iran, Pakistan, Myanmar and Pacific Alliance (Peru, Chile, Colombia, Mexico). As these growing economies open up for international investment following exciting political and economic developments, each are starting a new exciting era in their energy markets that the industry's big players can't ignore.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.energynet.co.uk/event/growing-economies-latin-america-energy-forum]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160622]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160622]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-04-01T08:20:59.472Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Offshore Opportunities Colombia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bogotá ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>There is recent renewed confidence in an upwards trajectory of energy prices – and Colombia's offshore oil and gas potential has piqued the interest of E&amp;P and service companies – both local and global. The Energy Conference Network's Offshore Opportunities Colombia conference brings together key Government stakeholders, local and international E&amp;P operators and service companies to discuss blocks, partnerships and the promising results thus far.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://energyconferencenetwork.com/ooc/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a5962ef7-688b-4ebb-9cc2-2d401791d1f6.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160405]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160406]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-31T06:30:50.330Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 10th National Congress of Free Trade Zones]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Colombia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Santa Marta ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>ANDI, the National Business Association of Colombia presents the 10th version of the event Congreso Zonas Francas, which aims to present the important changes in the free trade zones regulation, in custom and foreign trade matters. This changes will positively impact the user operators, as well as the industrial and commercial companies, special free zones and businesses interested in new projects. In april 8th, the First Meeting of free trade zones will be held, a new reunion to encourage commercial exchange and the creation of new alliances between the free trade zone users and companies from other sectors.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.andi.com.co/10_Congreso_Zonas_Francas/paginas/index.html]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/ea4b3709-5e33-4f60-a4d8-bcdf490d558e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160406]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160407]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-28T13:34:08.972Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Third Annual Energy Conference Energy and Sustainable Development 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/d951ba57-1926-4a41-80f9-7ebb74f64805.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In 10 May 2016, Business News Foundation is holding its third annual energy conference amid numerous shifts at the local, regional and global levels and in the trends of investment in the energy sector.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://beta.bnegypt.com/en/events/the-third-annual-energy-conference-energy-and-future-of-investment-in-egypt/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/82b33220-4590-4828-8bfa-930bb7e4ee43.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160509]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160509]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-28T07:06:56.680Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Cityscape Qatar]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/85b231e5-a6cc-41ee-b3f3-3e91e76018a4.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Qatar]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Doha ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Under the Patronage of H.E. Sheikh Abdullah Bin Nasser Bin Khalifa Al-Thani, The Prime Minister and Minister of the Interior for the State of Qatar.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.cityscapeqatar.com/forms/register-your-visit?utm_source=Free%20Media%20Partner&utm_medium=Display&utm_campaign=thebusinessyear_webbanner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e5530be4-26a0-49f2-9ef4-58b79af61346.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160425]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160427]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-22T10:54:55.304Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur International Aerospace Business Convention 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Malaysia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Kuala Lumpur ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The first of its kind in Malaysia, Aerospace Business Convention Kuala Lumpur is an excellent opportunity for leaders of the aerospace industry to meet with potential industry partners.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.bciaerospace.com/malaysia/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/df1ffa8f-e34b-4d94-b27e-d89f7701ae7a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161207]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161209]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-21T15:34:35.071Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Retail Congress]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>World Retail Congress was founded in 2007 in response to retailers seeking a platform for senior leaders to come together to discuss the major issues and trends affecting the industry. In delivering this agenda, the Congress has welcomed thousands of senior retail speakers, from some of the world's biggest, to the newest businesses, as well as leading industry stakeholders from global economics, politics, finance and NGOs.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.worldretailcongress.com/find-more-world-retail-congress?utm_source=TBY&utm_medium=Partner&utm_campaign=WRC_16_Visprom&utm_content=MediaPartner]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/57ae2e0c-9e40-4a5a-a1f4-49abe37f3d86.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160411]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160413]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-15T14:05:17.801Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[ICSG Istanbul 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>ICSG Istanbul 2016 will be held on 20-21 April 2016 in Istanbul, Turkey.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.icsgistanbul.com/en/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7418e994-2436-435f-b897-5fad0f321095.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160419]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160420]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-15T08:23:39.441Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Turkey Hospital Expansion Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Ankara ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>At the 3rd Annual Turkey Hospital Expansion Summit, government officials, construction companies, management groups and hospital owners will go in discussion with consultants, lenders, architects, medical companies, equipment providers and service groups, in order to better explore the market and support project`s development.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://turkey.hospitalexpansionsummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/6460937f-4262-4d17-b4bc-75edcb8dccf9.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161004]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161005]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-15T08:21:09.363Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Africa Hospital Expansion Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Ghana]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Accra ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>After successful editions in South-Africa, Zambia and Mozambique Noppen is hosting the 4th Annual Africa Hospital Expansion Summit in West-Africa, Ghana, Accra. At the event government officials, investors, operators, architects and contractors will be meeting medical device suppliers, technology and service vendors, consultants, banks and regulatory bodies.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://africa.hospitalexpansionsummit.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8e885d47-01e2-464f-ac24-cb24eba09e76.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160921]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160922]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-14T12:58:47.972Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Turkey Trade & Export Finance Conference 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Following 2015's highly successful event which welcomed 442 delegates, re-affirming its position as the country's trade finance conference of choice, GTR's Turkey Trade &amp; Export Finance Conference returns to Istanbul on March 22-23.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gtreview.com/events/europe/turkey-trade-export-finance-conference-2016/?utm_source=TBY&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=socialmedia]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/c60c83b7-332f-4ab3-94e5-4cb03140031f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160322]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160323]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-14T09:45:46.890Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[World Aviation Safety Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Returning for its 4th edition, the World Aviation Safety Summit (25 - 26 April 2016, Dubai, UAE), hosted by the Dubai Civil Aviation Authority has been established as the meeting place for thought leaders of the global aviation safety sector to discuss essential safety measures in order to efficiently manage the processes, threats, risks and calamities facing aviation safety professionals worldwide.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://bit.ly/1YMbPqE]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/9bf26dba-1a0a-4cf6-a7af-39a764670ae4.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160424]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160425]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-14T09:43:53.325Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Mobile World Congress Shanghai 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/6f5c93b0-80f0-4969-855e-84057443db7c.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > China]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Shanghai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.mwcshanghai.com/">GSMA Mobile World Congress Shanghai 2016</a> will showcase the incredible possibilities offered by mobile. Senior industry professionals will gather, network, learn new ideas and make important connections to grow their business in coming years. Passionate consumers will meet to discover the latest devices and innovative technologies. Don't miss this truly unique event. Make plans to join us in Shanghai, 29 June - 1 July 2016, where our global audience will celebrate the individuality of mobile. <a href="http://www.mwcshanghai.com/register-plan/register-now/">Register today</a> with code <strong>FEPIMOCYFM</strong> for a <strong>complimentary Industry Exhibition Pass</strong> courtesy of our partner.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mwcshanghai.com/?utm_campaign=SHANPB&utm_source=BusinessYear&utm_medium=Banner&utm_term=Website&utm_content=492103]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/7c052bab-ea19-4d0d-89b3-5bd2bd3f80dc.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160628]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160630]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-14T09:38:36.041Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Cityscape Egypt]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/7efe4c8d-2235-48b4-84a4-7aca04091f8b.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Egypt]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Cairo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Cityscape Egypt will be held on 7-10 April 2016 in Cairo.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.cityscapeegypt.com/forms/visitor-pre-registration-form?utm_source=Free%20Media%20Partner&utm_medium=Display&utm_campaign=TBY%20Social%20Post%201]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/30416ba6-9af6-4e4a-a8bb-a25d9c764992.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160406]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160409]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-09T15:08:40.276Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Astana Mining & Metallurgy 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Kazakhstan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Congress]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Astana ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The organizers of the Congress are: the Ministry for Investment and Development of the Republic of Kazakhstan, Kazakhstani exhibition company Iteca and its international partner ITE Group Plc (UK).</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://amm.kz/en/?utm_source=business_year&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=1]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/dd9fcff5-2eb1-429b-a33e-43229bddacdf.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160614]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160615]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-04T12:17:46.389Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Middle East & North Africa Project Finance Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Middle East &amp; North Africa Project Finance Forum is taking place on the 21st &amp; 22nd March 2016 at the Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Dubai. The conference will gather key representatives from across the project financing chain, including leading developers, lenders, advisors, law firms and investors. With oil prices impacting liquidity levels across the region, we are anticipating a change in the dynamics of the project financing market. The discussions will explore this change, and the subsequent opportunities in financing for the private sector, in addition to the current and future demand for project financing across the Middle East and North Africa.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.euromoneyseminars.com/details/8774/the-middle-east-and-north-africa-project-finance-forum/details.html]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8631534a-08c2-49dc-b8f9-ec4432dbe1e5.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160321]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160322]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-04T07:55:33.827Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Gastech]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/9ec0e427-eace-4ac4-936a-e01cb4e921db.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Japan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Exhibition & Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Tokyo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Gastech is the world's leading exhibition, conference and networking event, bringing together thousands of technical innovators and commercial experts to deliver global success stories. The event represents and addresses the current commercial and technical challenges spanning the entire natural gas &amp; LNG supply chain Gastech's broad, diverse programme is shaped by energy professionals to deliver outstanding insight, create exceptional networking and new business opportunities, whilst ensuring a robust return-on-investment.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gastechevent.com/call-for-papers/?utm_source=the-business-year&utm_medium=Website-Banner&utm_term=the-business-year-banner&utm_content=Conference-CFP&utm_campaign=Media-Partners]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/de942f04-6f59-48c3-88f9-27c5ad91e71e.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20170403]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20170406]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-04T07:51:57.884Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[KIOGE Kazakhstan]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Kazakhstan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Almaty ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>KIOGE Kazakhstan will be held on October 4-7 in Almaty.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.kioge.kz/ru/?utm_source=thebusinessyear-com&utm_medium=banner&utm_term=thebusinessyear&utm_campaign=KIOGE%202016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/83a25f04-1b3f-4598-96b6-76ab410d9e57.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161003]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161006]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-03T13:05:12.409Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Buildexpo 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Tanzania]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dar es Salaam ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 19th Buildexpo 2016 - International Trade Expo on Building &amp; Construction Products, Equipment. &amp; Machinery, is the largest trade event held annually in Tanzania. The exhibition attracts exhibitors from more than 30 countries and visitors from all over East &amp; Central Africa, thus giving exhibitors an excellent opportunity to explore several countries in one time.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.expogr.com/tanzania/buildexpo/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4efb2302-1364-4b17-a1e3-a9b09d89b0ba.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160701]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160703]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-03T12:38:34.872Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[GCC Waste Management & Recycling Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The purpose of this conference is to review recent experiences in this field and highlight lessons learned and identify critical gaps to be addressed. The event seeks to explore inter-sectoral partnerships as a means to achieving sustainable waste management systems. Point of departure is that the highest level of service and maximum benefit is gained when the municipality sees its waste management mandate and responsibilities clearly, but nevertheless can make use of the strengths of the various other actors such as Government authorities, private sector and social organizations.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.gccwmf.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/a65e31e5-eefc-439e-8a66-999ac4c40da5.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160528]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160530]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-03T09:28:24.444Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The FT Asia Banking Forum]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Singapore]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The FT Asia Banking Forum will bring together industry professionals from all corners of the banking ecosystem, providing a platform where practitioners can reflect on the trends that are redefining many elements of banking and what this means for different divisions and functions. C-suite executives, strategists, heads of technology, risk, compliance, and other specialists will share insights on the opportunities and challenges banks are presented with in the current volatile macroeconomic environment, and in today's increasingly crowded and competitive marketplace.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://live.ft.com/AsiaBanking?reference=TBY]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/0bf28abd-66fb-45b1-9de1-bbb67a6ec86f.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160621]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160621]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-03T09:27:16.683Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[FT Investment Management Summit: Asia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > China]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Hong Kong ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Now in its fifth year, the Investment Management Summit Asia provides an unrivalled platform where institutional investors, leading asset management CEOs, economists, portfolio managers and analysts come together to discuss the big issues defining the investment landscape.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://live.ft.com/IMSA?reference=TBY]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/997952e7-d0cb-48ab-86ad-269a4d63a447.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160615]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160615]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-02T11:04:34.855Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[12th Trans Middle East 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jeddah ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Park Hyatt Jeddah – Marina, Club &amp; Spa, Jeddah, Saudi ArabiaWednesday 26  and  Thursday 27 October 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.transportevents.com/ForthcomingEvents.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/97c562e9-d689-4968-9525-69e69d0035c4.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161025]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161026]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-02T11:03:37.836Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[16th Intermodal Africa 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Kenya]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mombasa ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Sarova Whitesands Beach Resort &amp; Spa, Mombasa, KenyaThursday 17  and  Friday 18 November 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.transportevents.com/ForthcomingEvents.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/46ac0485-74f1-4634-8caf-a031ba561307.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161117]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161118]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-02T11:02:28.019Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[15th Intermodal Africa 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Ghana]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Accra ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mövenpick Ambassador Hotel Accra, GhanaThursday 07  and  Friday 08 April 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.transportevents.com/ForthcomingEvents.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4f30eddb-b249-455f-a2bf-6d4d15b17863.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160406]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160407]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-02T11:00:45.165Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[14th ASEAN Ports and Shipping 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Landmark Bangkok, ThailandThursday 14  and  Friday 15 July 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.transportevents.com/ForthcomingEvents.aspx]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/4a664605-456b-4b4d-a45a-ce5ae5196bf9.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160713]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160714]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-03-01T10:51:02.114Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Middle East Rail 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Dubai ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Under the honorary patronage of His Highness Sheikh Mansour Bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Prime Minister, Minister of Presidential AffairsH.E. Dr. Abdulla Belhaif Al Nuaimi, Minister of Public Works and Chairman of the Federal Transport Authority - Land &amp; Maritimeis delighted to invite you to attend Middle East Rail 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://secure.terrapinn.com/V5/step1.aspx?E=7934&p=1&utm_source=tby&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=tby]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/14866d15-4aea-4a7b-a04e-c7b9a7ee5027.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160308]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160309]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-29T07:44:44.679Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The Abu Dhabi International Petroleum Exhibition & Conference (ADIPEC)]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/a0152663-4d63-4605-b41e-f88a9d9efe13.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Abu Dhabi International Petroleum Exhibition &amp; Conference (ADIPEC) will be held on Nov7-11 in Abu Dhabi, UAE.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.adipec.com/conference/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3894c2df-8c23-479f-a0a8-13caded17743.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161107]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161110]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-26T08:38:20.808Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Kazakhstan Power & Renewable Energy Investment Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Kazakhstan]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Astana ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Euroconvention Global is inviting up to 150 renewable energy projects developers, engineering, consulting and advisory companies in the energy sector to attend the Kazakhstan Power &amp; Renewable Energy Investment Conference taking place in Astana on 20 and 21 April 2016.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.conventionventures.com/events.php?action=details&event_id=113]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/1cb8b108-787a-4d83-8357-75010a307988.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160419]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160420]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-25T14:50:16.783Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Qatar Projects]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Qatar]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Doha ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Under the patronage of H.E. Sheikh Ahmed bin Jassim Al Thani, Minister of Economy and Commerce and endorsed by the Ministry of Economy and Commerce in Qatar.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.qatarprojectsconference.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/435f1dcb-c3d7-4f86-813a-ece1de8ada86.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160315]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160318]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-25T14:47:33.966Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[EXPO TURISMO INTERNACIONAL 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Panama]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Panama City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>EXPO TURISMO INTERNACIONAL 2016 will be held in Panam on May 27-28.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/51de4b93-436d-494d-afef-77dc6f897346.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160526]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160527]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-25T14:45:19.856Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[EXPO LOGÍSTICA PANAMÁ]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Panama]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Expo]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Panama City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>EXPO LOGÍSTICA PANAMÁ will be held in Panama on October 19-21.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.expologistica.org/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/cea39815-194b-43f1-b7e0-be2b86db8948.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20161018]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20161020]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-22T15:33:05.316Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[PPP Healthcare Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Our 2016 Summit will bring together the key stakeholders in the Healthcare PPP Ecosystem including those working on successful PPP projects in North America, Europe and Asia, to share lessons learned so far. From establishing the legal framework and securing financing to operating and maintaining a profitable hospital, this event will explore the entire lifecycle of the agreement from the perspective of all parties.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.ppphealth.com/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/3e8f7a13-f820-40fc-8c8f-e65132559c00.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160425]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160427]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-22T11:13:09.087Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Jeddah Economic Forum 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > Saudi Arabia]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Forum]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Jeddah ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Jeddah Economic Forum (JEF) 2016 will focus on public private partnerships (PPP) with a view to privatization in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia. Historically an oil-based economy, the Kingdom now seeks to diversify, and is keen on involving private stakeholders. Such a shift introduces lucrative commercial possibilities, but it also presents potential challenges. Bringing together high ranking government officials, international businesses, policy makers and global experts, JEF 2016 is a unique forum to discuss and debate solutions to overcome these challenges, explore business opportunities, and assess economic benefits offered by the evolving landscape of the Kingdom.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.jef.org.sa/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e83f3631-6b02-4a08-8543-19d8913d2fb8.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160301]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160303]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-22T08:27:55.010Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[FT Turkey Summit 2016]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Europe & CIS > Turkey]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Istanbul ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 4th annual FT Turkey Summit will examine the increasingly significant role of Turkey on the global stage, the positive shifts in the political and business landscape that are drawing international investors to its shores, and some of the challenges to expect along the way.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[https://live.ft.com/Events/2016/FT-Turkey-Summit-2016?reference=&utm_source=bwe&utm_medium=supporting%20partner%20website&utm_content=gen&utm_campaign=2016FTTurkeySummit]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/e06c56a2-b97d-4b85-8b75-26d84d52c7ea.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160524]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160524]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-19T09:50:34.228Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[The 24th Annual Middle East Petroleum & Gas Conference]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Middle East > UAE]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Conference]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>MPGC, is the region's longest running annual oil &amp; gas conference, taking place annually and attracting the captains of the oil and gas industry globally. Running since 1993, MPGC enjoys the Patronage of the highest political support in each venue, having had six national oil company hosts in its 24 year history.  MPGC 2016, hosted by the Abu Dhabi National Oil Company, bringing together 500 participants from more than 150 global companies and 50 countries.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.mpgc.cc/]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/8fdf9d72-9995-4eba-b381-2c1457f61d30.gif]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160423]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160425]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-18T14:30:47.732Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Carriers World Asia]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Asia > Thailand]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Event]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Bangkok ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Next month, over 300 telecommunications executives from across 100 organizations will convene at the 18th annual Carriers World Asia – the region's leading forum for wholesale carriers and operators. With discussions on the future of voice, the evolution of the carrier-OTT relationship, game-changing technologies and updates on emerging markets in the region, don't miss out on your opportunity to meet and learn from key decision makers influencing the future of Asia's telecommunications industry.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.terrapinn.com/conference/carriers-world-asia/?utm_source=thebusinessyear&utm_medium=op&utm_content=listing&utm_campaign=op-thebusinessyear]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/72091f99-04a3-4bb8-8941-e17b6adf81ab.png]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160315]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160316]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-18T12:14:30.856Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[Southern Africa Energy & Infrastructure Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/Content/events/pressrelease/505aef33-21bd-4678-ac2a-8e13381ada9b.pdf]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Africa > Mozambique]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Maputo ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>EnergyNet are excited to launch the groundbreaking Southern Africa Energy and Infrastructure Summit (SAEIS), which will bring together countries from the SADC region and beyond.  Regional development is the key to unlocking Africa's energy investment potential - it is with this in mind that EnergyNet are delighted to bring these countries together in Maputo, Mozambique, the Heart of Southern Africa, from 4th to 6th of May to celebrate regional co-operation and promote energy and infrastructure projects that require both private- and public-sector support to succeed.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://www.energynet.co.uk/event/southern-africa-energy-infrastructure-summit-2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/cfc2fdc9-5a78-4bd9-898a-62ef16f1f5c1.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160503]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160505]]></enddate>
	</node>
	<node>
		<inserttime><![CDATA[2016-02-18T11:53:42.136Z]]></inserttime>
		<name><![CDATA[6th Latam Power Generation Summit]]></name>
		<pressreleaseurl><![CDATA[]]></pressreleaseurl>
		<geocountryname><![CDATA[Latin America & Caribbean > Mexico]]></geocountryname>
		<eventtypeid><![CDATA[Summit]]></eventtypeid>
		<location><![CDATA[Mexico City ]]></location>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The 6th Latam Power Generation Summit will be held in Mexico City on August 10-11.</p>]]></description>
		<linkurl><![CDATA[http://events.bnamericas.com/bnamericas_events/6latampowersummit/en/?utm_source=tby&utm_medium=banner&utm_campaign=LPGS2016]]></linkurl>
		<oldbannerurl><![CDATA[https://www.thebusinessyear.com/content/events/f980d180-7a37-44b3-aece-8f951000042a.jpg]]></oldbannerurl>
		<startdate><![CDATA[20160809]]></startdate>
		<enddate><![CDATA[20160810]]></enddate>
	</node>
</data>
